[
    {
        "Front": "嗚呼",
        "Back": "Ah!;Oh!;Alas!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "Front": "相",
        "Back": "together;mutually;fellow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "Front": "相変わらず",
        "Back": "as ever;as usual;the same",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "Front": "愛想",
        "Back": "civility;courtesy;compliments;sociability;graces",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "Front": "相対",
        "Back": "confrontation;facing;between ourselves;no third party;tete-a-tete",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 4
    },
    {
        "Front": "間柄",
        "Back": "relation(ship)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 5
    },
    {
        "Front": "愛憎",
        "Back": "likes and dislikes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 6
    },
    {
        "Front": "合間",
        "Back": "interval",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 7
    },
    {
        "Front": "曖昧",
        "Back": "vague;ambiguous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 8
    },
    {
        "Front": "敢えて",
        "Back": "dare (to do);challenge (to do)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 9
    },
    {
        "Front": "仰ぐ",
        "Back": "to look up (to);to respect;to depend on;to ask for;to seek;to revere;to drink;to take",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 10
    },
    {
        "Front": "垢",
        "Back": "dirt;filth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 11
    },
    {
        "Front": "亜科",
        "Back": "suborder;subfamily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 12
    },
    {
        "Front": "銅",
        "Back": "copper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 13
    },
    {
        "Front": "証",
        "Back": "proof;evidence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 14
    },
    {
        "Front": "赤字",
        "Back": "deficit;go in the red",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 15
    },
    {
        "Front": "明かす",
        "Back": "to pass;spend;to reveal;to divulge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 16
    },
    {
        "Front": "赤ちゃん",
        "Back": "baby;infant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 17
    },
    {
        "Front": "明白",
        "Back": "obvious;overt;plainly;frankly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 18
    },
    {
        "Front": "赤らむ",
        "Back": "to become red;to redden;to blush",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 19
    },
    {
        "Front": "明るい",
        "Back": "bright;cheerful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 20
    },
    {
        "Front": "上がり",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;slope;advance income;crop yield;ascent;rise;advance;death;spinning;completion;stop;finish;after",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 21
    },
    {
        "Front": "上がる",
        "Back": "to enter;to go up;to rise;to climb up;to advance;to appreciate;to be promoted;to improve;to call on;",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 22
    },
    {
        "Front": "商人",
        "Back": "trader;shopkeeper;merchant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 23
    },
    {
        "Front": "空間",
        "Back": "vacancy;room for rent or lease",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 24
    },
    {
        "Front": "諦め",
        "Back": "resignation;acceptance;consolation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 25
    },
    {
        "Front": "呆れる",
        "Back": "to be amazed;to be shocked",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 26
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪",
        "Back": "evil;wickedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 27
    },
    {
        "Front": "灰",
        "Back": "puckery juice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 28
    },
    {
        "Front": "あくどい",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;gaudy;showy;excessive; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;vicious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪日",
        "Back": "unlucky day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 29
    },
    {
        "Front": "明くる",
        "Back": "next;following",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 30
    },
    {
        "Front": "憧れ",
        "Back": "yearning;longing;aspiration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 31
    },
    {
        "Front": "顎",
        "Back": "chin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 32
    },
    {
        "Front": "麻",
        "Back": "flax;linen;hemp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 33
    },
    {
        "Front": "明後日",
        "Back": "day after tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 34
    },
    {
        "Front": "朝寝坊",
        "Back": "oversleeping;late riser",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 35
    },
    {
        "Front": "浅ましい",
        "Back": "wretched;miserable;shameful;mean;despicable;abject",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 36
    },
    {
        "Front": "字",
        "Back": "section of village",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 37
    },
    {
        "Front": "欺く",
        "Back": "to deceive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 38
    },
    {
        "Front": "鮮やか",
        "Back": "vivid;clear;brilliant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 39
    },
    {
        "Front": "あざ笑う",
        "Back": "to sneer at;to ridicule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 40
    },
    {
        "Front": "味わい",
        "Back": "flavour;meaning;significance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 41
    },
    {
        "Front": "東",
        "Back": "east;Eastern Japan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 42
    },
    {
        "Front": "焦る",
        "Back": "to be in a hurry;to be impatient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 43
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼処",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;(uk) there;over there;that place; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;(X) (col) genitals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 44
    },
    {
        "Front": "値",
        "Back": "value;price;cost;worth;merit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 45
    },
    {
        "Front": "値する",
        "Back": "to be worth;to deserve;to merit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 46
    },
    {
        "Front": "私",
        "Back": "I (fem)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 47
    },
    {
        "Front": "当たり",
        "Back": "hit;success;reaching the mark;per ...;vicinity;neighborhood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 48
    },
    {
        "Front": "当たり前",
        "Back": "usual;common;ordinary;natural;reasonable;obvious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 49
    },
    {
        "Front": "他人",
        "Back": "another person;unrelated person;outsider;stranger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 50
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼方此方",
        "Back": "here and there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 51
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼方",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;there;yonder;that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 52
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪化",
        "Back": "deterioration;growing worse;aggravation;degeneration;corruption",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 53
    },
    {
        "Front": "呆気ない",
        "Back": "not enough;too quick (short&nbsp;&nbsp;long&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 54
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪口",
        "Back": "abuse;insult;slander;evil speaking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 55
    },
    {
        "Front": "あっさり",
        "Back": "easily;readily;quickly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "圧迫",
        "Back": "pressure;coercion;oppression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 56
    },
    {
        "Front": "扱い",
        "Back": "treatment;service",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 57
    },
    {
        "Front": "集まる",
        "Back": "to gather;to collect;to assemble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 58
    },
    {
        "Front": "誂える",
        "Back": "to give an order;to place an order",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 59
    },
    {
        "Front": "圧力",
        "Back": "stress;pressure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 60
    },
    {
        "Front": "当て",
        "Back": "object;aim;end;hopes;expectations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 61
    },
    {
        "Front": "宛",
        "Back": "addressed to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 62
    },
    {
        "Front": "当て字",
        "Back": "phonetic-equivalent character;substitute character",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 63
    },
    {
        "Front": "当てはまる",
        "Back": "to apply (a rule)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 64
    },
    {
        "Front": "当てはめる",
        "Back": "to apply;to adapt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 65
    },
    {
        "Front": "宛てる",
        "Back": "to address",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 66
    },
    {
        "Front": "跡継ぎ",
        "Back": "heir;successor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 67
    },
    {
        "Front": "後回し",
        "Back": "putting off;postponing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 68
    },
    {
        "Front": "貴女",
        "Back": "you;lady",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 69
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼の",
        "Back": "that over there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 70
    },
    {
        "Front": "溢れる",
        "Back": "to flood;to overflow;to brim over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 71
    },
    {
        "Front": "油絵",
        "Back": "oil painting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 72
    },
    {
        "Front": "炙る",
        "Back": "to scorch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 73
    },
    {
        "Front": "あべこべ",
        "Back": "contrary;opposite;inverse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "甘える",
        "Back": "to behave like a spoiled child;to fawn on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 74
    },
    {
        "Front": "甘口",
        "Back": "sweet flavour;mildness;flattery;stupidity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 75
    },
    {
        "Front": "雨具",
        "Back": "rain gear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 76
    },
    {
        "Front": "天",
        "Back": "heavenly;imperial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 77
    },
    {
        "Front": "網",
        "Back": "net;network",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 78
    },
    {
        "Front": "天地",
        "Back": "heaven and earth;the universe;nature;top and bottom;realm;sphere;world",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 79
    },
    {
        "Front": "操る",
        "Back": "to manipulate;to operate;to pull strings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 80
    },
    {
        "Front": "あやふや",
        "Back": "uncertain;vague;ambiguous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "危ぶむ",
        "Back": "to fear;to have misgivings;to be doubtful;to mistrust",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 81
    },
    {
        "Front": "過ち",
        "Back": "fault;error;indiscretion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 82
    },
    {
        "Front": "誤る",
        "Back": "to make a mistake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 83
    },
    {
        "Front": "歩み",
        "Back": "walking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 84
    },
    {
        "Front": "歩む",
        "Back": "to walk;to go on foot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 85
    },
    {
        "Front": "あら",
        "Back": "oh;ah;saw-edged perch (Niphon spinosus)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "予め",
        "Back": "beforehand;in advance;previously",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 86
    },
    {
        "Front": "荒らす",
        "Back": "to lay waste;to devastate;to damage;to invade;to break into",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 87
    },
    {
        "Front": "粗筋",
        "Back": "outline;summary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 88
    },
    {
        "Front": "争い",
        "Back": "dispute;strife;quarrel;dissension;conflict;rivalry;contest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 89
    },
    {
        "Front": "改まる",
        "Back": "to be renewed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 90
    },
    {
        "Front": "荒っぽい",
        "Back": "rough;rude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 91
    },
    {
        "Front": "凡ゆる",
        "Back": "all;every",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 92
    },
    {
        "Front": "あられ",
        "Back": "kind of cookie;cartoon character",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "現われ",
        "Back": "embodiment;materialization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 93
    },
    {
        "Front": "現われる",
        "Back": "to appear;to come in sight;to become visible;to come out;to embody;to materialize;to express oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 94
    },
    {
        "Front": "有難う",
        "Back": "Thank you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 95
    },
    {
        "Front": "有様",
        "Back": "state;condition;circumstances;the way things are or should be;truth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 96
    },
    {
        "Front": "有りのまま",
        "Back": "the truth;fact;as it is;frankly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 97
    },
    {
        "Front": "或る",
        "Back": "a certain...;some...",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 98
    },
    {
        "Front": "或いは",
        "Back": "or;possibly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 99
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼此",
        "Back": "one thing or another;this and that;this or that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 100
    },
    {
        "Front": "合わす",
        "Back": "to join together;to face;to unite;to be opposite;to combine;to connect;to add up;to mix;to match;to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 101
    },
    {
        "Front": "合わせ",
        "Back": "joint together;opposite;facing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 102
    },
    {
        "Front": "慌ただしい",
        "Back": "busy;hurried;confused;flurried",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 103
    },
    {
        "Front": "慌てる",
        "Back": "to become confused (disconcerted&nbsp;&nbsp;disorganized)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 104
    },
    {
        "Front": "暗殺",
        "Back": "assassination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 105
    },
    {
        "Front": "暗算",
        "Back": "mental arithmetic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 106
    },
    {
        "Front": "暗示",
        "Back": "hint;suggestion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 107
    },
    {
        "Front": "案じる",
        "Back": "to be anxious;to ponder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 108
    },
    {
        "Front": "安静",
        "Back": "rest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 109
    },
    {
        "Front": "案の定",
        "Back": "sure enough;as usual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 110
    },
    {
        "Front": "余り",
        "Back": "not very (this form only used as adverb);not much;remainder;rest;remnant;surplus;balance;excess;rema",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 111
    },
    {
        "Front": "依",
        "Back": "depending on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 112
    },
    {
        "Front": "良い",
        "Back": "good",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 113
    },
    {
        "Front": "伊井",
        "Back": "that one;Italy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 114
    },
    {
        "Front": "否",
        "Back": "no;nay;yes;well",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 115
    },
    {
        "Front": "いい加減",
        "Back": "moderate;right;random;not thorough;vague;irresponsible;halfhearted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 116
    },
    {
        "Front": "言い訳",
        "Back": "excuse;explanation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 117
    },
    {
        "Front": "家出",
        "Back": "running away from home;leaving home",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 118
    },
    {
        "Front": "家主",
        "Back": "landlord",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 119
    },
    {
        "Front": "如何",
        "Back": "how;in what way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 120
    },
    {
        "Front": "生かす",
        "Back": "to revive;to resuscitate;to make use of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 121
    },
    {
        "Front": "雷",
        "Back": "thunder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 122
    },
    {
        "Front": "如何に",
        "Back": "how?;in what way?;how much?;however;whatever",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 123
    },
    {
        "Front": "如何にも",
        "Back": "indeed;really;phrase meaning agreement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 124
    },
    {
        "Front": "怒り",
        "Back": "anger;hatred",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 125
    },
    {
        "Front": "怒る",
        "Back": "to get angry;to be angry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 126
    },
    {
        "Front": "歪む",
        "Back": "to warp;to swerve;to deflect;to be crooked;to be distorted;to be bent;to incline;to slant;to be perv",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 127
    },
    {
        "Front": "粋",
        "Back": "chic;style;purity;essence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 128
    },
    {
        "Front": "域外",
        "Back": "outside the area",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 129
    },
    {
        "Front": "意気込む",
        "Back": "to be enthusiastic about",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 130
    },
    {
        "Front": "経緯",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;details;whole story;sequence of events;particulars;how it started;how things got this way; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;c",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 131
    },
    {
        "Front": "行き違い",
        "Back": "misunderstanding;estrangement;disagreement;crossing without meeting;going astray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 132
    },
    {
        "Front": "行き成り",
        "Back": "suddenly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 133
    },
    {
        "Front": "異議",
        "Back": "objection;dissent;protest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 134
    },
    {
        "Front": "いく",
        "Back": "to come;to orgasm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "軍",
        "Back": "war;battle;campaign;fight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 135
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦",
        "Back": "war;battle;campaign;fight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 136
    },
    {
        "Front": "育成",
        "Back": "rearing;training;nurture;cultivation;promotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 137
    },
    {
        "Front": "幾多",
        "Back": "many;numerous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 138
    },
    {
        "Front": "活ける",
        "Back": "to arrange (flowers)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 139
    },
    {
        "Front": "異見",
        "Back": "different opinion;objection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 140
    },
    {
        "Front": "意向",
        "Back": "intention;idea;inclination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 141
    },
    {
        "Front": "移行",
        "Back": "switching over to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 142
    },
    {
        "Front": "いざ",
        "Back": "now;come (now);well;crucial moment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "碑",
        "Back": "stone monument bearing an inscription",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 143
    },
    {
        "Front": "衣装",
        "Back": "clothing;costume;outfit;garment;dress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 144
    },
    {
        "Front": "意地",
        "Back": "disposition;spirit;willpower;obstinacy;backbone;appetite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 145
    },
    {
        "Front": "苛める",
        "Back": "to tease;to torment;to persecute;to chastise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 146
    },
    {
        "Front": "移住",
        "Back": "migration;immigration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 147
    },
    {
        "Front": "弄る",
        "Back": "to touch;to tamper with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 148
    },
    {
        "Front": "何れ",
        "Back": "where;which;who;anyway;anyhow;at any rate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 149
    },
    {
        "Front": "異性",
        "Back": "the opposite sex",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 150
    },
    {
        "Front": "遺跡",
        "Back": "historic ruins (remains&nbsp;&nbsp;relics)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 151
    },
    {
        "Front": "依然",
        "Back": "still;as yet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 152
    },
    {
        "Front": "依存",
        "Back": "dependence;dependent;reliance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 153
    },
    {
        "Front": "委託",
        "Back": "consign (goods (for sale) to a firm);entrust (person with something);commit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 154
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪戯",
        "Back": "tease;prank;trick;practical joke;mischief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 155
    },
    {
        "Front": "頂",
        "Back": "(top of) head;summit;spire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 156
    },
    {
        "Front": "戴きます",
        "Back": "expression of gratitude before meals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 157
    },
    {
        "Front": "至って",
        "Back": "very much;exceedingly;extremely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 158
    },
    {
        "Front": "痛む",
        "Back": "to hurt;to feel a pain;to be injured",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 159
    },
    {
        "Front": "痛める",
        "Back": "to hurt;to injure;to cause pain;to worry;to bother;to afflict;to be grieved over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 160
    },
    {
        "Front": "炒める",
        "Back": "to stir-fry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 161
    },
    {
        "Front": "労る",
        "Back": "to pity;to sympathize with;to console;to care for;to be kind to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 162
    },
    {
        "Front": "市",
        "Back": "market;fair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 163
    },
    {
        "Front": "位地",
        "Back": "place;situation;position;location",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 164
    },
    {
        "Front": "一々",
        "Back": "one by one;separately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 165
    },
    {
        "Front": "一概に",
        "Back": "unconditionally;as a rule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 166
    },
    {
        "Front": "一見",
        "Back": "unfamiliar;never before met",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 167
    },
    {
        "Front": "一言",
        "Back": "single word",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 168
    },
    {
        "Front": "一日",
        "Back": "(1) one day, (2) first of month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 169
    },
    {
        "Front": "一定",
        "Back": "fixed;settled;definite;uniform;regularized;defined;standardized;certain;prescribed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 170
    },
    {
        "Front": "著しい",
        "Back": "remarkable;considerable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 171
    },
    {
        "Front": "一同",
        "Back": "all present;all concerned;all of us",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 172
    },
    {
        "Front": "一人",
        "Back": "one person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 173
    },
    {
        "Front": "一部",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;one copy&nbsp;&nbsp;e.g. of a document; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;a part;partly;some",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 174
    },
    {
        "Front": "一部分",
        "Back": "a part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 175
    },
    {
        "Front": "一別",
        "Back": "parting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 176
    },
    {
        "Front": "一面",
        "Back": "one side;one phase;front page;the other hand;the whole surface",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 177
    },
    {
        "Front": "一目",
        "Back": "a glance;a look;a glimpse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 178
    },
    {
        "Front": "一様",
        "Back": "uniformity;evenness;similarity;equality;impartiality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 179
    },
    {
        "Front": "一律",
        "Back": "evenness;uniformity;monotony;equality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 180
    },
    {
        "Front": "一連",
        "Back": "a series;a chain;a ream (of paper)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 181
    },
    {
        "Front": "一括",
        "Back": "all together;batch;one lump;one bundle;summing up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 182
    },
    {
        "Front": "一気",
        "Back": "drink!(said repeatedly as a party cheer)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 183
    },
    {
        "Front": "一挙に",
        "Back": "at a stroke;with a single swoop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 184
    },
    {
        "Front": "一切",
        "Back": "all;everything;without exception;the whole;entirely;absolutely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 185
    },
    {
        "Front": "一心",
        "Back": "one mind;wholeheartedness;the whole heart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 186
    },
    {
        "Front": "いっそ",
        "Back": "rather;sooner;might as well",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "一帯",
        "Back": "a region;a zone;the whole place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 187
    },
    {
        "Front": "一敗",
        "Back": "one defeat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 188
    },
    {
        "Front": "一変",
        "Back": "complete change;about-face",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 189
    },
    {
        "Front": "何時",
        "Back": "when;how soon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 190
    },
    {
        "Front": "何時か",
        "Back": "sometime;someday;one day;some time or other;the other day;in due course;in time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 191
    },
    {
        "Front": "何時でも",
        "Back": "(at) any time;always;at all times;never (neg);whenever",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 192
    },
    {
        "Front": "何時の間にか",
        "Back": "before one knows;unnoticed;unawares",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 193
    },
    {
        "Front": "何時までも",
        "Back": "forever;for good;eternally;as long as one likes;indefinitely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 194
    },
    {
        "Front": "何時も",
        "Back": "always;usually;every time;never (with neg. verb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 195
    },
    {
        "Front": "意図",
        "Back": "intention;aim;design",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 196
    },
    {
        "Front": "営む",
        "Back": "to carry on (e.g. in ceremony);to run a business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 197
    },
    {
        "Front": "暇",
        "Back": "free time;leisure;leave;spare time;farewell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 198
    },
    {
        "Front": "異動",
        "Back": "a change",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 199
    },
    {
        "Front": "挑む",
        "Back": "to challenge;to contend for;to make love to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 200
    },
    {
        "Front": "稲光",
        "Back": "(flash of) lightning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 201
    },
    {
        "Front": "古",
        "Back": "antiquity;ancient times",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 202
    },
    {
        "Front": "祈り",
        "Back": "prayer;supplication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 203
    },
    {
        "Front": "鼾",
        "Back": "snoring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 204
    },
    {
        "Front": "今更",
        "Back": "now;at this late hour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 205
    },
    {
        "Front": "未だ",
        "Back": "as yet;hitherto;not yet (neg)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 206
    },
    {
        "Front": "移民",
        "Back": "emigration;immigration;emigrant;immigrant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 207
    },
    {
        "Front": "厭々",
        "Back": "unwillingly;grudgingly;shaking head in refusal (to children)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 208
    },
    {
        "Front": "卑しい",
        "Back": "greedy;vulgar;shabby;humble;base;mean;vile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 209
    },
    {
        "Front": "いやに",
        "Back": "awfully;terribly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "厭やらしい",
        "Back": "detestable;disagreeable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 210
    },
    {
        "Front": "愈々",
        "Back": "more and more;all the more;increasingly;at last;beyond doubt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 211
    },
    {
        "Front": "意欲",
        "Back": "will;desire;ambition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 212
    },
    {
        "Front": "苛々",
        "Back": "getting nervous;irritation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 213
    },
    {
        "Front": "入口",
        "Back": "entrance;gate;approach;mouth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 214
    },
    {
        "Front": "衣料",
        "Back": "clothing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 215
    },
    {
        "Front": "威力",
        "Back": "power;might;authority;influence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 216
    },
    {
        "Front": "入る",
        "Back": "to get in;to go in;to come in;to flow into;to set;to set in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 217
    },
    {
        "Front": "衣類",
        "Back": "clothes;clothing;garments",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 218
    },
    {
        "Front": "色々",
        "Back": "various",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 219
    },
    {
        "Front": "異論",
        "Back": "different opinion;objection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 220
    },
    {
        "Front": "所謂",
        "Back": "the so-called;so to speak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 221
    },
    {
        "Front": "印",
        "Back": "seal;stamp;mark;print",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 222
    },
    {
        "Front": "員",
        "Back": "member",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 223
    },
    {
        "Front": "印鑑",
        "Back": "stamp;seal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 224
    },
    {
        "Front": "陰気",
        "Back": "gloom;melancholy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 225
    },
    {
        "Front": "隠居",
        "Back": "retirement;retired person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 226
    },
    {
        "Front": "上下",
        "Back": "high and low;up and down;unloading and loading;praising and blaming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 227
    },
    {
        "Front": "浮かぶ",
        "Back": "to float;to rise to surface;to come to mind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 228
    },
    {
        "Front": "受かる",
        "Back": "to pass (examination)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 229
    },
    {
        "Front": "含嗽",
        "Back": "gargle;rinse mouth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 230
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け入れ",
        "Back": "receiving;acceptance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 231
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け入れる",
        "Back": "to accept;to receive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 232
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け継ぐ",
        "Back": "to inherit;to succeed;to take over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 233
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け付ける",
        "Back": "to be accepted;to receive (an application)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 234
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け止める",
        "Back": "to catch;to stop the blow;to react to;to take",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 235
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け取り",
        "Back": "receipt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 236
    },
    {
        "Front": "受身",
        "Back": "passive;passive voice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 237
    },
    {
        "Front": "動き",
        "Back": "movement;activity;trend;development;change",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 238
    },
    {
        "Front": "潮",
        "Back": "tide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 239
    },
    {
        "Front": "氏",
        "Back": "family name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 240
    },
    {
        "Front": "渦",
        "Back": "swirl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 241
    },
    {
        "Front": "埋まる",
        "Back": "to be buried;to be surrounded;to overflow;to be filled",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 242
    },
    {
        "Front": "嘘つき",
        "Back": "liar (sometimes said with not much seriousness);fibber",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 243
    },
    {
        "Front": "打ち合わせ",
        "Back": "business meeting;previous arrangement;appointment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 244
    },
    {
        "Front": "打ち合わせる",
        "Back": "to knock together;to arrange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 245
    },
    {
        "Front": "打ち切る",
        "Back": "to stop;to abort;to discontinue;to close",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 246
    },
    {
        "Front": "打ち消し",
        "Back": "negation;denial;negative",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 247
    },
    {
        "Front": "打ち込む",
        "Back": "to drive in (e.g. nail&nbsp;&nbsp;stake);to devote oneself to;to shoot into;to smash;to throw into;to cast int",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 248
    },
    {
        "Front": "団扇",
        "Back": "fan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 249
    },
    {
        "Front": "内訳",
        "Back": "the items;breakdown;classification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 250
    },
    {
        "Front": "訴え",
        "Back": "lawsuit;complaint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 251
    },
    {
        "Front": "鬱陶しい",
        "Back": "gloomy;depressing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 252
    },
    {
        "Front": "写し",
        "Back": "copy;duplicate;facsimile;transcript",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 253
    },
    {
        "Front": "空ろ",
        "Back": "blank;cavity;hollow;empty (space)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 254
    },
    {
        "Front": "器",
        "Back": "bowl;vessel;container",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 255
    },
    {
        "Front": "雨天",
        "Back": "rainy weather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 256
    },
    {
        "Front": "腕前",
        "Back": "ability;skill;facility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 257
    },
    {
        "Front": "饂飩",
        "Back": "noodles (Japanese)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 258
    },
    {
        "Front": "促す",
        "Back": "to urge;to press;to suggest;to demand;to stimulate;to quicken;to incite;to invite (attention to)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 259
    },
    {
        "Front": "唸る",
        "Back": "to groan;to moan;to roar;to howl;to growl;to hum;to buzz;to sough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 260
    },
    {
        "Front": "自惚れ",
        "Back": "pretension;conceit;hubris",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 261
    },
    {
        "Front": "甘い",
        "Back": "delicious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 262
    },
    {
        "Front": "生まれつき",
        "Back": "by nature;by birth;native",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 263
    },
    {
        "Front": "海路",
        "Back": "sea route",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 264
    },
    {
        "Front": "産む",
        "Back": "to give birth;to deliver;to produce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 265
    },
    {
        "Front": "埋め込む",
        "Back": "to bury",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 266
    },
    {
        "Front": "梅干",
        "Back": "dried plum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 267
    },
    {
        "Front": "末",
        "Back": "top end;tip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 268
    },
    {
        "Front": "裏返し",
        "Back": "inside out;upside down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 269
    },
    {
        "Front": "売り出し",
        "Back": "(bargain) sale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 270
    },
    {
        "Front": "売り出す",
        "Back": "to put on sale;to market;to become popular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 271
    },
    {
        "Front": "潤う",
        "Back": "to be moist;to be damp;to get wet;to profit by;to be watered;to receive benefits;to favor;to charm;t",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 272
    },
    {
        "Front": "五月蝿い",
        "Back": "noisy;loud;fussy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 273
    },
    {
        "Front": "売れ行き",
        "Back": "sales",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 274
    },
    {
        "Front": "浮気",
        "Back": "flighty;fickle;wanton;unfaithful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 275
    },
    {
        "Front": "上手",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;upper part;upper stream;left side (of a stage); 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;skillful (only in comparisons);dexterity (on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 276
    },
    {
        "Front": "上回る",
        "Back": "to exceed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 277
    },
    {
        "Front": "植わる",
        "Back": "to be planted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 278
    },
    {
        "Front": "運営",
        "Back": "management;administration;operation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 279
    },
    {
        "Front": "うんざり",
        "Back": "tedious;boring;being fed up with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "運送",
        "Back": "shipping;marine transportation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 280
    },
    {
        "Front": "運賃",
        "Back": "freight rates;shipping expenses;fare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 281
    },
    {
        "Front": "云々",
        "Back": "and so on;and so forth;comment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 282
    },
    {
        "Front": "運搬",
        "Back": "transport;carriage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 283
    },
    {
        "Front": "運命",
        "Back": "fate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 284
    },
    {
        "Front": "運輸",
        "Back": "transportation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 285
    },
    {
        "Front": "運用",
        "Back": "making use of;application;investment;practical use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 286
    },
    {
        "Front": "会",
        "Back": "understanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 287
    },
    {
        "Front": "重",
        "Back": "-fold;-ply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 288
    },
    {
        "Front": "えい",
        "Back": "ray (fish)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "映写",
        "Back": "projection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 289
    },
    {
        "Front": "英字",
        "Back": "English letter (character)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 290
    },
    {
        "Front": "衛生",
        "Back": "health;hygiene;sanitation;medical",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 291
    },
    {
        "Front": "映像",
        "Back": "reflection;image",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 292
    },
    {
        "Front": "英雄",
        "Back": "hero;great man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 293
    },
    {
        "Front": "液",
        "Back": "liquid;fluid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 294
    },
    {
        "Front": "役",
        "Back": "war;campaign;battle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 295
    },
    {
        "Front": "閲覧",
        "Back": "inspection;reading",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 296
    },
    {
        "Front": "獲物",
        "Back": "game;spoils;trophy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 297
    },
    {
        "Front": "襟",
        "Back": "neck;collar;lapel;neckband",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 298
    },
    {
        "Front": "縁",
        "Back": "chance;fate;destiny;relation;bonds;connection;karma",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 299
    },
    {
        "Front": "塩",
        "Back": "salt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 300
    },
    {
        "Front": "艶",
        "Back": "charming;fascinating;voluptuous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 301
    },
    {
        "Front": "園",
        "Back": "garden (esp. man-made)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 302
    },
    {
        "Front": "円滑",
        "Back": "harmony;smoothness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 303
    },
    {
        "Front": "縁側",
        "Back": "veranda;porch;balcony;open corridor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 304
    },
    {
        "Front": "沿岸",
        "Back": "coast;shore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 305
    },
    {
        "Front": "婉曲",
        "Back": "euphemistic;circumlocution;roundabout;indirect;insinuating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 306
    },
    {
        "Front": "演習",
        "Back": "practice;exercises;manoeuvers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 307
    },
    {
        "Front": "演出",
        "Back": "production (e.g. play);direction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 308
    },
    {
        "Front": "演じる",
        "Back": "to perform (a play);to play (a part);to act (a part);to commit (a blunder)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 309
    },
    {
        "Front": "演ずる",
        "Back": "to perform;to play",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 310
    },
    {
        "Front": "沿線",
        "Back": "along railway line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 311
    },
    {
        "Front": "縁談",
        "Back": "marriage proposal;engagement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 312
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠方",
        "Back": "long way;distant place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 313
    },
    {
        "Front": "円満",
        "Back": "perfection;harmony;peace;smoothness;completeness;satisfaction;integrity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 314
    },
    {
        "Front": "尾",
        "Back": "tail;ridge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 315
    },
    {
        "Front": "於",
        "Back": "at;in;on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 316
    },
    {
        "Front": "甥",
        "Back": "nephew",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 317
    },
    {
        "Front": "追い込む",
        "Back": "to herd;to corner;to drive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 318
    },
    {
        "Front": "美味しい",
        "Back": "delicious;tasty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 319
    },
    {
        "Front": "追い出す",
        "Back": "to expel;to drive out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 320
    },
    {
        "Front": "於いて",
        "Back": "at;in;on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 321
    },
    {
        "Front": "お出でになる",
        "Back": "to be",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 322
    },
    {
        "Front": "老いる",
        "Back": "to age;to grow old",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 323
    },
    {
        "Front": "負う",
        "Back": "to bear;to owe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 324
    },
    {
        "Front": "応急",
        "Back": "emergency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 325
    },
    {
        "Front": "黄金",
        "Back": "gold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 326
    },
    {
        "Front": "黄色",
        "Back": "yellow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 327
    },
    {
        "Front": "応募",
        "Back": "subscription;application",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 328
    },
    {
        "Front": "おおい",
        "Back": "hey!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "大方",
        "Back": "perhaps;almost all;majority",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 329
    },
    {
        "Front": "大柄",
        "Back": "large build;large pattern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 330
    },
    {
        "Front": "大げさ",
        "Back": "grandiose;exaggerated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 331
    },
    {
        "Front": "大事",
        "Back": "important;valuable;serious matter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 332
    },
    {
        "Front": "大ざっぱ",
        "Back": "rough (as in not precise);broad;sketchy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 333
    },
    {
        "Front": "大筋",
        "Back": "outline;summary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 334
    },
    {
        "Front": "大空",
        "Back": "heaven;firmament;the sky",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 335
    },
    {
        "Front": "大幅",
        "Back": "full width;large scale;drastic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 336
    },
    {
        "Front": "大水",
        "Back": "flood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 337
    },
    {
        "Front": "公",
        "Back": "official;public;formal;open;governmental",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 338
    },
    {
        "Front": "お蔭",
        "Back": "(your) backing;assistance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 339
    },
    {
        "Front": "お蔭様で",
        "Back": "Thanks to god;thanks to you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 340
    },
    {
        "Front": "可笑しい",
        "Back": "strange;funny;amusing;ridiculous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 341
    },
    {
        "Front": "犯す",
        "Back": "to commit;to perpetrate;to violate;to rape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 342
    },
    {
        "Front": "侵す",
        "Back": "to invade;to raid;to trespass;to violate;to intrude on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 343
    },
    {
        "Front": "お菜",
        "Back": "side dish;accompaniment for rice dishes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 344
    },
    {
        "Front": "臆病",
        "Back": "cowardice;timidity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 345
    },
    {
        "Front": "遅らす",
        "Back": "to retard;to delay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 346
    },
    {
        "Front": "遅れ",
        "Back": "delay;lag",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 347
    },
    {
        "Front": "起こす",
        "Back": "to raise;to cause;to wake someone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 348
    },
    {
        "Front": "行い",
        "Back": "deed;conduct;behavior;action;asceticism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 349
    },
    {
        "Front": "厳か",
        "Back": "austere;majestic;dignified;stately;awful;impressive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 350
    },
    {
        "Front": "傲る",
        "Back": "to be proud",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 351
    },
    {
        "Front": "長",
        "Back": "chief;head",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 352
    },
    {
        "Front": "押さえる",
        "Back": "to stop;to restrain;to seize;to repress;to suppress;to press down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 353
    },
    {
        "Front": "お先に",
        "Back": "before;ahead;previously",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 354
    },
    {
        "Front": "収まる",
        "Back": "to be obtained;to end;to settle into;to fit into;to be settled;to be paid;to be delivered",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 355
    },
    {
        "Front": "納まる",
        "Back": "to be obtained;to end;to settle into;to fit into;to be settled;to be paid;to be delivered",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 356
    },
    {
        "Front": "治まる",
        "Back": "to be at peace;to clamp down;to lessen (storm&nbsp;&nbsp;terror&nbsp;&nbsp;anger)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 357
    },
    {
        "Front": "お産",
        "Back": "(giving) birth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 358
    },
    {
        "Front": "教え",
        "Back": "teachings;precept;lesson;doctrine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 359
    },
    {
        "Front": "押し込む",
        "Back": "to push into;to crowd into",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 361
    },
    {
        "Front": "惜しむ",
        "Back": "to be frugal;to value;to regret",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 360
    },
    {
        "Front": "お喋り",
        "Back": "chattering;talk;idle talk;chat;chitchat;gossip;chatty;talkative;chatterbox;blabbermouth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 362
    },
    {
        "Front": "お洒落",
        "Back": "smartly dressed;someone smartly dressed;fashion-conscious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 363
    },
    {
        "Front": "押し寄せる",
        "Back": "to push aside;to advance on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 364
    },
    {
        "Front": "お祖父さん",
        "Back": "grandfather;male senior-citizen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 365
    },
    {
        "Front": "お邪魔します",
        "Back": "Excuse me for disturbing (interrupting) you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 366
    },
    {
        "Front": "雄",
        "Back": "male (animal)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 367
    },
    {
        "Front": "お世辞",
        "Back": "flattery;compliment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 368
    },
    {
        "Front": "襲う",
        "Back": "to attack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 369
    },
    {
        "Front": "遅くとも",
        "Back": "at the latest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 370
    },
    {
        "Front": "恐らく",
        "Back": "perhaps",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 371
    },
    {
        "Front": "恐れ",
        "Back": "fear;horror",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 372
    },
    {
        "Front": "恐れ入る",
        "Back": "to be filled with awe;to feel small;to be amazed;to be surprised;to be disconcerted;to be sorry;to b",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 373
    },
    {
        "Front": "お大事に",
        "Back": "Take care of yourself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 374
    },
    {
        "Front": "煽てる",
        "Back": "to stir up;to instigate;to flatter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 375
    },
    {
        "Front": "落ち込む",
        "Back": "to fall into;to feel down (sad)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 376
    },
    {
        "Front": "落ち着き",
        "Back": "calm;composure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 377
    },
    {
        "Front": "落ち葉",
        "Back": "fallen leaves;leaf litter;defoliation;shedding leaves",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 378
    },
    {
        "Front": "落ちる",
        "Back": "to fail (e.g. exam);to fall down;to drop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 379
    },
    {
        "Front": "おっかない",
        "Back": "frightening;huge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "仰っしゃる",
        "Back": "to say;to speak;to tell;to talk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 380
    },
    {
        "Front": "乙",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;strange;quaint;stylish;chic;spicy;queer;witty;tasty;romantic; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;2nd in rank;second sign of the",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 381
    },
    {
        "Front": "お使い",
        "Back": "errand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 382
    },
    {
        "Front": "お手上げ",
        "Back": "all over;given in;given up hope;bring to knees",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 383
    },
    {
        "Front": "御手洗い",
        "Back": "toilet;restroom;lavatory;bathroom (US)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 384
    },
    {
        "Front": "弟",
        "Back": "younger brother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 385
    },
    {
        "Front": "落とす",
        "Back": "to drop;to lose;to let fall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 386
    },
    {
        "Front": "訪れる",
        "Back": "to visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 387
    },
    {
        "Front": "大人しい",
        "Back": "obedient;docile;quiet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 388
    },
    {
        "Front": "少女",
        "Back": "daughter;young lady;virgin;maiden;little girl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 389
    },
    {
        "Front": "お供",
        "Back": "attendant;companion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 390
    },
    {
        "Front": "衰える",
        "Back": "to become weak;to decline;to wear;to abate;to decay;to wither;to waste away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 391
    },
    {
        "Front": "おどおど",
        "Back": "coweringly;hesitantly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "脅かす",
        "Back": "to threaten;to coerce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 392
    },
    {
        "Front": "脅す",
        "Back": "to threaten;to menace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 393
    },
    {
        "Front": "驚き",
        "Back": "surprise;astonishment;wonder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 394
    },
    {
        "Front": "同い年",
        "Back": "of the same age",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 395
    },
    {
        "Front": "女子",
        "Back": "woman;girl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 396
    },
    {
        "Front": "お願いします",
        "Back": "please",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 397
    },
    {
        "Front": "各",
        "Back": "each;every;either;respectively;severally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 398
    },
    {
        "Front": "自ずから",
        "Back": "naturally;as a matter of course",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 399
    },
    {
        "Front": "お早う",
        "Back": "Good morning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 400
    },
    {
        "Front": "お祖母さん",
        "Back": "grandmother;female senior-citizen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 401
    },
    {
        "Front": "怯える",
        "Back": "to become frightened;to have a nightmare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 402
    },
    {
        "Front": "夥しい",
        "Back": "abundantly;innumerably",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 403
    },
    {
        "Front": "帯びる",
        "Back": "to wear;to carry;to be entrusted;to have;to take on;to have a trace of;to be tinged with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 404
    },
    {
        "Front": "覚え",
        "Back": "memory;sense;experience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 405
    },
    {
        "Front": "御負け",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;a discount;a prize; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;something additional;bonus;an extra; 3.&nbsp;&nbsp;an exaggeration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 406
    },
    {
        "Front": "お巡りさん",
        "Back": "policeman (friendly term)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 407
    },
    {
        "Front": "お宮",
        "Back": "Shinto shrine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 408
    },
    {
        "Front": "お襁褓",
        "Back": "diaper;nappy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 409
    },
    {
        "Front": "お目出度う",
        "Back": "(ateji) (int) (uk) Congratulations!;an auspicious occasion!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 410
    },
    {
        "Front": "面",
        "Back": "face",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 411
    },
    {
        "Front": "思い付き",
        "Back": "plan;idea;suggestion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 412
    },
    {
        "Front": "面白い",
        "Back": "interesting;amusing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 413
    },
    {
        "Front": "玩具",
        "Back": "toy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 414
    },
    {
        "Front": "重なる",
        "Back": "main;principal;important",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 415
    },
    {
        "Front": "趣",
        "Back": "meaning;tenor;gist;effect;appearance;taste;grace;charm;refinement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 416
    },
    {
        "Front": "赴く",
        "Back": "to go;to proceed;to repair to;to become",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 417
    },
    {
        "Front": "重役",
        "Back": "heavy responsibilities;director",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 418
    },
    {
        "Front": "重んじる",
        "Back": "to respect;to honor;to esteem;to prize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 419
    },
    {
        "Front": "重んずる",
        "Back": "to honor;to respect;to esteem;to prize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 420
    },
    {
        "Front": "お休み",
        "Back": "holiday;absence;rest;Good night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 421
    },
    {
        "Front": "お八",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;(uk) between meal snack;afternoon refreshment;afternoon tea; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;mid-day snack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 422
    },
    {
        "Front": "凡そ",
        "Back": "about;roughly;as a rule;approximately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 423
    },
    {
        "Front": "及び",
        "Back": "and;as well as",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 424
    },
    {
        "Front": "及ぶ",
        "Back": "to reach;to come up to;to amount to;to befall;to happen to;to extend;to match;to equal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 425
    },
    {
        "Front": "織",
        "Back": "weave;weaving;woven item",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 426
    },
    {
        "Front": "檻",
        "Back": "cage;pen;jail cell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 427
    },
    {
        "Front": "折り返す",
        "Back": "to turn up;to fold back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 428
    },
    {
        "Front": "織物",
        "Back": "textile;fabric",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 429
    },
    {
        "Front": "織る",
        "Back": "to weave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 430
    },
    {
        "Front": "俺",
        "Back": "I (ego) (boastful first-person pronoun)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 431
    },
    {
        "Front": "愚か",
        "Back": "foolish;stupid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 432
    },
    {
        "Front": "疎か",
        "Back": "neglect;negligence;carelessness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 433
    },
    {
        "Front": "終わる",
        "Back": "to finish;to close",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 434
    },
    {
        "Front": "音色",
        "Back": "tone color;tone quality;timbre;synthesizer patch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 435
    },
    {
        "Front": "温和",
        "Back": "gentle;mild;moderate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 436
    },
    {
        "Front": "仮",
        "Back": "tentative;provisional",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 437
    },
    {
        "Front": "科",
        "Back": "department;section",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 438
    },
    {
        "Front": "個",
        "Back": "article counter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 439
    },
    {
        "Front": "下位",
        "Back": "low rank;subordinate;lower order (e.g. byte)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 440
    },
    {
        "Front": "階",
        "Back": "-floor (counter);stories",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 441
    },
    {
        "Front": "改悪",
        "Back": "deterioration;changing for the worse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 442
    },
    {
        "Front": "海運",
        "Back": "maritime;marine transportation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 443
    },
    {
        "Front": "改革",
        "Back": "reform;reformation;innovation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 444
    },
    {
        "Front": "貝殻",
        "Back": "shell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 445
    },
    {
        "Front": "階級",
        "Back": "class;rank;grade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 446
    },
    {
        "Front": "海峡",
        "Back": "channel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 447
    },
    {
        "Front": "会見",
        "Back": "interview;audience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 448
    },
    {
        "Front": "介護",
        "Back": "nursing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 449
    },
    {
        "Front": "開催",
        "Back": "holding a meeting;open an exhibition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 450
    },
    {
        "Front": "回収",
        "Back": "collection;recovery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 451
    },
    {
        "Front": "改修",
        "Back": "repair;improvement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 452
    },
    {
        "Front": "怪獣",
        "Back": "monster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 453
    },
    {
        "Front": "解除",
        "Back": "cancellation;rescinding;release;calling off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 454
    },
    {
        "Front": "回送",
        "Back": "forwarding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 455
    },
    {
        "Front": "階層",
        "Back": "class;level;stratum;hierarchy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 456
    },
    {
        "Front": "開拓",
        "Back": "reclamation (of wasteland);cultivation;pioneer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 457
    },
    {
        "Front": "会談",
        "Back": "conversation;conference;discussion;interview",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 458
    },
    {
        "Front": "改定",
        "Back": "reform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 459
    },
    {
        "Front": "改訂",
        "Back": "revision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 460
    },
    {
        "Front": "街道",
        "Back": "highway",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 461
    },
    {
        "Front": "介入",
        "Back": "intervention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 462
    },
    {
        "Front": "開発",
        "Back": "development;exploitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 463
    },
    {
        "Front": "海抜",
        "Back": "height above sea level",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 464
    },
    {
        "Front": "介抱",
        "Back": "nursing;looking after",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 465
    },
    {
        "Front": "解剖",
        "Back": "dissection;autopsy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 466
    },
    {
        "Front": "回覧",
        "Back": "circulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 467
    },
    {
        "Front": "海流",
        "Back": "ocean current",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 468
    },
    {
        "Front": "改良",
        "Back": "improvement;reform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 469
    },
    {
        "Front": "回路",
        "Back": "circuit (electric)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 470
    },
    {
        "Front": "顧みる",
        "Back": "to look back;to turn around;to review",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 471
    },
    {
        "Front": "省みる",
        "Back": "to reflect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 472
    },
    {
        "Front": "返る",
        "Back": "to return;to come back;to go back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 473
    },
    {
        "Front": "顔付き",
        "Back": "(outward) looks;features;face;countenance;expression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 474
    },
    {
        "Front": "掲げる",
        "Back": "to publish;to print;to carry (an article);to put up;to hang out;to hoist;to fly (a sail);to float (a",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 475
    },
    {
        "Front": "踵",
        "Back": "(shoe) heel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 476
    },
    {
        "Front": "係り",
        "Back": "official;duty;person in charge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 477
    },
    {
        "Front": "課外",
        "Back": "extracurricular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 478
    },
    {
        "Front": "書き取り",
        "Back": "dictation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 479
    },
    {
        "Front": "書き取る",
        "Back": "to write down;to take dictation;to take notes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 480
    },
    {
        "Front": "掻き回す",
        "Back": "to stir up;to churn;to ransack;to disturb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 481
    },
    {
        "Front": "欠く",
        "Back": "to lack;to break;to crack;to chip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 482
    },
    {
        "Front": "角",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;angle; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;bishop (shogi)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 483
    },
    {
        "Front": "核",
        "Back": "nucleus;kernel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 484
    },
    {
        "Front": "格",
        "Back": "status;character;case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 485
    },
    {
        "Front": "佳句",
        "Back": "beautiful passage of literature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 486
    },
    {
        "Front": "画",
        "Back": "stroke",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 487
    },
    {
        "Front": "格差",
        "Back": "qualitative difference;disparity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 488
    },
    {
        "Front": "拡散",
        "Back": "scattering;diffusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 489
    },
    {
        "Front": "各種",
        "Back": "every kind;all sorts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 490
    },
    {
        "Front": "隔週",
        "Back": "every other week",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 491
    },
    {
        "Front": "確信",
        "Back": "conviction;confidence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 492
    },
    {
        "Front": "革新",
        "Back": "reform;innovation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 493
    },
    {
        "Front": "確定",
        "Back": "definition (math);decision;settlement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 494
    },
    {
        "Front": "獲得",
        "Back": "acquisition;possession",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 495
    },
    {
        "Front": "確保",
        "Back": "guarantee;ensure;maintain;insure;secure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 496
    },
    {
        "Front": "革命",
        "Back": "revolution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 497
    },
    {
        "Front": "確立",
        "Back": "establishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 498
    },
    {
        "Front": "賭け",
        "Back": "betting;gambling;a gamble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 499
    },
    {
        "Front": "掛け",
        "Back": "credit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 500
    },
    {
        "Front": "駆け足",
        "Back": "running fast;double time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 501
    },
    {
        "Front": "家計",
        "Back": "household economy;family finances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 502
    },
    {
        "Front": "駆けっこ",
        "Back": "(foot) race",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 503
    },
    {
        "Front": "駆ける",
        "Back": "to run (race&nbsp;&nbsp;esp. horse);to gallop;to canter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 504
    },
    {
        "Front": "賭ける",
        "Back": "to wager;to bet;to risk;to stake;to gamble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 505
    },
    {
        "Front": "ヶ月",
        "Back": "#NAME?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 506
    },
    {
        "Front": "加工",
        "Back": "manufacturing;processing;treatment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 507
    },
    {
        "Front": "化合",
        "Back": "chemical combination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 508
    },
    {
        "Front": "嵩張る",
        "Back": "to be bulky;to be unwieldy;to grow voluminous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 509
    },
    {
        "Front": "嵩む",
        "Back": "to pile up;to increase",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 510
    },
    {
        "Front": "風車",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;windmill; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;pinwheel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 511
    },
    {
        "Front": "畏まりました",
        "Back": "certainly!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 512
    },
    {
        "Front": "華奢",
        "Back": "luxury;pomp;delicate;slender;gorgeous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 513
    },
    {
        "Front": "箇所",
        "Back": "passage;place;point;part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 514
    },
    {
        "Front": "火傷",
        "Back": "burn;scald",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 515
    },
    {
        "Front": "箇条書き",
        "Back": "itemized form;itemization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 516
    },
    {
        "Front": "噛る",
        "Back": "to chew;to bite (at);to gnaw;to nibble;to munch;to crunch;to have a smattering of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 517
    },
    {
        "Front": "微か",
        "Back": "faint;dim;weak;indistinct;hazy;poor;wretched",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 518
    },
    {
        "Front": "霞む",
        "Back": "to grow hazy;to be misty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 519
    },
    {
        "Front": "化する",
        "Back": "to change into;to convert into;to transform;to be reduced;to influence;to improve (someone)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 520
    },
    {
        "Front": "擦る",
        "Back": "to touch lightly;to take a percentage (from)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 521
    },
    {
        "Front": "火星",
        "Back": "Mars (planet)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 522
    },
    {
        "Front": "化石",
        "Back": "fossil;petrifaction;fossilization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 523
    },
    {
        "Front": "河川",
        "Back": "rivers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 524
    },
    {
        "Front": "化繊",
        "Back": "synthetic fibres",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 525
    },
    {
        "Front": "過疎",
        "Back": "depopulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 526
    },
    {
        "Front": "過多",
        "Back": "excess;superabundance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 527
    },
    {
        "Front": "難い",
        "Back": "difficult;hard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 528
    },
    {
        "Front": "片思い",
        "Back": "unrequited love",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 529
    },
    {
        "Front": "敵",
        "Back": "enemy;rival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 530
    },
    {
        "Front": "気質",
        "Back": "spirit;character;trait;temperament;disposition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 531
    },
    {
        "Front": "片言",
        "Back": "a smattering;talk like a baby;speak haltingly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 532
    },
    {
        "Front": "片付け",
        "Back": "tidying up;finishing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 533
    },
    {
        "Front": "傾く",
        "Back": "to incline toward;to slant;to lurch;to heel over;to be disposed to;to trend toward;to be prone to;to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 534
    },
    {
        "Front": "傾ける",
        "Back": "to incline;to list;to bend;to lean;to tip;to tilt;to slant;to concentrate on;to ruin (a country);to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 535
    },
    {
        "Front": "固める",
        "Back": "to harden;to freeze;to fortify",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 536
    },
    {
        "Front": "偏る",
        "Back": "to be one-sided;to incline;to be partial;to be prejudiced;to lean;to be biased",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 537
    },
    {
        "Front": "傍ら",
        "Back": "beside(s);while;nearby",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 538
    },
    {
        "Front": "課題",
        "Back": "subject;theme;task",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 539
    },
    {
        "Front": "花壇",
        "Back": "flower bed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 540
    },
    {
        "Front": "家畜",
        "Back": "domestic animals;livestock;cattle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 541
    },
    {
        "Front": "画期",
        "Back": "epoch-making",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 542
    },
    {
        "Front": "活発",
        "Back": "vigor;active",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 543
    },
    {
        "Front": "且つ",
        "Back": "yet;and",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 544
    },
    {
        "Front": "割",
        "Back": "divide;cut;halve;separate;split;rip;break;crack;smash;dilute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 545
    },
    {
        "Front": "嘗て",
        "Back": "once;ever",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 546
    },
    {
        "Front": "日付",
        "Back": "date;dating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 547
    },
    {
        "Front": "門",
        "Back": "gate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 548
    },
    {
        "Front": "叶う",
        "Back": "to come true (wish)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 549
    },
    {
        "Front": "叶える",
        "Back": "to grant (request&nbsp;&nbsp;wish)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 550
    },
    {
        "Front": "金槌",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;(iron) hammer; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;punishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 551
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉄棒",
        "Back": "iron rod;crowbar;horizontal bar (gymnastics)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 552
    },
    {
        "Front": "可成",
        "Back": "considerably;fairly;quite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 553
    },
    {
        "Front": "加入",
        "Back": "becoming a member;joining;entry;admission;subscription;affiliation;adherence;signing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 554
    },
    {
        "Front": "金庫",
        "Back": "safe;vault;treasury;provider of funds",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 555
    },
    {
        "Front": "予言",
        "Back": "prediction;promise;prognostication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 556
    },
    {
        "Front": "兼ねて",
        "Back": "simultaneously",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 557
    },
    {
        "Front": "下番",
        "Back": "going off duty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 558
    },
    {
        "Front": "下品",
        "Back": "inferior article",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 559
    },
    {
        "Front": "華美",
        "Back": "pomp;splendor;gaudiness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 560
    },
    {
        "Front": "花粉",
        "Back": "pollen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 561
    },
    {
        "Front": "株式",
        "Back": "stock (company)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 562
    },
    {
        "Front": "気触れる",
        "Back": "to react to;to be influenced by;to go overboard for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 563
    },
    {
        "Front": "貨幣",
        "Back": "money;currency;coinage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 564
    },
    {
        "Front": "構え",
        "Back": "posture;pose;style",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 565
    },
    {
        "Front": "構える",
        "Back": "to set up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 566
    },
    {
        "Front": "加味",
        "Back": "seasoning;flavoring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 567
    },
    {
        "Front": "噛み切る",
        "Back": "to bite off;to gnaw through",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 568
    },
    {
        "Front": "過密",
        "Back": "crowded",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 569
    },
    {
        "Front": "瓶",
        "Back": "earthenware pot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 570
    },
    {
        "Front": "かも知れない",
        "Back": "may;might;perhaps;may be;possibly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 571
    },
    {
        "Front": "粥",
        "Back": "(rice) gruel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 572
    },
    {
        "Front": "痒い",
        "Back": "itchy;itching",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 573
    },
    {
        "Front": "揶揄う",
        "Back": "to ridicule;to tease;to banter with;to make fun of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 574
    },
    {
        "Front": "身体",
        "Back": "the body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 575
    },
    {
        "Front": "体付き",
        "Back": "body build;figure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 576
    },
    {
        "Front": "絡む",
        "Back": "to entangle;to entwine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 577
    },
    {
        "Front": "借り",
        "Back": "borrowing;debt;loan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 578
    },
    {
        "Front": "下吏",
        "Back": "lower official",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 579
    },
    {
        "Front": "加留多",
        "Back": "(pt:) (n) playing cards (pt: carta)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 580
    },
    {
        "Front": "涸れる",
        "Back": "to dry up;to run out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 581
    },
    {
        "Front": "過労",
        "Back": "overwork;strain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 582
    },
    {
        "Front": "辛うじて",
        "Back": "barely;narrowly;just manage to do st",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 583
    },
    {
        "Front": "側",
        "Back": "side;row;surroundings;part;(watch) case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 584
    },
    {
        "Front": "可愛い",
        "Back": "pretty;cute;lovely;charming;dear;darling;pet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 585
    },
    {
        "Front": "可愛がる",
        "Back": "to love;to be affectionate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 586
    },
    {
        "Front": "可哀想",
        "Back": "poor;pitiable;pathetic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 587
    },
    {
        "Front": "可愛らしい",
        "Back": "lovely;sweet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 588
    },
    {
        "Front": "交わす",
        "Back": "to exchange (messages);to dodge;to parry;to avoid;to turn aside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 589
    },
    {
        "Front": "代わる",
        "Back": "to take the place of;to relieve;to be substituted for;to be exchanged;to change places with;to take",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 590
    },
    {
        "Front": "代わる代わる",
        "Back": "alternately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 591
    },
    {
        "Front": "乾",
        "Back": "heaven;emperor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 592
    },
    {
        "Front": "管",
        "Back": "pipe;tube",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 593
    },
    {
        "Front": "幹",
        "Back": "(tree) trunk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 594
    },
    {
        "Front": "冠",
        "Back": "crown;diadem;first;best;peerless;cap;naming;designating;initiating on coming of age;top character ra",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 595
    },
    {
        "Front": "観",
        "Back": "look;appearance;spectacle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 596
    },
    {
        "Front": "館",
        "Back": "house;hall;building;hotel;inn;guesthouse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 597
    },
    {
        "Front": "簡易",
        "Back": "simplicity;easiness;quasi-",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 598
    },
    {
        "Front": "感慨",
        "Back": "strong feelings;deep emotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 599
    },
    {
        "Front": "寒気",
        "Back": "cold;frost;chill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 600
    },
    {
        "Front": "簡潔",
        "Back": "brevity;conciseness;simplicity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 601
    },
    {
        "Front": "還元",
        "Back": "resolution;reduction;return to origins",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 602
    },
    {
        "Front": "刊行",
        "Back": "publication;issue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 603
    },
    {
        "Front": "慣行",
        "Back": "customary practice;habit;traditional event",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 604
    },
    {
        "Front": "勧告",
        "Back": "advice;counsel;remonstrance;recommendation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 605
    },
    {
        "Front": "看護",
        "Back": "nursing;(army) nurse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 606
    },
    {
        "Front": "漢語",
        "Back": "Chinese word;Sino-Japanese word",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 607
    },
    {
        "Front": "換算",
        "Back": "conversion;change;exchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 608
    },
    {
        "Front": "監視",
        "Back": "observation;guarding;inspection;surveillance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 609
    },
    {
        "Front": "慣習",
        "Back": "usual (historical) custom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 610
    },
    {
        "Front": "観衆",
        "Back": "spectators;onlookers;members of the audience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 611
    },
    {
        "Front": "干渉",
        "Back": "interference;intervention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 612
    },
    {
        "Front": "感触",
        "Back": "sense of touch;feeling;sensation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 613
    },
    {
        "Front": "肝心",
        "Back": "essential;fundamental;crucial;vital;main",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 614
    },
    {
        "Front": "歓声",
        "Back": "cheer;shout of joy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 615
    },
    {
        "Front": "感染",
        "Back": "infection;contagion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 616
    },
    {
        "Front": "幹線",
        "Back": "main line;trunk line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 617
    },
    {
        "Front": "関税",
        "Back": "customs;duty;tariff",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 618
    },
    {
        "Front": "簡素",
        "Back": "simplicity;plain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 619
    },
    {
        "Front": "観点",
        "Back": "point of view",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 620
    },
    {
        "Front": "感度",
        "Back": "sensitivity;severity (quake)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 621
    },
    {
        "Front": "幹部",
        "Back": "management;(executive) staff;leaders",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 622
    },
    {
        "Front": "勘弁",
        "Back": "pardon;forgiveness;forbearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 623
    },
    {
        "Front": "完璧",
        "Back": "perfection;completeness;flawless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 624
    },
    {
        "Front": "感無量",
        "Back": "deep feeling;inexpressible feeling;filled with emotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 625
    },
    {
        "Front": "勧誘",
        "Back": "invitation;solicitation;canvassing;inducement;persuasion;encouragement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 626
    },
    {
        "Front": "関与",
        "Back": "participation;taking part in;participating in;being concerned in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 627
    },
    {
        "Front": "慣用",
        "Back": "common;customary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 628
    },
    {
        "Front": "寛容",
        "Back": "forbearance;tolerance;generosity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 629
    },
    {
        "Front": "観覧",
        "Back": "viewing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 630
    },
    {
        "Front": "官僚",
        "Back": "bureaucrat;bureaucracy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 631
    },
    {
        "Front": "慣例",
        "Back": "custom;precedent;of convention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 632
    },
    {
        "Front": "還暦",
        "Back": "60th birthday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 633
    },
    {
        "Front": "貫禄",
        "Back": "presence;dignity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 634
    },
    {
        "Front": "緩和",
        "Back": "relief;mitigation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 635
    },
    {
        "Front": "蓋",
        "Back": "cover;lid;cap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 636
    },
    {
        "Front": "街",
        "Back": "~street;~quarters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 637
    },
    {
        "Front": "外貨",
        "Back": "imported goods;foreign money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 638
    },
    {
        "Front": "外観",
        "Back": "appearance;exterior;facade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 639
    },
    {
        "Front": "外相",
        "Back": "Foreign Minister",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 640
    },
    {
        "Front": "害する",
        "Back": "to injure;to damage;to harm;to kill;to hinder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 641
    },
    {
        "Front": "概説",
        "Back": "general statement;outline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 642
    },
    {
        "Front": "該当",
        "Back": "corresponding;answering to;coming under",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 643
    },
    {
        "Front": "街頭",
        "Back": "in the street",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 644
    },
    {
        "Front": "概念",
        "Back": "general idea;concept;notion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 645
    },
    {
        "Front": "外来",
        "Back": "imported;outpatient clinic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 646
    },
    {
        "Front": "概略",
        "Back": "outline;summary;gist;in brief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 647
    },
    {
        "Front": "学芸",
        "Back": "arts and sciences;liberal arts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 648
    },
    {
        "Front": "学士",
        "Back": "university graduate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 649
    },
    {
        "Front": "学説",
        "Back": "theory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 650
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽譜",
        "Back": "score (music)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 651
    },
    {
        "Front": "学歴",
        "Back": "academic background",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 652
    },
    {
        "Front": "崖",
        "Back": "cliff",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 653
    },
    {
        "Front": "雅致",
        "Back": "artistry;good taste;elegance;grace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 654
    },
    {
        "Front": "がっくり",
        "Back": "heartbroken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "合唱",
        "Back": "chorus;singing in a chorus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 655
    },
    {
        "Front": "がっしり",
        "Back": "firmly;solidly;tough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "合致",
        "Back": "agreement;concurrence;conforming to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 656
    },
    {
        "Front": "がっちり",
        "Back": "solidly built;tightly;shrewd;calculating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "月日",
        "Back": "(the) date",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 657
    },
    {
        "Front": "合併",
        "Back": "combination;union;amalgamation;consolidation;merger;coalition;fusion;annexation;affiliation;incorpor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 658
    },
    {
        "Front": "がる",
        "Back": "feel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "癌",
        "Back": "cancer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 659
    },
    {
        "Front": "眼科",
        "Back": "ophthalmology",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 660
    },
    {
        "Front": "眼球",
        "Back": "eyeball",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 661
    },
    {
        "Front": "眼鏡",
        "Back": "spectacles;glasses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 662
    },
    {
        "Front": "頑固",
        "Back": "stubbornness;obstinacy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 663
    },
    {
        "Front": "願書",
        "Back": "written application or petition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 664
    },
    {
        "Front": "頑丈",
        "Back": "solid;firm;stout;burly;strong;sturdy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 665
    },
    {
        "Front": "岩石",
        "Back": "rock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 666
    },
    {
        "Front": "元年",
        "Back": "first year (of a specific reign)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 667
    },
    {
        "Front": "贋物",
        "Back": "imitation;counterfeit;forgery;sham",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 668
    },
    {
        "Front": "元来",
        "Back": "originally;primarily;essentially;logically;naturally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 669
    },
    {
        "Front": "生",
        "Back": "pure;undiluted;raw;crude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 670
    },
    {
        "Front": "期",
        "Back": "period;time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 671
    },
    {
        "Front": "企画",
        "Back": "planning;project",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 672
    },
    {
        "Front": "規格",
        "Back": "standard;norm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 673
    },
    {
        "Front": "着飾る",
        "Back": "to dress up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 674
    },
    {
        "Front": "器官",
        "Back": "organ (of body);instrument",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 675
    },
    {
        "Front": "季刊",
        "Back": "quarterly (e.g. magazine)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 676
    },
    {
        "Front": "危害",
        "Back": "injury;harm;danger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 677
    },
    {
        "Front": "気兼ね",
        "Back": "hesitance;diffidence;feeling constraint;fear of troubling someone;having scruples about doing someth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 678
    },
    {
        "Front": "気軽",
        "Back": "cheerful;buoyant;lighthearted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 679
    },
    {
        "Front": "危機",
        "Back": "crisis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 680
    },
    {
        "Front": "聞き取り",
        "Back": "listening comprehension",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 681
    },
    {
        "Front": "効き目",
        "Back": "effect;virtue;efficacy;impression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 682
    },
    {
        "Front": "帰京",
        "Back": "returning to Tokyo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 683
    },
    {
        "Front": "基金",
        "Back": "fund;foundation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 684
    },
    {
        "Front": "棄権",
        "Back": "abstain from voting;renunciation of a right",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 685
    },
    {
        "Front": "喜劇",
        "Back": "comedy;funny show",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 686
    },
    {
        "Front": "起源",
        "Back": "origin;beginning;rise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 687
    },
    {
        "Front": "機構",
        "Back": "mechanism;organization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 688
    },
    {
        "Front": "既婚",
        "Back": "marriage;married",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 689
    },
    {
        "Front": "記載",
        "Back": "mention;entry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 690
    },
    {
        "Front": "気障",
        "Back": "affectation;conceit;snobbery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 691
    },
    {
        "Front": "兆し",
        "Back": "signs;omen;symptoms",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 692
    },
    {
        "Front": "兆",
        "Back": "signs;omen;symptoms",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 693
    },
    {
        "Front": "軋む",
        "Back": "to jar;to creak;to grate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 694
    },
    {
        "Front": "気象",
        "Back": "weather;climate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 695
    },
    {
        "Front": "期日",
        "Back": "fixed date;settlement date",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 696
    },
    {
        "Front": "記述",
        "Back": "describing;descriptor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 697
    },
    {
        "Front": "奇数",
        "Back": "odd number",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 698
    },
    {
        "Front": "築く",
        "Back": "to build;to pile up;to amass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 699
    },
    {
        "Front": "傷付く",
        "Back": "to be hurt;to be wounded;to get injured",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 700
    },
    {
        "Front": "規制",
        "Back": "regulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 701
    },
    {
        "Front": "汽船",
        "Back": "steamship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 702
    },
    {
        "Front": "寄贈",
        "Back": "donation;presentation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 703
    },
    {
        "Front": "貴族",
        "Back": "noble;aristocrat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 704
    },
    {
        "Front": "鍛える",
        "Back": "to forge;to drill;to temper;to train;to discipline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 705
    },
    {
        "Front": "来る",
        "Back": "to come;to arrive;to be due to;to be next;to be forthcoming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 706
    },
    {
        "Front": "気立て",
        "Back": "disposition;nature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 707
    },
    {
        "Front": "きちっと",
        "Back": "exactly;perfectly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "几帳面",
        "Back": "methodical;punctual;steady",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 708
    },
    {
        "Front": "切っ掛け",
        "Back": "chance;start;cue;excuse;motive;impetus;occasion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 709
    },
    {
        "Front": "きっかり",
        "Back": "exactly;precisely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "喫茶",
        "Back": "tea drinking;tea house",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 710
    },
    {
        "Front": "きっちり",
        "Back": "precisely;tightly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "屹度",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;(uk) surely;undoubtedly;certainly;without fail; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;sternly;severely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 711
    },
    {
        "Front": "きっぱり",
        "Back": "clearly;plainly;distinctly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "規定",
        "Back": "regulation;provisions",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 712
    },
    {
        "Front": "起点",
        "Back": "starting point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 713
    },
    {
        "Front": "軌道",
        "Back": "orbit;railroad track",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 714
    },
    {
        "Front": "甲",
        "Back": "1st in rank;first sign of the Chinese calendar;shell;instep;grade A",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 715
    },
    {
        "Front": "気配",
        "Back": "indication;market trend;worry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 716
    },
    {
        "Front": "規範",
        "Back": "model;standard;pattern;norm;criterion;example",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 717
    },
    {
        "Front": "気品",
        "Back": "aroma",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 718
    },
    {
        "Front": "気風",
        "Back": "character;traits;ethos",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 719
    },
    {
        "Front": "起伏",
        "Back": "undulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 720
    },
    {
        "Front": "規模",
        "Back": "scale;scope;plan;structure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 721
    },
    {
        "Front": "気まぐれ",
        "Back": "whim;caprice;whimsy;fickle;moody;uneven temper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 722
    },
    {
        "Front": "生真面目",
        "Back": "too serious;person who is too serious;honesty;sincerity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 723
    },
    {
        "Front": "期末",
        "Back": "end of term",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 724
    },
    {
        "Front": "決まり悪い",
        "Back": "feeling awkward;being ashamed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 725
    },
    {
        "Front": "決まる",
        "Back": "to be decided;to be settled;to look good in (clothes)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 726
    },
    {
        "Front": "記名",
        "Back": "signature;register",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 727
    },
    {
        "Front": "脚色",
        "Back": "dramatization (e.g. film)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 728
    },
    {
        "Front": "脚本",
        "Back": "scenario",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 729
    },
    {
        "Front": "客観",
        "Back": "objective",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 730
    },
    {
        "Front": "規約",
        "Back": "agreement;rules;code",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 731
    },
    {
        "Front": "救援",
        "Back": "relief;rescue;reinforcement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 732
    },
    {
        "Front": "休学",
        "Back": "temporary absence from school;suspension",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 733
    },
    {
        "Front": "究極",
        "Back": "ultimate;final;eventual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 734
    },
    {
        "Front": "窮屈",
        "Back": "narrow;tight;stiff;rigid;uneasy;formal;constrained",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 735
    },
    {
        "Front": "球根",
        "Back": "(plant) bulb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 736
    },
    {
        "Front": "救済",
        "Back": "relief;aid;rescue;salvation;help",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 737
    },
    {
        "Front": "給食",
        "Back": "school lunch;providing a meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 738
    },
    {
        "Front": "給仕",
        "Back": "office boy (girl);page;waiter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 739
    },
    {
        "Front": "休戦",
        "Back": "truce;armistice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 740
    },
    {
        "Front": "旧知",
        "Back": "old friend;old friendship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 741
    },
    {
        "Front": "宮殿",
        "Back": "palace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 742
    },
    {
        "Front": "窮乏",
        "Back": "poverty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 743
    },
    {
        "Front": "丘陵",
        "Back": "hill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 744
    },
    {
        "Front": "共",
        "Back": "both;neither (neg);all;and;as well as;including;with;together with;plural ending",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 745
    },
    {
        "Front": "供",
        "Back": "offer;present;submit;serve (a meal);supply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 746
    },
    {
        "Front": "驚異",
        "Back": "wonder;miracle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 747
    },
    {
        "Front": "教員",
        "Back": "teaching staff",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 748
    },
    {
        "Front": "教科",
        "Back": "subject;curriculum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 749
    },
    {
        "Front": "協会",
        "Back": "association;society;organization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 750
    },
    {
        "Front": "共感",
        "Back": "sympathy;response",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 751
    },
    {
        "Front": "共学",
        "Back": "coeducation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 752
    },
    {
        "Front": "協議",
        "Back": "conference;consultation;discussion;negotiation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 753
    },
    {
        "Front": "教訓",
        "Back": "lesson;precept;moral instruction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 754
    },
    {
        "Front": "境遇",
        "Back": "environment;circumstances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 755
    },
    {
        "Front": "強行",
        "Back": "forcing;enforcement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 756
    },
    {
        "Front": "強硬",
        "Back": "firm;vigorous;unbending;unyielding;strong;stubborn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 757
    },
    {
        "Front": "凶作",
        "Back": "bad harvest;poor crop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 758
    },
    {
        "Front": "共産",
        "Back": "communism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 759
    },
    {
        "Front": "教材",
        "Back": "teaching materials",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 760
    },
    {
        "Front": "教習",
        "Back": "training;instruction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 761
    },
    {
        "Front": "郷愁",
        "Back": "nostalgia;homesickness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 762
    },
    {
        "Front": "教職",
        "Back": "teaching certificate;the teaching profession",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 763
    },
    {
        "Front": "享受",
        "Back": "reception;acceptance;enjoyment;being given",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 764
    },
    {
        "Front": "興じる",
        "Back": "to amuse oneself;to make merry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 765
    },
    {
        "Front": "強制",
        "Back": "obligation;coercion;compulsion;enforcement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 766
    },
    {
        "Front": "共存",
        "Back": "coexistence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 767
    },
    {
        "Front": "姉妹",
        "Back": "sisters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 768
    },
    {
        "Front": "協調",
        "Back": "co-operation;conciliation;harmony;firm (market) tone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 769
    },
    {
        "Front": "協定",
        "Back": "arrangement;pact;agreement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 770
    },
    {
        "Front": "脅迫",
        "Back": "threat;menace;coercion;terrorism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 771
    },
    {
        "Front": "共鳴",
        "Back": "resonance;sympathy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 772
    },
    {
        "Front": "郷里",
        "Back": "birth-place;home town",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 773
    },
    {
        "Front": "強烈",
        "Back": "strong;intense;severe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 774
    },
    {
        "Front": "共和",
        "Back": "republicanism;cooperation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 775
    },
    {
        "Front": "曲",
        "Back": "tune;piece of music",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 776
    },
    {
        "Front": "局限",
        "Back": "limit;localize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 777
    },
    {
        "Front": "極端",
        "Back": "extreme;extremity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 778
    },
    {
        "Front": "居住",
        "Back": "residence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 779
    },
    {
        "Front": "拒絶",
        "Back": "refusal;rejection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 780
    },
    {
        "Front": "拒否",
        "Back": "denial;veto;rejection;refusal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 781
    },
    {
        "Front": "許容",
        "Back": "permission;pardon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 782
    },
    {
        "Front": "距離",
        "Back": "distance;range",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 783
    },
    {
        "Front": "寄与",
        "Back": "contribution;service",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 784
    },
    {
        "Front": "清らか",
        "Back": "clean;pure;chaste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 785
    },
    {
        "Front": "気楽",
        "Back": "at ease;comfortable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 786
    },
    {
        "Front": "煌びやか",
        "Back": "gorgeous;gaudy;dazzling;gay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 787
    },
    {
        "Front": "切り",
        "Back": "limits;end;bounds;period;place to leave off;closing sentence;all there is;only;since",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 788
    },
    {
        "Front": "桐",
        "Back": "paulownia tree",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 789
    },
    {
        "Front": "切り替える",
        "Back": "to change;to exchange;to convert;to renew;to throw a switch;to replace;to switch over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 790
    },
    {
        "Front": "気流",
        "Back": "atmospheric current",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 791
    },
    {
        "Front": "奇麗",
        "Back": "pretty;clean;nice;tidy;beautiful;fair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 792
    },
    {
        "Front": "切れ目",
        "Back": "break;pause;gap;end;rift;interruption;cut;section;notch;incision;end (of a task)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 793
    },
    {
        "Front": "際",
        "Back": "edge;brink;verge;side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 794
    },
    {
        "Front": "木綿",
        "Back": "cotton",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 795
    },
    {
        "Front": "極めて",
        "Back": "exceedingly;extremely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 796
    },
    {
        "Front": "僅",
        "Back": "a little;small quantity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 797
    },
    {
        "Front": "近眼",
        "Back": "nearsightedness;shortsightedness;myopia",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 798
    },
    {
        "Front": "緊急",
        "Back": "urgent;pressing;emergency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 799
    },
    {
        "Front": "近々",
        "Back": "nearness;before long",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 800
    },
    {
        "Front": "近郊",
        "Back": "suburbs;outskirts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 801
    },
    {
        "Front": "均衡",
        "Back": "equilibrium;balance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 802
    },
    {
        "Front": "近視",
        "Back": "shortsightedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 803
    },
    {
        "Front": "禁じる",
        "Back": "to prohibit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 804
    },
    {
        "Front": "禁ずる",
        "Back": "to forbid;to suppress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 805
    },
    {
        "Front": "勤勉",
        "Back": "industry;diligence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 806
    },
    {
        "Front": "勤務",
        "Back": "service;duty;work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 807
    },
    {
        "Front": "禁物",
        "Back": "taboo;forbidden thing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 808
    },
    {
        "Front": "勤労",
        "Back": "labor;exertion;diligent service",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 809
    },
    {
        "Front": "議案",
        "Back": "legislative bill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 810
    },
    {
        "Front": "戯曲",
        "Back": "play;drama",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 811
    },
    {
        "Front": "議決",
        "Back": "resolution;decision;vote",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 812
    },
    {
        "Front": "議事堂",
        "Back": "Diet building",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 813
    },
    {
        "Front": "犠牲",
        "Back": "sacrifice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 814
    },
    {
        "Front": "偽造",
        "Back": "forgery;falsification;fabrication;counterfeiting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 815
    },
    {
        "Front": "議題",
        "Back": "topic of discussion;agenda",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 816
    },
    {
        "Front": "技能",
        "Back": "technical skill;ability;capacity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 817
    },
    {
        "Front": "逆転",
        "Back": "(sudden) change;reversal;turn-around;coming from behind (baseball)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 818
    },
    {
        "Front": "行",
        "Back": "line;row;verse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 819
    },
    {
        "Front": "業者",
        "Back": "trader;merchant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 820
    },
    {
        "Front": "行政",
        "Back": "administration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 821
    },
    {
        "Front": "業績",
        "Back": "achievement;performance;results;work;contribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 822
    },
    {
        "Front": "業務",
        "Back": "business;affairs;duties;work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 823
    },
    {
        "Front": "玉",
        "Back": "king (shogi)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 824
    },
    {
        "Front": "漁船",
        "Back": "fishing boat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 825
    },
    {
        "Front": "漁村",
        "Back": "fishing village",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 826
    },
    {
        "Front": "義理",
        "Back": "duty;sense of duty;honor;decency;courtesy;debt of gratitude;social obligation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 827
    },
    {
        "Front": "疑惑",
        "Back": "doubt;misgivings;distrust;suspicion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 828
    },
    {
        "Front": "吟味",
        "Back": "testing;scrutiny;careful investigation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 829
    },
    {
        "Front": "区",
        "Back": "ward;district;section",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 830
    },
    {
        "Front": "食い違う",
        "Back": "to cross each other;to run counter to;to differ;to clash;to go awry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 831
    },
    {
        "Front": "空腹",
        "Back": "hunger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 832
    },
    {
        "Front": "区画",
        "Back": "division;section;compartment;boundary;area;block",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 833
    },
    {
        "Front": "区間",
        "Back": "section (of track&nbsp;&nbsp;etc)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 834
    },
    {
        "Front": "茎",
        "Back": "stalk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 835
    },
    {
        "Front": "区切り",
        "Back": "an end;a stop;punctuation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 836
    },
    {
        "Front": "潜る",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;to drive;to pass through; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;to evade;to hide; 3.&nbsp;&nbsp;to dive (into or under water);to go undergro",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 837
    },
    {
        "Front": "種々",
        "Back": "variety",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 838
    },
    {
        "Front": "嚏",
        "Back": "sneeze",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 839
    },
    {
        "Front": "旧事",
        "Back": "past events;bygones",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 840
    },
    {
        "Front": "籤引",
        "Back": "lottery;drawn lot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 841
    },
    {
        "Front": "擽ぐったい",
        "Back": "ticklish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 842
    },
    {
        "Front": "草臥れる",
        "Back": "to get tired;to wear out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 843
    },
    {
        "Front": "下らない",
        "Back": "good-for-nothing;stupid;trivial;worthless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 844
    },
    {
        "Front": "件",
        "Back": "example;precedent;the usual;the said;the above-mentioned;(man) in question",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 845
    },
    {
        "Front": "口ずさむ",
        "Back": "to hum something;to sing to oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 846
    },
    {
        "Front": "嘴",
        "Back": "beak;bill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 847
    },
    {
        "Front": "朽ちる",
        "Back": "to rot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 848
    },
    {
        "Front": "くっきり",
        "Back": "distinctly;clearly;boldly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "屈折",
        "Back": "bending;indentation;refraction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 849
    },
    {
        "Front": "くっ付く",
        "Back": "to adhere to;to keep close to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 850
    },
    {
        "Front": "くっ付ける",
        "Back": "to attach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 851
    },
    {
        "Front": "覆す",
        "Back": "to overturn;to upset;to overthrow;to undermine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 852
    },
    {
        "Front": "諄い",
        "Back": "verbose;importunate;heavy (taste)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 853
    },
    {
        "Front": "国境",
        "Back": "national or state border",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 854
    },
    {
        "Front": "首飾り",
        "Back": "necklace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 855
    },
    {
        "Front": "首輪",
        "Back": "necklace;choker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 856
    },
    {
        "Front": "組み合わせ",
        "Back": "combination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 857
    },
    {
        "Front": "組み合わせる",
        "Back": "to join together;to combine;to join up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 858
    },
    {
        "Front": "組み込む",
        "Back": "to insert;to include;to cut in (printing)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 859
    },
    {
        "Front": "蔵",
        "Back": "warehouse;cellar;magazine;granary;godown;depository;treasury;elevator",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 860
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦しめる",
        "Back": "to torment;to harass;to inflict pain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 861
    },
    {
        "Front": "包む",
        "Back": "to be engulfed in;to be enveloped by;to wrap up;to tuck in;to pack;to do up;to cover with;to dress i",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 862
    },
    {
        "Front": "呉れ呉れも",
        "Back": "repeatedly;sincerely;earnestly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 863
    },
    {
        "Front": "呉れる",
        "Back": "to give;to let one have;to do for one;to be given",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 864
    },
    {
        "Front": "玄人",
        "Back": "expert;professional;geisha;prostitute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 865
    },
    {
        "Front": "黒字",
        "Back": "balance (figure) in the black",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 866
    },
    {
        "Front": "君主",
        "Back": "ruler;monarch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 867
    },
    {
        "Front": "愚痴",
        "Back": "idle complaint;grumble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 868
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぐっと",
        "Back": "firmly;fast;much;more",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぐらい",
        "Back": "approximately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "群",
        "Back": "group (math)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 869
    },
    {
        "Front": "軍艦",
        "Back": "warship;battleship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 870
    },
    {
        "Front": "群集",
        "Back": "(social) group;crowd;throng;mob;multitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 871
    },
    {
        "Front": "軍事",
        "Back": "military affairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 872
    },
    {
        "Front": "軍備",
        "Back": "armaments;military preparations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 873
    },
    {
        "Front": "軍服",
        "Back": "military or naval uniform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 874
    },
    {
        "Front": "刑",
        "Back": "penalty;sentence;punishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 875
    },
    {
        "Front": "頃",
        "Back": "time;about;toward;approximately (time)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 876
    },
    {
        "Front": "傾",
        "Back": "lean;incline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 877
    },
    {
        "Front": "系",
        "Back": "system;lineage;group",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 878
    },
    {
        "Front": "経過",
        "Back": "passage;expiration;progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 879
    },
    {
        "Front": "軽快",
        "Back": "rhythmical (e.g. melody);casual (e.g. dress);light;nimble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 880
    },
    {
        "Front": "警戒",
        "Back": "warning;admonition;vigilance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 881
    },
    {
        "Front": "計器",
        "Back": "meter;gauge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 882
    },
    {
        "Front": "契機",
        "Back": "opportunity;chance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 883
    },
    {
        "Front": "敬具",
        "Back": "Sincerely yours",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 884
    },
    {
        "Front": "軽減",
        "Back": "abatement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 885
    },
    {
        "Front": "掲載",
        "Back": "appearance (e.g. article in paper)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 886
    },
    {
        "Front": "傾斜",
        "Back": "inclination;slant;slope;bevel;list;dip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 887
    },
    {
        "Front": "形成",
        "Back": "formation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 888
    },
    {
        "Front": "形勢",
        "Back": "condition;situation;prospects",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 889
    },
    {
        "Front": "軽率",
        "Back": "rash;thoughtless;careless;hasty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 890
    },
    {
        "Front": "携帯",
        "Back": "carrying something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 891
    },
    {
        "Front": "形態",
        "Back": "form;shape;figure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 892
    },
    {
        "Front": "刑罰",
        "Back": "judgement;penalty;punishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 893
    },
    {
        "Front": "経費",
        "Back": "expenses;cost;outlay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 894
    },
    {
        "Front": "警部",
        "Back": "police inspector",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 895
    },
    {
        "Front": "軽蔑",
        "Back": "scorn;disdain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 896
    },
    {
        "Front": "経歴",
        "Back": "personal history;career",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 897
    },
    {
        "Front": "経路",
        "Back": "course;route;channel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 898
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚す",
        "Back": "to disgrace;to dishonour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 899
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚らわしい",
        "Back": "filthy;unfair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 900
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚れ",
        "Back": "uncleanness;impurity;disgrace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 901
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚れる",
        "Back": "to get dirty;to become dirty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 902
    },
    {
        "Front": "獣",
        "Back": "beast;brute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 903
    },
    {
        "Front": "吝嗇",
        "Back": "stinginess;miser;miserliness;skinflint;tightwad;niggard;pinching pennies",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 904
    },
    {
        "Front": "結核",
        "Back": "tuberculosis;tubercule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 905
    },
    {
        "Front": "血管",
        "Back": "blood vessel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 906
    },
    {
        "Front": "決行",
        "Back": "doing (with resolve);carrying out (i.e. a plan)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 907
    },
    {
        "Front": "決算",
        "Back": "balance sheet;settlement of accounts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 908
    },
    {
        "Front": "決勝",
        "Back": "decision of a contest;finals (in sports)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 909
    },
    {
        "Front": "結晶",
        "Back": "crystal;crystallization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 910
    },
    {
        "Front": "結成",
        "Back": "formation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 911
    },
    {
        "Front": "結束",
        "Back": "union;unity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 912
    },
    {
        "Front": "傑",
        "Back": "excellence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 913
    },
    {
        "Front": "決意",
        "Back": "decision;determination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 914
    },
    {
        "Front": "決議",
        "Back": "resolution;vote;decision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 915
    },
    {
        "Front": "結合",
        "Back": "combination;union",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 916
    },
    {
        "Front": "決断",
        "Back": "decision;determination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 917
    },
    {
        "Front": "欠乏",
        "Back": "want;shortage;famine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 918
    },
    {
        "Front": "蹴飛ばす",
        "Back": "to kick away;to kick off;to kick (someone);to refuse;to reject",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 919
    },
    {
        "Front": "貶す",
        "Back": "to speak ill of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 920
    },
    {
        "Front": "煙たい",
        "Back": "smoky;feeling awkward",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 921
    },
    {
        "Front": "煙る",
        "Back": "to smoke (e.g. fire)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 922
    },
    {
        "Front": "家来",
        "Back": "retainer;retinue;servant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 923
    },
    {
        "Front": "けれど",
        "Back": "but;however",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "圏",
        "Back": "sphere;circle;range",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 924
    },
    {
        "Front": "権",
        "Back": "authority;the right (to do something)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 925
    },
    {
        "Front": "権威",
        "Back": "authority;power;influence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 926
    },
    {
        "Front": "兼業",
        "Back": "side line;second business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 927
    },
    {
        "Front": "権限",
        "Back": "power;authority;jurisdiction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 928
    },
    {
        "Front": "健在",
        "Back": "in good health;well",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 929
    },
    {
        "Front": "懸賞",
        "Back": "offering prizes;winning;reward",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 930
    },
    {
        "Front": "検事",
        "Back": "public prosecutor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 931
    },
    {
        "Front": "健全",
        "Back": "health;soundness;wholesome",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 932
    },
    {
        "Front": "見地",
        "Back": "point of view",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 933
    },
    {
        "Front": "賢明",
        "Back": "wisdom;intelligence;prudence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 934
    },
    {
        "Front": "倹約",
        "Back": "thrift;economy;frugality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 935
    },
    {
        "Front": "兼用",
        "Back": "multi-use;combined use;combination;serving two purposes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 936
    },
    {
        "Front": "権力",
        "Back": "power;authority;influence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 937
    },
    {
        "Front": "劇団",
        "Back": "troupe;theatrical company",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 938
    },
    {
        "Front": "激励",
        "Back": "encouragement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 939
    },
    {
        "Front": "月謝",
        "Back": "monthly tuition fee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 940
    },
    {
        "Front": "げっそり",
        "Back": "being disheartened;losing weight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "月賦",
        "Back": "monthly installment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 941
    },
    {
        "Front": "下痢",
        "Back": "diarrhoea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 942
    },
    {
        "Front": "原",
        "Back": "original;primitive;primary;fundamental;raw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 943
    },
    {
        "Front": "原形",
        "Back": "original form;base form",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 944
    },
    {
        "Front": "現行",
        "Back": "present;current;in operation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 945
    },
    {
        "Front": "原作",
        "Back": "original work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 946
    },
    {
        "Front": "原子",
        "Back": "atom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 947
    },
    {
        "Front": "元首",
        "Back": "ruler;sovereign",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 948
    },
    {
        "Front": "原書",
        "Back": "original document",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 949
    },
    {
        "Front": "減少",
        "Back": "decrease;reduction;decline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 950
    },
    {
        "Front": "現場",
        "Back": "actual spot;scene;scene of the crime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 951
    },
    {
        "Front": "元素",
        "Back": "chemical element",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 952
    },
    {
        "Front": "原則",
        "Back": "principle;general rule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 953
    },
    {
        "Front": "現像",
        "Back": "developing (film)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 954
    },
    {
        "Front": "現地",
        "Back": "actual place;local",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 955
    },
    {
        "Front": "限定",
        "Back": "limit;restriction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 956
    },
    {
        "Front": "原点",
        "Back": "origin (coordinates);starting point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 957
    },
    {
        "Front": "原典",
        "Back": "original (text)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 958
    },
    {
        "Front": "減点",
        "Back": "subtract;give a demerit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 959
    },
    {
        "Front": "原爆",
        "Back": "atomic bomb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 960
    },
    {
        "Front": "原文",
        "Back": "the text;original",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 961
    },
    {
        "Front": "厳密",
        "Back": "strict;close",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 962
    },
    {
        "Front": "原油",
        "Back": "crude oil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 963
    },
    {
        "Front": "言論",
        "Back": "discussion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 964
    },
    {
        "Front": "故",
        "Back": "the late (deceased)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 965
    },
    {
        "Front": "戸",
        "Back": "counter for houses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 966
    },
    {
        "Front": "児",
        "Back": "child;the young of animals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 967
    },
    {
        "Front": "巨",
        "Back": "big;large;great",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 968
    },
    {
        "Front": "恋する",
        "Back": "to fall in love with;to love",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 969
    },
    {
        "Front": "溝",
        "Back": "10^38;hundred undecillion (American);hundred sextillion (British)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 970
    },
    {
        "Front": "校",
        "Back": "-school;proof",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 971
    },
    {
        "Front": "好意",
        "Back": "good will;favor;courtesy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 972
    },
    {
        "Front": "行為",
        "Back": "act;deed;conduct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 973
    },
    {
        "Front": "行員",
        "Back": "bank clerk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 974
    },
    {
        "Front": "交易",
        "Back": "trade;commerce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 975
    },
    {
        "Front": "公演",
        "Back": "public performance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 976
    },
    {
        "Front": "後悔",
        "Back": "regret;repentance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 977
    },
    {
        "Front": "公開",
        "Back": "presenting to the public",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 978
    },
    {
        "Front": "航海",
        "Back": "sail;voyage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 979
    },
    {
        "Front": "工学",
        "Back": "engineering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 980
    },
    {
        "Front": "皇居",
        "Back": "Imperial Palace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 981
    },
    {
        "Front": "好況",
        "Back": "prosperous conditions;healthy economy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 982
    },
    {
        "Front": "抗議",
        "Back": "protest;objection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 983
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉱業",
        "Back": "mining industry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 984
    },
    {
        "Front": "興業",
        "Back": "industrial enterprise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 985
    },
    {
        "Front": "高原",
        "Back": "tableland;plateau",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 986
    },
    {
        "Front": "煌々と",
        "Back": "brilliantly;brightly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 987
    },
    {
        "Front": "考古学",
        "Back": "archaeology",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 988
    },
    {
        "Front": "交互",
        "Back": "mutual;reciprocal;alternate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 989
    },
    {
        "Front": "工作",
        "Back": "work;construction;handicraft;maneuvering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 990
    },
    {
        "Front": "耕作",
        "Back": "cultivation;farming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 991
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉱山",
        "Back": "mine (ore)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 992
    },
    {
        "Front": "講習",
        "Back": "short course;training",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 993
    },
    {
        "Front": "交渉",
        "Back": "negotiations;discussions;connection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 994
    },
    {
        "Front": "高尚",
        "Back": "high;noble;refined;advanced",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 995
    },
    {
        "Front": "行進",
        "Back": "march;parade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 996
    },
    {
        "Front": "香辛料",
        "Back": "spices",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 997
    },
    {
        "Front": "口述",
        "Back": "verbal statement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 998
    },
    {
        "Front": "控除",
        "Back": "subsidy;deduction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 999
    },
    {
        "Front": "向上",
        "Back": "elevation;rise;improvement;advancement;progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1000
    },
    {
        "Front": "降水",
        "Back": "rainfall;precipitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1001
    },
    {
        "Front": "洪水",
        "Back": "flood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1002
    },
    {
        "Front": "公然",
        "Back": "open (e.g. secret);public;official",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1003
    },
    {
        "Front": "抗争",
        "Back": "dispute;resistance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1004
    },
    {
        "Front": "構想",
        "Back": "plan;plot;idea;conception",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1005
    },
    {
        "Front": "拘束",
        "Back": "restriction;restraint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1006
    },
    {
        "Front": "後退",
        "Back": "retreat;backspace (BS)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1007
    },
    {
        "Front": "光沢",
        "Back": "brilliance;polish;lustre;glossy finish (of photographs)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1008
    },
    {
        "Front": "公団",
        "Back": "public corporation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1009
    },
    {
        "Front": "好調",
        "Back": "favourable;promising;satisfactory;in good shape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1010
    },
    {
        "Front": "口頭",
        "Back": "oral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1011
    },
    {
        "Front": "講読",
        "Back": "reading;translation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1012
    },
    {
        "Front": "購読",
        "Back": "subscription (e.g. magazine)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1013
    },
    {
        "Front": "購入",
        "Back": "purchase;buy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1014
    },
    {
        "Front": "公認",
        "Back": "official recognition;authorization;licence;accreditation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1015
    },
    {
        "Front": "光熱費",
        "Back": "cost of fuel and light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1016
    },
    {
        "Front": "荒廃",
        "Back": "ruin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1017
    },
    {
        "Front": "購買",
        "Back": "purchase;buy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1018
    },
    {
        "Front": "好評",
        "Back": "popularity;favorable reputation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1019
    },
    {
        "Front": "交付",
        "Back": "delivering;furnishing (with copies)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1020
    },
    {
        "Front": "降伏",
        "Back": "capitulation;surrender;submission",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1021
    },
    {
        "Front": "興奮",
        "Back": "excitement;stimulation;agitation;arousal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1022
    },
    {
        "Front": "公募",
        "Back": "public appeal;public contribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1023
    },
    {
        "Front": "巧妙",
        "Back": "ingenious;skillful;clever;deft",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1024
    },
    {
        "Front": "公用",
        "Back": "government business;public use;public expense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1025
    },
    {
        "Front": "小売",
        "Back": "retail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1026
    },
    {
        "Front": "効率",
        "Back": "efficiency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1027
    },
    {
        "Front": "公立",
        "Back": "public (institution)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1028
    },
    {
        "Front": "小柄",
        "Back": "short (build)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1029
    },
    {
        "Front": "小切手",
        "Back": "cheque;check",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1030
    },
    {
        "Front": "国産",
        "Back": "domestic products",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1031
    },
    {
        "Front": "国定",
        "Back": "state-sponsored;national",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1032
    },
    {
        "Front": "国土",
        "Back": "realm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1033
    },
    {
        "Front": "告白",
        "Back": "confession;acknowledgement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1034
    },
    {
        "Front": "国防",
        "Back": "national defence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1035
    },
    {
        "Front": "国有",
        "Back": "national ownership",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1036
    },
    {
        "Front": "国連",
        "Back": "U.N.;United Nations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1037
    },
    {
        "Front": "漕ぐ",
        "Back": "to row;to scull;to pedal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1038
    },
    {
        "Front": "焦げ茶",
        "Back": "black tea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1039
    },
    {
        "Front": "個々",
        "Back": "individual;one by one",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1040
    },
    {
        "Front": "箇箇",
        "Back": "individual;separate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1041
    },
    {
        "Front": "心地",
        "Back": "feeling;sensation;mood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1042
    },
    {
        "Front": "心得",
        "Back": "knowledge;information",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1043
    },
    {
        "Front": "心掛け",
        "Back": "readiness;intention;aim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1044
    },
    {
        "Front": "心掛ける",
        "Back": "to bear in mind;to aim to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1045
    },
    {
        "Front": "志",
        "Back": "will;intention;motive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1046
    },
    {
        "Front": "志す",
        "Back": "to plan;to intend;to aspire to;to set aims (sights on)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1047
    },
    {
        "Front": "心強い",
        "Back": "heartening;reassuring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1048
    },
    {
        "Front": "心細い",
        "Back": "helpless;forlorn;hopeless;unpromising;lonely;discouraging;disheartening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1049
    },
    {
        "Front": "試み",
        "Back": "trial;experiment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1050
    },
    {
        "Front": "試みる",
        "Back": "to try;to test",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1051
    },
    {
        "Front": "快い",
        "Back": "pleasant;agreeable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1052
    },
    {
        "Front": "凝らす",
        "Back": "to freeze;to congeal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1053
    },
    {
        "Front": "凝る",
        "Back": "to congeal;to freeze",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1054
    },
    {
        "Front": "拵える",
        "Back": "to make;to manufacture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1055
    },
    {
        "Front": "孤児",
        "Back": "orphan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1056
    },
    {
        "Front": "拗れる",
        "Back": "to get complicated;to grow worse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1057
    },
    {
        "Front": "故人",
        "Back": "the deceased;old friend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1058
    },
    {
        "Front": "梢",
        "Back": "treetop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1059
    },
    {
        "Front": "個性",
        "Back": "individuality;personality;idiosyncrasy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1060
    },
    {
        "Front": "戸籍",
        "Back": "census;family register",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1061
    },
    {
        "Front": "小銭",
        "Back": "coins;small change",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1062
    },
    {
        "Front": "固体",
        "Back": "solid (body)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1063
    },
    {
        "Front": "堪える",
        "Back": "to bear;to stand;to endure;to put up with;to support;to withstand;to resist;to brave;to be fit for;t",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1065
    },
    {
        "Front": "答え",
        "Back": "answer;response",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1064
    },
    {
        "Front": "火燵",
        "Back": "table with heater;(orig) charcoal brazier in a floor well",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1066
    },
    {
        "Front": "古代",
        "Back": "ancient times",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1067
    },
    {
        "Front": "こだわる",
        "Back": "to fuss over;to be particular about;to be concerned about",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "誇張",
        "Back": "exaggeration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1068
    },
    {
        "Front": "滑稽",
        "Back": "funny;humorous;comical;laughable;ridiculous;joking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1069
    },
    {
        "Front": "国交",
        "Back": "diplomatic relations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1070
    },
    {
        "Front": "骨董品",
        "Back": "curio",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1071
    },
    {
        "Front": "骨",
        "Back": "knack;skill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1072
    },
    {
        "Front": "固定",
        "Back": "fixation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1073
    },
    {
        "Front": "事柄",
        "Back": "matter;thing;affair;circumstance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1074
    },
    {
        "Front": "悉く",
        "Back": "altogether;entirely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1075
    },
    {
        "Front": "言伝",
        "Back": "declaration;hearsay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1076
    },
    {
        "Front": "殊に",
        "Back": "especially;above all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1077
    },
    {
        "Front": "事によると",
        "Back": "depending on the circumstances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1078
    },
    {
        "Front": "孤独",
        "Back": "isolation;loneliness;solitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1079
    },
    {
        "Front": "粉々",
        "Back": "in very small pieces",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1080
    },
    {
        "Front": "此の",
        "Back": "this",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1081
    },
    {
        "Front": "この間",
        "Back": "the other day;lately;recently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1082
    },
    {
        "Front": "この頃",
        "Back": "recently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1083
    },
    {
        "Front": "好ましい",
        "Back": "nice;likeable;desirable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1084
    },
    {
        "Front": "個別",
        "Back": "particular case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1085
    },
    {
        "Front": "零す",
        "Back": "to spill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1086
    },
    {
        "Front": "零れる",
        "Back": "to overflow;to spill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1087
    },
    {
        "Front": "細やか",
        "Back": "friendly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1088
    },
    {
        "Front": "混む",
        "Back": "to be crowded",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1089
    },
    {
        "Front": "込める",
        "Back": "to include;to put into",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1090
    },
    {
        "Front": "篭る",
        "Back": "to seclude oneself;to be confined in;to be implied;to be stuffy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1091
    },
    {
        "Front": "固有",
        "Back": "characteristic;tradition;peculiar;inherent;eigen-",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1092
    },
    {
        "Front": "雇用",
        "Back": "employment (long term);hire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1094
    },
    {
        "Front": "暦",
        "Back": "calendar;almanac",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1093
    },
    {
        "Front": "孤立",
        "Back": "isolation;helplessness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1095
    },
    {
        "Front": "懲りる",
        "Back": "to learn by experience;to be disgusted with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1096
    },
    {
        "Front": "此れ",
        "Back": "this",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1097
    },
    {
        "Front": "此れ等",
        "Back": "these",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1098
    },
    {
        "Front": "魂",
        "Back": "soul;spirit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1099
    },
    {
        "Front": "根気",
        "Back": "patience;perseverance;energy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1101
    },
    {
        "Front": "根拠",
        "Back": "basis;foundation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1100
    },
    {
        "Front": "混血",
        "Back": "mixed race;mixed parentage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1102
    },
    {
        "Front": "昆虫",
        "Back": "insect;bug",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1103
    },
    {
        "Front": "根底",
        "Back": "root;basis;foundation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1104
    },
    {
        "Front": "混同",
        "Back": "confusion;mixing;merger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1105
    },
    {
        "Front": "今日は",
        "Back": "hello;good day (daytime greeting&nbsp;&nbsp;id)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1106
    },
    {
        "Front": "今晩は",
        "Back": "good evening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1107
    },
    {
        "Front": "根本",
        "Back": "origin;source;foundation;root;base;principle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1108
    },
    {
        "Front": "御",
        "Back": "go-;honourable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1109
    },
    {
        "Front": "語彙",
        "Back": "vocabulary;glossary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1110
    },
    {
        "Front": "濠",
        "Back": "moat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1111
    },
    {
        "Front": "業",
        "Back": "Buddhist karma;actions committed in a former life",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1112
    },
    {
        "Front": "号",
        "Back": "number;issue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1113
    },
    {
        "Front": "合意",
        "Back": "agreement;consent;mutual understanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1114
    },
    {
        "Front": "合議",
        "Back": "consultation;conference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1115
    },
    {
        "Front": "強気",
        "Back": "great;grand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1116
    },
    {
        "Front": "合成",
        "Back": "synthesis;composition;synthetic;composite;mixed;combined;compound",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1117
    },
    {
        "Front": "護衛",
        "Back": "guard;convoy;escort",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1118
    },
    {
        "Front": "語句",
        "Back": "words;phrases",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1119
    },
    {
        "Front": "極楽",
        "Back": "paradise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1120
    },
    {
        "Front": "ご苦労様",
        "Back": "Thank you very much for your....",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1121
    },
    {
        "Front": "語源",
        "Back": "word root;word derivation;etymology",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1122
    },
    {
        "Front": "誤差",
        "Back": "error",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1123
    },
    {
        "Front": "ご座います",
        "Back": "to be (polite);to exist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1124
    },
    {
        "Front": "ご馳走",
        "Back": "feast;treating (someone)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1125
    },
    {
        "Front": "ご馳走さま",
        "Back": "feast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1126
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎",
        "Back": "each respectively",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1127
    },
    {
        "Front": "碁盤",
        "Back": "Go board",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1128
    },
    {
        "Front": "ご無沙汰",
        "Back": "not writing or contacting for a while",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1129
    },
    {
        "Front": "誤魔化す",
        "Back": "to deceive;to falsify;to misrepresent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1130
    },
    {
        "Front": "御免ください",
        "Back": "May I come in?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1131
    },
    {
        "Front": "御免なさい",
        "Back": "I beg your pardon;excuse me",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1132
    },
    {
        "Front": "御覧なさい",
        "Back": "(please) look;(please) try to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1133
    },
    {
        "Front": "佐",
        "Back": "help",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1134
    },
    {
        "Front": "再",
        "Back": "re-;again;repeated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1135
    },
    {
        "Front": "差異",
        "Back": "difference;disparity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1136
    },
    {
        "Front": "歳",
        "Back": "#NAME?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1137
    },
    {
        "Front": "再会",
        "Back": "another meeting;meeting again;reunion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1138
    },
    {
        "Front": "災害",
        "Back": "calamity;disaster;misfortune",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1139
    },
    {
        "Front": "細菌",
        "Back": "bacillus;bacterium;germ",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1140
    },
    {
        "Front": "細工",
        "Back": "work;craftsmanship;tactics;trick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1141
    },
    {
        "Front": "採掘",
        "Back": "mining",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1142
    },
    {
        "Front": "採決",
        "Back": "vote;roll call",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1143
    },
    {
        "Front": "再建",
        "Back": "rebuilding;reconstruction;rehabilitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1144
    },
    {
        "Front": "再現",
        "Back": "reappearance;reproduction;return;revival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1145
    },
    {
        "Front": "採算",
        "Back": "profit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1146
    },
    {
        "Front": "採集",
        "Back": "collecting;gathering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1147
    },
    {
        "Front": "再生",
        "Back": "playback;regeneration;resuscitation;return to life;rebirth;reincarnation;narrow escape;reclamation;r",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1148
    },
    {
        "Front": "最善",
        "Back": "the very best",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1149
    },
    {
        "Front": "採択",
        "Back": "adoption;selection;choice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1150
    },
    {
        "Front": "再発",
        "Back": "return;relapse;reoccurrence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1151
    },
    {
        "Front": "栽培",
        "Back": "cultivation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1152
    },
    {
        "Front": "細胞",
        "Back": "cell (biology)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1153
    },
    {
        "Front": "採用",
        "Back": "use;adopt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1154
    },
    {
        "Front": "遮る",
        "Back": "to interrupt;to intercept;to obstruct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1155
    },
    {
        "Front": "囀る",
        "Back": "to sing;to chirp;to twitter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1156
    },
    {
        "Front": "冴える",
        "Back": "to be clear;to be serene;to be cold;to be skillful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1157
    },
    {
        "Front": "竿",
        "Back": "rod;pole (e.g. for drying laundry)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1158
    },
    {
        "Front": "栄える",
        "Back": "to prosper;to flourish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1159
    },
    {
        "Front": "杯",
        "Back": "wine cups",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1160
    },
    {
        "Front": "逆立ち",
        "Back": "handstand;headstand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1161
    },
    {
        "Front": "逆上る",
        "Back": "to go back;to go upstream;to make retroactive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1162
    },
    {
        "Front": "盛る",
        "Back": "to prosper;to flourish;to copulate (animals)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1163
    },
    {
        "Front": "差額",
        "Back": "balance;difference;margin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1164
    },
    {
        "Front": "下がる",
        "Back": "to hang down;to abate;to retire;to fall;to step back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1165
    },
    {
        "Front": "一昨昨日",
        "Back": "two days before yesterday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1166
    },
    {
        "Front": "先に",
        "Back": "before;earlier than;ahead;beyond;away;previously;recently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1167
    },
    {
        "Front": "詐欺",
        "Back": "fraud;swindle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1168
    },
    {
        "Front": "作",
        "Back": "a work;a harvest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1169
    },
    {
        "Front": "策",
        "Back": "plan;policy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1170
    },
    {
        "Front": "柵",
        "Back": "fence;paling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1171
    },
    {
        "Front": "削減",
        "Back": "cut;reduction;curtailment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1172
    },
    {
        "Front": "錯誤",
        "Back": "mistake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1173
    },
    {
        "Front": "作戦",
        "Back": "military or naval operations;tactics;strategy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1174
    },
    {
        "Front": "作物",
        "Back": "literary work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1175
    },
    {
        "Front": "叫び",
        "Back": "shout;scream;outcry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1176
    },
    {
        "Front": "裂ける",
        "Back": "to split;to tear;to burst",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1177
    },
    {
        "Front": "捧げる",
        "Back": "to lift up;to give;to offer;to consecrate;to devote;to sacrifice;to dedicate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1178
    },
    {
        "Front": "差し掛かる",
        "Back": "to come near to;to approach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1179
    },
    {
        "Front": "指図",
        "Back": "instruction;mandate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1180
    },
    {
        "Front": "差し出す",
        "Back": "to present;to submit;to tender;to hold out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1181
    },
    {
        "Front": "差し支える",
        "Back": "to interfere;to hinder;to become impeded",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1182
    },
    {
        "Front": "差し引く",
        "Back": "to deduct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1183
    },
    {
        "Front": "些事",
        "Back": "something small or petty;trifle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1184
    },
    {
        "Front": "授ける",
        "Back": "to grant;to award;to teach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1185
    },
    {
        "Front": "嘸",
        "Back": "I am sure;certainly;no doubt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1186
    },
    {
        "Front": "定まる",
        "Back": "to become settled;to be fixed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1187
    },
    {
        "Front": "定める",
        "Back": "to decide;to establish;to determine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1188
    },
    {
        "Front": "錯覚",
        "Back": "optical illusion;hallucination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1189
    },
    {
        "Front": "早急",
        "Back": "urgent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1190
    },
    {
        "Front": "察する",
        "Back": "to guess;to sense;to presume;to judge;to sympathize with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1191
    },
    {
        "Front": "さっと",
        "Back": "quickly;suddenly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "冊",
        "Back": "counter for books",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1192
    },
    {
        "Front": "殺人",
        "Back": "murder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1193
    },
    {
        "Front": "偖",
        "Back": "well;now;then",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1194
    },
    {
        "Front": "悟る",
        "Back": "to attain enlightenment;to perceive;to understand;to discern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1195
    },
    {
        "Front": "真実",
        "Back": "truth;reality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1196
    },
    {
        "Front": "裁く",
        "Back": "to judge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1197
    },
    {
        "Front": "錆び",
        "Back": "rust (colour)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1198
    },
    {
        "Front": "左程",
        "Back": "(not) very;(not) much",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1199
    },
    {
        "Front": "様",
        "Back": "Mr. or Mrs.;manner;kind;appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1200
    },
    {
        "Front": "三味線",
        "Back": "three-stringed Japanese guitar;shamisen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1201
    },
    {
        "Front": "侍",
        "Back": "Samurai;warrior",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1202
    },
    {
        "Front": "然も",
        "Back": "with gusto;with satisfaction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1203
    },
    {
        "Front": "作用",
        "Back": "action;operation;effect;function",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1204
    },
    {
        "Front": "左様なら",
        "Back": "good-bye",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1205
    },
    {
        "Front": "拐う",
        "Back": "to carry off;to run away with;to kidnap;to abduct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1206
    },
    {
        "Front": "爽やか",
        "Back": "fresh;refreshing;invigorating;clear;fluent;eloquent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1207
    },
    {
        "Front": "障る",
        "Back": "to hinder;to interfere with;to affect;to do one harm;to be harmful to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1208
    },
    {
        "Front": "酸",
        "Back": "acid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1209
    },
    {
        "Front": "さん",
        "Back": "Mr or Mrs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "酸化",
        "Back": "oxidation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1210
    },
    {
        "Front": "山岳",
        "Back": "mountains",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1211
    },
    {
        "Front": "産休",
        "Back": "maternity leave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1212
    },
    {
        "Front": "桟橋",
        "Back": "wharf;bridge;jetty;pier",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1213
    },
    {
        "Front": "参議院",
        "Back": "House of Councillors",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1214
    },
    {
        "Front": "産後",
        "Back": "postpartum;after childbirth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1215
    },
    {
        "Front": "産出",
        "Back": "yield;produce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1216
    },
    {
        "Front": "参照",
        "Back": "reference;consultation;consultation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1217
    },
    {
        "Front": "参上",
        "Back": "calling on;visiting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1218
    },
    {
        "Front": "賛成",
        "Back": "approval;agreement;support;favour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1219
    },
    {
        "Front": "賛美",
        "Back": "praise;adoration;glorification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1220
    },
    {
        "Front": "産婦人科",
        "Back": "maternity and gynecology department",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1221
    },
    {
        "Front": "産物",
        "Back": "product;result;fruit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1222
    },
    {
        "Front": "山腹",
        "Back": "hillside;mountainside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1223
    },
    {
        "Front": "山脈",
        "Back": "mountain range",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1224
    },
    {
        "Front": "財",
        "Back": "fortune;riches",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1225
    },
    {
        "Front": "財源",
        "Back": "source of funds;resources;finances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1226
    },
    {
        "Front": "在庫",
        "Back": "stockpile;stock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1227
    },
    {
        "Front": "財政",
        "Back": "economy;financial affairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1228
    },
    {
        "Front": "座談会",
        "Back": "symposium;round-table discussion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1229
    },
    {
        "Front": "雑貨",
        "Back": "miscellaneous goods;general goods;sundries",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1230
    },
    {
        "Front": "雑",
        "Back": "rough;crude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1231
    },
    {
        "Front": "雑談",
        "Back": "chatting;idle talk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1232
    },
    {
        "Front": "雑木",
        "Back": "various kinds of small trees;assorted trees",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1233
    },
    {
        "Front": "座標",
        "Back": "coordinate(s)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1234
    },
    {
        "Front": "残金",
        "Back": "remaining money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1235
    },
    {
        "Front": "残酷",
        "Back": "cruelty;harshness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1236
    },
    {
        "Front": "残高",
        "Back": "(bank) balance;remainder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1237
    },
    {
        "Front": "死",
        "Back": "death;decease",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1238
    },
    {
        "Front": "し",
        "Back": "10^24 (kanji is JIS X 0212 kuten 4906);septillion (American);quadrillion (British)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "次",
        "Back": "order;sequence;times;next;below",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1239
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕上がり",
        "Back": "finish;end;completion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1240
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕上げ",
        "Back": "end;finishing touches;being finished",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1241
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕上げる",
        "Back": "to finish up;to complete",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1242
    },
    {
        "Front": "明々後日",
        "Back": "two days after tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1243
    },
    {
        "Front": "飼育",
        "Back": "breeding;raising;rearing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1244
    },
    {
        "Front": "強いて",
        "Back": "by force",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1245
    },
    {
        "Front": "強いる",
        "Back": "to force;to compel;to coerce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1246
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕入れる",
        "Back": "to lay in stock;to replenish stock;to procure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1247
    },
    {
        "Front": "しいんと",
        "Back": "silent (as the grave);(deathly) quiet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "歯科",
        "Back": "dentistry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1248
    },
    {
        "Front": "資格",
        "Back": "qualifications;requirements;capabilities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1249
    },
    {
        "Front": "視覚",
        "Back": "sense of sight;vision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1250
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕掛け",
        "Back": "device;trick;mechanism;gadget;(small) scale;half finished;commencement;set up;challenge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1251
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕掛ける",
        "Back": "to commence;to lay (mines);to set (traps);to wage (war);to challenge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1252
    },
    {
        "Front": "然し",
        "Back": "however;but",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1253
    },
    {
        "Front": "然しながら",
        "Back": "nevertheless;however",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1254
    },
    {
        "Front": "而も",
        "Back": "moreover;furthermore;nevertheless;and yet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1255
    },
    {
        "Front": "市街",
        "Back": "urban areas;the streets;town;city",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1256
    },
    {
        "Front": "指揮",
        "Back": "command;direction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1257
    },
    {
        "Front": "色彩",
        "Back": "colour;hue;tints",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1258
    },
    {
        "Front": "式場",
        "Back": "ceremonial hall;place of ceremony (e.g. marriage)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1259
    },
    {
        "Front": "為来り",
        "Back": "customs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1260
    },
    {
        "Front": "頻りに",
        "Back": "frequently;repeatedly;incessantly;eagerly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1261
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕切る",
        "Back": "to partition;to divide;to mark off;to settle accounts;to toe the mark",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1262
    },
    {
        "Front": "資金",
        "Back": "funds;capital",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1263
    },
    {
        "Front": "施行",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;execution;enforcing;carrying out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1264
    },
    {
        "Front": "しくじる",
        "Back": "to fail;to fall through;to blunder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕組み",
        "Back": "devising;plan;plot;contrivance;construction;arrangement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1265
    },
    {
        "Front": "死刑",
        "Back": "death penalty;capital punishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1266
    },
    {
        "Front": "湿気る",
        "Back": "to be damp;to be moist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1267
    },
    {
        "Front": "思考",
        "Back": "thought",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1268
    },
    {
        "Front": "志向",
        "Back": "intention;aim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1269
    },
    {
        "Front": "嗜好",
        "Back": "taste;liking;preference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1270
    },
    {
        "Front": "視察",
        "Back": "inspection;observation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1271
    },
    {
        "Front": "資産",
        "Back": "property;fortune;means;assets",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1272
    },
    {
        "Front": "刺繍",
        "Back": "embroidery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1273
    },
    {
        "Front": "支持",
        "Back": "support;maintenance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1274
    },
    {
        "Front": "指示",
        "Back": "indication;instruction;directions",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1275
    },
    {
        "Front": "雫",
        "Back": "drop (of water)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1276
    },
    {
        "Front": "沈める",
        "Back": "to sink;to submerge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1277
    },
    {
        "Front": "施設",
        "Back": "institution;establishment;facility;(army) engineer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1278
    },
    {
        "Front": "子息",
        "Back": "son",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1279
    },
    {
        "Front": "慕う",
        "Back": "to yearn for;to miss;to adore;to love dearly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1280
    },
    {
        "Front": "従って",
        "Back": "therefore;consequently;in accordance with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1281
    },
    {
        "Front": "下心",
        "Back": "secret intention;motive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1282
    },
    {
        "Front": "親しむ",
        "Back": "to be intimate with;to befriend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1283
    },
    {
        "Front": "下調べ",
        "Back": "preliminary investigation;preparation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1284
    },
    {
        "Front": "下地",
        "Back": "groundwork;foundation;inclination;aptitude;elementary knowledge of;grounding in;prearrangement;spade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1285
    },
    {
        "Front": "認める",
        "Back": "to write up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1286
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕立てる",
        "Back": "to tailor;to make;to prepare;to train;to send (a messenger)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1287
    },
    {
        "Front": "下取り",
        "Back": "trade in;part exchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1288
    },
    {
        "Front": "下火",
        "Back": "burning low;waning;declining",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1289
    },
    {
        "Front": "失格",
        "Back": "disqualification;elimination;incapacity (legal)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1290
    },
    {
        "Front": "確り",
        "Back": "firmly;tightly;reliable;level-headed;steady",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1291
    },
    {
        "Front": "質素",
        "Back": "simplicity;modesty;frugality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1292
    },
    {
        "Front": "失調",
        "Back": "lack of harmony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1293
    },
    {
        "Front": "嫉妬",
        "Back": "jealousy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1294
    },
    {
        "Front": "尻尾",
        "Back": "tail (animal)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1295
    },
    {
        "Front": "室",
        "Back": "room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1296
    },
    {
        "Front": "質疑",
        "Back": "question",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1297
    },
    {
        "Front": "躾",
        "Back": "home discipline;training;upbringing;breeding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1298
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕付ける",
        "Back": "to be used to a job;to begin to do;to baste;to tack;to plant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1299
    },
    {
        "Front": "指摘",
        "Back": "pointing out;identification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1300
    },
    {
        "Front": "視点",
        "Back": "opinion;point of view;visual point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1301
    },
    {
        "Front": "萎びる",
        "Back": "to wilt;to fade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1302
    },
    {
        "Front": "嫋か",
        "Back": "supple;flexible;elastic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1303
    },
    {
        "Front": "屎尿",
        "Back": "excreta;raw sewage;human waste;night soil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1304
    },
    {
        "Front": "凌ぐ",
        "Back": "to outdo;to surpass;to endure;to keep out (rain);to stave off;to tide over;to pull through;to defy;t",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1305
    },
    {
        "Front": "始発",
        "Back": "first train",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1306
    },
    {
        "Front": "芝",
        "Back": "lawn;sod;turf",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1307
    },
    {
        "Front": "屡",
        "Back": "often;again and again;frequently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1308
    },
    {
        "Front": "暫く",
        "Back": "little while",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1309
    },
    {
        "Front": "痺れる",
        "Back": "to become numb;to go to sleep (i.e.&nbsp;&nbsp;a limb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1310
    },
    {
        "Front": "渋い",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;tasteful (clothing);cool;an aura of refined masculinity; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;astringent;sullen;bitter (taste); 3",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1311
    },
    {
        "Front": "私物",
        "Back": "private property;personal effects",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1312
    },
    {
        "Front": "しぶとい",
        "Back": "tenacious;stubborn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "司法",
        "Back": "administration of justice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1313
    },
    {
        "Front": "脂肪",
        "Back": "fat;grease;blubber",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1314
    },
    {
        "Front": "志望",
        "Back": "wish;desire;ambition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1315
    },
    {
        "Front": "萎む",
        "Back": "to wither;to fade (away);to shrivel;to wilt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1316
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕舞",
        "Back": "end;termination;informal (Noh play)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1317
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕舞う",
        "Back": "to finish;to close;to do something completely;to put away;to put an end to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1318
    },
    {
        "Front": "しまった",
        "Back": "Damn it!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "始末",
        "Back": "management;dealing;settlement;cleaning up afterwards",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1319
    },
    {
        "Front": "泌み泌み",
        "Back": "keenly;deeply;heartily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1320
    },
    {
        "Front": "染みる",
        "Back": "to pierce;to permeate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1321
    },
    {
        "Front": "使命",
        "Back": "mission;errand;message",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1322
    },
    {
        "Front": "締め切り",
        "Back": "closing;cut-off;end;deadline;Closed;No Entrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1323
    },
    {
        "Front": "僕",
        "Back": "manservant;servant (of God)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1324
    },
    {
        "Front": "社交",
        "Back": "social life;social intercourse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1325
    },
    {
        "Front": "謝絶",
        "Back": "refusal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1326
    },
    {
        "Front": "社宅",
        "Back": "company owned house",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1327
    },
    {
        "Front": "吃逆",
        "Back": "hiccough;hiccup",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1328
    },
    {
        "Front": "喋る",
        "Back": "to talk;to chat;to chatter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1329
    },
    {
        "Front": "斜面",
        "Back": "slope;slanting surface;bevel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1330
    },
    {
        "Front": "洒落",
        "Back": "frank;open-hearted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1331
    },
    {
        "Front": "洒落る",
        "Back": "to joke;to play on words;to dress stylishly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1332
    },
    {
        "Front": "視野",
        "Back": "field of vision;outlook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1333
    },
    {
        "Front": "種",
        "Back": "kind;variety;species",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1334
    },
    {
        "Front": "衆",
        "Back": "masses;great number;the people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1335
    },
    {
        "Front": "周",
        "Back": "circuit;lap;circumference;vicinity;Chou (dynasty)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1336
    },
    {
        "Front": "収益",
        "Back": "earnings;proceeds;returns",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1337
    },
    {
        "Front": "修学",
        "Back": "learning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1338
    },
    {
        "Front": "周期",
        "Back": "cycle;period",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1339
    },
    {
        "Front": "衆議院",
        "Back": "Lower House;House of Representatives",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1340
    },
    {
        "Front": "就業",
        "Back": "employment;starting work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1341
    },
    {
        "Front": "修行",
        "Back": "pursuit of knowledge;studying;learning;training;ascetic practice;discipline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1342
    },
    {
        "Front": "集計",
        "Back": "totalization;aggregate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1343
    },
    {
        "Front": "襲撃",
        "Back": "attack;charge;raid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1344
    },
    {
        "Front": "収支",
        "Back": "income and expenditure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1345
    },
    {
        "Front": "終始",
        "Back": "beginning and end;from beginning to end;doing a thing from beginning to end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1346
    },
    {
        "Front": "修士",
        "Back": "Masters degree program",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1347
    },
    {
        "Front": "収集",
        "Back": "gathering up;collection;accumulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1348
    },
    {
        "Front": "修飾",
        "Back": "ornamentation;embellishment;decoration;adornment;polish up (writing);modification (gram)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1349
    },
    {
        "Front": "終日",
        "Back": "all day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1350
    },
    {
        "Front": "執着",
        "Back": "attachment;adhesion;tenacity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1351
    },
    {
        "Front": "収容",
        "Back": "accommodation;reception;seating;housing;custody;admission;entering (in a dictionary)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1352
    },
    {
        "Front": "修了",
        "Back": "completion (of a course)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1353
    },
    {
        "Front": "守衛",
        "Back": "security guard;doorkeeper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1354
    },
    {
        "Front": "主演",
        "Back": "starring;playing the leading part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1355
    },
    {
        "Front": "主観",
        "Back": "subjectivity;subject;ego",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1356
    },
    {
        "Front": "祝賀",
        "Back": "celebration;congratulations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1357
    },
    {
        "Front": "宿命",
        "Back": "fate;destiny;predestination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1358
    },
    {
        "Front": "主権",
        "Back": "sovereignty;supremacy;dominion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1359
    },
    {
        "Front": "手芸",
        "Back": "handicrafts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1360
    },
    {
        "Front": "主催",
        "Back": "organization;sponsorship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1361
    },
    {
        "Front": "取材",
        "Back": "choice of subject;collecting data",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1362
    },
    {
        "Front": "趣旨",
        "Back": "object;meaning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1363
    },
    {
        "Front": "主食",
        "Back": "staple food",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1364
    },
    {
        "Front": "主人公",
        "Back": "protagonist;main character;hero(ine) (of a story);head of household",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1365
    },
    {
        "Front": "主体",
        "Back": "subject;main constituent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1366
    },
    {
        "Front": "主題",
        "Back": "subject;theme;motif",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1367
    },
    {
        "Front": "出血",
        "Back": "bleeding;haemorrhage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1368
    },
    {
        "Front": "出産",
        "Back": "(child)birth;delivery;production (of goods)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1369
    },
    {
        "Front": "出社",
        "Back": "arrival (in a country&nbsp;&nbsp;at work&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1370
    },
    {
        "Front": "出生",
        "Back": "birth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1371
    },
    {
        "Front": "出世",
        "Back": "promotion;successful career;eminence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1372
    },
    {
        "Front": "出費",
        "Back": "expenses;disbursements",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1373
    },
    {
        "Front": "出品",
        "Back": "exhibit;display",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1374
    },
    {
        "Front": "出演",
        "Back": "performance;stage appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1375
    },
    {
        "Front": "出題",
        "Back": "proposing a question",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1376
    },
    {
        "Front": "出動",
        "Back": "sailing;marching;going out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1377
    },
    {
        "Front": "主導",
        "Back": "main leadership",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1378
    },
    {
        "Front": "主任",
        "Back": "person in charge;responsible official",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1379
    },
    {
        "Front": "首脳",
        "Back": "head;brains",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1380
    },
    {
        "Front": "守備",
        "Back": "defense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1381
    },
    {
        "Front": "手法",
        "Back": "technique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1382
    },
    {
        "Front": "私有",
        "Back": "private ownership",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1383
    },
    {
        "Front": "諸",
        "Back": "various;many;several",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1384
    },
    {
        "Front": "背負う",
        "Back": "to be burdened with;to carry on back or shoulder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1385
    },
    {
        "Front": "象",
        "Back": "phenomenon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1386
    },
    {
        "Front": "症",
        "Back": "illness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1387
    },
    {
        "Front": "傷",
        "Back": "wound;injury;hurt;cut;gash;bruise;scratch;scar;weak point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1388
    },
    {
        "Front": "商",
        "Back": "quotient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1389
    },
    {
        "Front": "消去",
        "Back": "elimination;erasing;dying out;melting away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1390
    },
    {
        "Front": "衝撃",
        "Back": "shock;crash;impact;ballistic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1391
    },
    {
        "Front": "証言",
        "Back": "evidence;testimony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1392
    },
    {
        "Front": "証拠",
        "Back": "evidence;proof",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1393
    },
    {
        "Front": "消耗",
        "Back": "exhaustion;consumption",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1394
    },
    {
        "Front": "照合",
        "Back": "collation;comparison",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1395
    },
    {
        "Front": "詳細",
        "Back": "detail;particulars",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1396
    },
    {
        "Front": "昇進",
        "Back": "promotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1397
    },
    {
        "Front": "少数",
        "Back": "minority;few",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1398
    },
    {
        "Front": "称する",
        "Back": "to pretend;to take the name of;to feign;to purport",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1399
    },
    {
        "Front": "消息",
        "Back": "news;letter;circumstances",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1400
    },
    {
        "Front": "承諾",
        "Back": "consent;acquiescence;agreement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1401
    },
    {
        "Front": "象徴",
        "Back": "symbol",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1402
    },
    {
        "Front": "小児科",
        "Back": "pediatrics",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1403
    },
    {
        "Front": "証人",
        "Back": "witness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1404
    },
    {
        "Front": "照明",
        "Back": "illumination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1405
    },
    {
        "Front": "勝利",
        "Back": "victory;triumph;conquest;success;win",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1406
    },
    {
        "Front": "奨励",
        "Back": "encouragement;promotion;message;address",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1407
    },
    {
        "Front": "職員",
        "Back": "staff member;personnel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1408
    },
    {
        "Front": "植民地",
        "Back": "colony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1409
    },
    {
        "Front": "職務",
        "Back": "professional duties",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1410
    },
    {
        "Front": "諸君",
        "Back": "Gentlemen!;Ladies!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1411
    },
    {
        "Front": "所在",
        "Back": "whereabouts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1412
    },
    {
        "Front": "所々",
        "Back": "here and there;some parts (of something)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1413
    },
    {
        "Front": "所持",
        "Back": "possession;owning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1414
    },
    {
        "Front": "所属",
        "Back": "attached to;belong to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1415
    },
    {
        "Front": "処置",
        "Back": "treatment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1416
    },
    {
        "Front": "しょっちゅう",
        "Back": "always;constantly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "所定",
        "Back": "fixed;prescribed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1417
    },
    {
        "Front": "所得",
        "Back": "income;earnings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1418
    },
    {
        "Front": "初版",
        "Back": "first edition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1419
    },
    {
        "Front": "処罰",
        "Back": "punishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1420
    },
    {
        "Front": "書評",
        "Back": "book review",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1421
    },
    {
        "Front": "処分",
        "Back": "disposal;dealing;punishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1422
    },
    {
        "Front": "庶民",
        "Back": "masses;common people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1423
    },
    {
        "Front": "庶務",
        "Back": "general affairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1424
    },
    {
        "Front": "私用",
        "Back": "personal use;private business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1425
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕様",
        "Back": "way;method;resource;remedy;(technical) specification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1426
    },
    {
        "Front": "使用人",
        "Back": "employee;servant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1427
    },
    {
        "Front": "調べ",
        "Back": "preparation;investigation;inspection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1428
    },
    {
        "Front": "知り合い",
        "Back": "acquaintance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1429
    },
    {
        "Front": "退く",
        "Back": "to retreat;to recede;to withdraw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1430
    },
    {
        "Front": "退ける",
        "Back": "to repel;to drive away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1431
    },
    {
        "Front": "記す",
        "Back": "to note;to write down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1432
    },
    {
        "Front": "指令",
        "Back": "orders;instructions;directive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1433
    },
    {
        "Front": "代",
        "Back": "price;materials;substitution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1434
    },
    {
        "Front": "皺",
        "Back": "wrinkles;creases",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1435
    },
    {
        "Front": "新",
        "Back": "new",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1436
    },
    {
        "Front": "進化",
        "Back": "evolution;progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1437
    },
    {
        "Front": "殿",
        "Back": "rear;rear unit guard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1438
    },
    {
        "Front": "審議",
        "Back": "deliberation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1439
    },
    {
        "Front": "進行",
        "Back": "advance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1440
    },
    {
        "Front": "新興",
        "Back": "rising;developing;emergent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1441
    },
    {
        "Front": "振興",
        "Back": "promotion;encouragement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1442
    },
    {
        "Front": "申告",
        "Back": "report;statement;filing a return;notification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1443
    },
    {
        "Front": "新婚",
        "Back": "newly-wed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1444
    },
    {
        "Front": "審査",
        "Back": "judging;inspection;examination;investigation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1445
    },
    {
        "Front": "紳士",
        "Back": "gentleman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1446
    },
    {
        "Front": "進出",
        "Back": "advance;step forward",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1447
    },
    {
        "Front": "信者",
        "Back": "believer;adherent;devotee;Christian",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1448
    },
    {
        "Front": "真珠",
        "Back": "pearl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1449
    },
    {
        "Front": "心中",
        "Back": "double suicide;lovers suicide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1450
    },
    {
        "Front": "心情",
        "Back": "mentality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1451
    },
    {
        "Front": "新人",
        "Back": "new face;newcomer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1452
    },
    {
        "Front": "神聖",
        "Back": "holiness;sacredness;dignity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1453
    },
    {
        "Front": "親善",
        "Back": "friendship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1454
    },
    {
        "Front": "真相",
        "Back": "truth;real situation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1455
    },
    {
        "Front": "新築",
        "Back": "new building;new construction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1456
    },
    {
        "Front": "進呈",
        "Back": "presentation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1457
    },
    {
        "Front": "進展",
        "Back": "progress;development",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1458
    },
    {
        "Front": "神殿",
        "Back": "temple;sacred place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1459
    },
    {
        "Front": "進度",
        "Back": "progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1460
    },
    {
        "Front": "振動",
        "Back": "oscillation;vibration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1461
    },
    {
        "Front": "新入生",
        "Back": "freshman;first-year student",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1462
    },
    {
        "Front": "信任",
        "Back": "trust;confidence;credence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1463
    },
    {
        "Front": "審判",
        "Back": "refereeing;trial;judgement;umpire;referee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1464
    },
    {
        "Front": "神秘",
        "Back": "mystery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1465
    },
    {
        "Front": "辛抱",
        "Back": "patience;endurance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1466
    },
    {
        "Front": "真理",
        "Back": "truth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1467
    },
    {
        "Front": "侵略",
        "Back": "aggression;invasion;raid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1468
    },
    {
        "Front": "診療",
        "Back": "medical examination and treatment;diagnosis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1469
    },
    {
        "Front": "進路",
        "Back": "course;route",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1470
    },
    {
        "Front": "自覚",
        "Back": "self-conscious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1471
    },
    {
        "Front": "地方",
        "Back": "area;locality;district;region;the coast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1472
    },
    {
        "Front": "自我",
        "Back": "self;the ego",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1473
    },
    {
        "Front": "磁気",
        "Back": "magnetism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1474
    },
    {
        "Front": "磁器",
        "Back": "porcelain;china",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1475
    },
    {
        "Front": "事業",
        "Back": "project;enterprise;business;industry;operations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1476
    },
    {
        "Front": "地形",
        "Back": "terrain;geographical features;topography",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1477
    },
    {
        "Front": "軸",
        "Back": "axis;stem;shaft;axle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1478
    },
    {
        "Front": "自己",
        "Back": "self;oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1479
    },
    {
        "Front": "事項",
        "Back": "matter;item;facts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1480
    },
    {
        "Front": "時刻表",
        "Back": "table;diagram;chart;timetable;schedule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1481
    },
    {
        "Front": "地獄",
        "Back": "hell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1482
    },
    {
        "Front": "時差",
        "Back": "time difference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1483
    },
    {
        "Front": "自在",
        "Back": "freely;at will",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1484
    },
    {
        "Front": "自主",
        "Back": "independence;autonomy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1485
    },
    {
        "Front": "自首",
        "Back": "surrender;give oneself up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1486
    },
    {
        "Front": "辞職",
        "Back": "resignation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1487
    },
    {
        "Front": "自信",
        "Back": "self-confidence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1488
    },
    {
        "Front": "事前",
        "Back": "prior;beforehand;in advance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1489
    },
    {
        "Front": "自尊心",
        "Back": "self-respect;conceit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1490
    },
    {
        "Front": "持続",
        "Back": "continuation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1491
    },
    {
        "Front": "字体",
        "Back": "type;font;lettering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1492
    },
    {
        "Front": "辞退",
        "Back": "refusal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1493
    },
    {
        "Front": "じっくり",
        "Back": "deliberately;carefully",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "実質",
        "Back": "substance;essence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1494
    },
    {
        "Front": "実践",
        "Back": "practice;put into practice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1495
    },
    {
        "Front": "実態",
        "Back": "truth;fact",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1496
    },
    {
        "Front": "実費",
        "Back": "actual expense;cost price",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1497
    },
    {
        "Front": "十分",
        "Back": "10 minutes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1498
    },
    {
        "Front": "実",
        "Back": "truth;reality;sincerity;fidelity;kindness;faith;substance;essence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1499
    },
    {
        "Front": "実業家",
        "Back": "industrialist;businessman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1500
    },
    {
        "Front": "実情",
        "Back": "real condition;actual circumstances;actual state of affairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1501
    },
    {
        "Front": "自転",
        "Back": "rotation;spin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1502
    },
    {
        "Front": "自動詞",
        "Back": "intransitive verb (no direct obj)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1503
    },
    {
        "Front": "地主",
        "Back": "landlord",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1504
    },
    {
        "Front": "耳鼻科",
        "Back": "otolaryngology",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1505
    },
    {
        "Front": "地元",
        "Back": "local",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1506
    },
    {
        "Front": "弱",
        "Back": "weakness;the weak;little less then",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1507
    },
    {
        "Front": "若干",
        "Back": "some;few;number of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1508
    },
    {
        "Front": "砂利",
        "Back": "gravel;ballast;pebbles",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1509
    },
    {
        "Front": "じゃん拳",
        "Back": "rock-scissors-paper game",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1510
    },
    {
        "Front": "住",
        "Back": "dwelling;living",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1511
    },
    {
        "Front": "従業員",
        "Back": "employee;worker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1512
    },
    {
        "Front": "従事",
        "Back": "engaging;pursuing;following",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1513
    },
    {
        "Front": "充実",
        "Back": "fullness;completion;perfection;substantiality;enrichment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1514
    },
    {
        "Front": "十字路",
        "Back": "crossroads",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1515
    },
    {
        "Front": "絨毯",
        "Back": "carpet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1516
    },
    {
        "Front": "柔軟",
        "Back": "flexible;lithe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1517
    },
    {
        "Front": "重複",
        "Back": "duplication;repetition;overlapping;redundancy;restoration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1518
    },
    {
        "Front": "重宝",
        "Back": "priceless treasure;convenience;usefulness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1519
    },
    {
        "Front": "従来",
        "Back": "up to now;so far;traditional",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1520
    },
    {
        "Front": "塾",
        "Back": "coaching school;lessons",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1521
    },
    {
        "Front": "樹木",
        "Back": "trees and shrubs;arbour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1522
    },
    {
        "Front": "樹立",
        "Back": "establish;create",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1523
    },
    {
        "Front": "準急",
        "Back": "local express (train&nbsp;&nbsp;slower than an express)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1524
    },
    {
        "Front": "準じる",
        "Back": "to follow;to conform;to apply to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1525
    },
    {
        "Front": "準ずる",
        "Back": "to apply correspondingly;to correspond to;to be proportionate to;to conform to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1526
    },
    {
        "Front": "助",
        "Back": "help;rescue;assistant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1527
    },
    {
        "Front": "情",
        "Back": "feelings;emotion;passion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1528
    },
    {
        "Front": "畳",
        "Back": "#NAME?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1529
    },
    {
        "Front": "尉",
        "Back": "jailer;old man;rank;company officer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1530
    },
    {
        "Front": "嬢",
        "Back": "young woman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1531
    },
    {
        "Front": "状",
        "Back": "shape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1532
    },
    {
        "Front": "上位",
        "Back": "superior (rank not class);higher order (e.g. byte);host computer (of connected device)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1533
    },
    {
        "Front": "上演",
        "Back": "performance (e.g. music)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1534
    },
    {
        "Front": "城下",
        "Back": "land near the castle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1535
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗客",
        "Back": "passenger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1536
    },
    {
        "Front": "上空",
        "Back": "sky;the skies;high-altitude sky;upper air",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1537
    },
    {
        "Front": "上司",
        "Back": "superior authorities;boss",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1538
    },
    {
        "Front": "情緒",
        "Back": "emotion;feeling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1539
    },
    {
        "Front": "上昇",
        "Back": "rising;ascending;climbing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1540
    },
    {
        "Front": "情勢",
        "Back": "state of things;condition;situation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1541
    },
    {
        "Front": "情熱",
        "Back": "passion;enthusiasm;zeal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1542
    },
    {
        "Front": "丈夫",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;hero;gentleman;warrior;manly person; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;good health;robustness;strong;solid;durable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1543
    },
    {
        "Front": "譲歩",
        "Back": "concession;conciliation;compromise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1544
    },
    {
        "Front": "条約",
        "Back": "treaty;pact",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1545
    },
    {
        "Front": "上陸",
        "Back": "landing;disembarkation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1546
    },
    {
        "Front": "蒸留",
        "Back": "distillation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1547
    },
    {
        "Front": "除外",
        "Back": "exception;exclusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1548
    },
    {
        "Front": "助言",
        "Back": "advice;suggestion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1549
    },
    {
        "Front": "徐行",
        "Back": "going slowly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1550
    },
    {
        "Front": "女史",
        "Back": "Ms.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1551
    },
    {
        "Front": "助詞",
        "Back": "particle;postposition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1552
    },
    {
        "Front": "助動詞",
        "Back": "auxiliary verb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1553
    },
    {
        "Front": "自立",
        "Back": "independence;self-reliance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1554
    },
    {
        "Front": "人",
        "Back": "man;person;people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1555
    },
    {
        "Front": "人格",
        "Back": "personality;character;individuality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1556
    },
    {
        "Front": "人材",
        "Back": "man of talent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1557
    },
    {
        "Front": "迅速",
        "Back": "quick;fast;rapid;swift;prompt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1558
    },
    {
        "Front": "人体",
        "Back": "human body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1559
    },
    {
        "Front": "人民",
        "Back": "people;public",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1560
    },
    {
        "Front": "人目",
        "Back": "glimpse;public gaze",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1561
    },
    {
        "Front": "水気",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;moisture;dampness;vapor; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;dropsy;edema",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1562
    },
    {
        "Front": "水源",
        "Back": "source of river;fountainhead",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1563
    },
    {
        "Front": "推進",
        "Back": "propulsion;driving force",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1564
    },
    {
        "Front": "水洗",
        "Back": "flushing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1565
    },
    {
        "Front": "吹奏",
        "Back": "playing wind instruments",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1566
    },
    {
        "Front": "推測",
        "Back": "guess;conjecture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1567
    },
    {
        "Front": "水田",
        "Back": "(water-filled) paddy field",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1568
    },
    {
        "Front": "推理",
        "Back": "reasoning;inference;mystery or detective genre (movie&nbsp;&nbsp;novel&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1569
    },
    {
        "Front": "数詞",
        "Back": "numeral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1570
    },
    {
        "Front": "崇拝",
        "Back": "worship;adoration;admiration;cult",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1571
    },
    {
        "Front": "据え付ける",
        "Back": "to install;to equip;to mount",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1572
    },
    {
        "Front": "据える",
        "Back": "to set (table);to lay (foundation);to place (gun);to apply (moxa)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1573
    },
    {
        "Front": "清々しい",
        "Back": "fresh;refreshing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1574
    },
    {
        "Front": "過ぎ",
        "Back": "past;after",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1575
    },
    {
        "Front": "救い",
        "Back": "help;aid;relief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1576
    },
    {
        "Front": "掬う",
        "Back": "to scoop;to ladle out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1577
    },
    {
        "Front": "少なくとも",
        "Back": "at least",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1578
    },
    {
        "Front": "直ぐ",
        "Back": "immediately;soon;easily;right (near);honest;upright",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1579
    },
    {
        "Front": "健やか",
        "Back": "vigorous;healthy;sound",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1580
    },
    {
        "Front": "濯ぐ",
        "Back": "to rinse;to wash out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1581
    },
    {
        "Front": "進み",
        "Back": "progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1582
    },
    {
        "Front": "勧め",
        "Back": "recommendation;advice;encouragement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1583
    },
    {
        "Front": "裾",
        "Back": "(trouser) cuff;(skirt) hem;cut edge of a hairdo;foot of mountain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1584
    },
    {
        "Front": "廃れる",
        "Back": "to go out of use;to become obsolete;to die out;to go out of fashion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1585
    },
    {
        "Front": "酸っぱい",
        "Back": "sour;acid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1586
    },
    {
        "Front": "素敵",
        "Back": "lovely;dreamy;beautiful;great;fantastic;superb;cool;capital",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1587
    },
    {
        "Front": "即ち",
        "Back": "that is;namely;i.e.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1588
    },
    {
        "Front": "すばしこい",
        "Back": "nimble;smart;quick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "素早い",
        "Back": "fast;quick;prompt;agile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1589
    },
    {
        "Front": "済ます",
        "Back": "to finish;to get it over with;to settle;to conclude;to pay back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1590
    },
    {
        "Front": "澄ます",
        "Back": "to clear;to make clear;to be unruffled;to look unconcerned;to look demure;look prim;put on airs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1591
    },
    {
        "Front": "済まない",
        "Back": "sorry (phrase)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1592
    },
    {
        "Front": "済みません",
        "Back": "sorry;excuse me",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1593
    },
    {
        "Front": "天皇",
        "Back": "Emperor of Japan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1594
    },
    {
        "Front": "刷り",
        "Back": "printing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1595
    },
    {
        "Front": "剃る",
        "Back": "to shave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1596
    },
    {
        "Front": "擦れ違い",
        "Back": "chance encounter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1597
    },
    {
        "Front": "すれ違う",
        "Back": "to pass by one another;to disagree;to miss each other",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1598
    },
    {
        "Front": "擦れる",
        "Back": "to rub;to chafe;to wear;to become sophisticated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1599
    },
    {
        "Front": "すんなり",
        "Back": "pass with no objection;slim;slender",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "図々しい",
        "Back": "impudent;shameless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1600
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずばり",
        "Back": "decisively;decidedly;once and for all;unreservedly;frankly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずぶ濡れ",
        "Back": "soaked;dripping wet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1601
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずらっと",
        "Back": "in a line;in a row",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずるずる",
        "Back": "sound or act of dragging;loose;inconclusive but unwanted situation;trailingly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずれ",
        "Back": "gap;slippage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずれる",
        "Back": "to slide;to slip off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "制",
        "Back": "system;organization;imperial command;laws;regulation;control;government;suppression;restraint;holdin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1602
    },
    {
        "Front": "製",
        "Back": "-made;make",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1603
    },
    {
        "Front": "生育",
        "Back": "growth;development;breeding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1604
    },
    {
        "Front": "成果",
        "Back": "results;fruits",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1605
    },
    {
        "Front": "正解",
        "Back": "correct;right;correct interpretation (answer&nbsp;&nbsp;solution)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1606
    },
    {
        "Front": "正規",
        "Back": "regular;legal;formal;established;legitimate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1607
    },
    {
        "Front": "正義",
        "Back": "justice;right;righteousness;correct meaning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1608
    },
    {
        "Front": "生計",
        "Back": "livelihood;living",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1609
    },
    {
        "Front": "政権",
        "Back": "administration;political power",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1610
    },
    {
        "Front": "精巧",
        "Back": "elaborate;delicate;exquisite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1611
    },
    {
        "Front": "制裁",
        "Back": "restraint;sanctions;punishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1612
    },
    {
        "Front": "政策",
        "Back": "political measures;policy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1613
    },
    {
        "Front": "清算",
        "Back": "liquidation;settlement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1614
    },
    {
        "Front": "星座",
        "Back": "constellation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1615
    },
    {
        "Front": "生死",
        "Back": "life and death",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1616
    },
    {
        "Front": "静止",
        "Back": "stillness;repose;standing still",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1617
    },
    {
        "Front": "青春",
        "Back": "youth;springtime of life;adolescent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1618
    },
    {
        "Front": "聖書",
        "Back": "Bible;scriptures",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1619
    },
    {
        "Front": "誠実",
        "Back": "sincere;honest;faithful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1620
    },
    {
        "Front": "成熟",
        "Back": "maturity;ripeness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1621
    },
    {
        "Front": "清純",
        "Back": "purity;innocence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1622
    },
    {
        "Front": "正常",
        "Back": "normalcy;normality;normal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1623
    },
    {
        "Front": "制する",
        "Back": "to control;to command;to get the better of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1624
    },
    {
        "Front": "整然",
        "Back": "orderly;regular;well-organized;trim;accurate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1625
    },
    {
        "Front": "盛装",
        "Back": "be dressed up;wear rich clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1626
    },
    {
        "Front": "盛大",
        "Back": "grand;prosperous;magnificent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1627
    },
    {
        "Front": "清濁",
        "Back": "good and evil;purity and impurity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1628
    },
    {
        "Front": "制定",
        "Back": "enactment;establishment;creation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1629
    },
    {
        "Front": "静的",
        "Back": "static",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1630
    },
    {
        "Front": "製鉄",
        "Back": "iron manufacture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1631
    },
    {
        "Front": "晴天",
        "Back": "fine weather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1632
    },
    {
        "Front": "正当",
        "Back": "just;justifiable;right;due;proper;equitable;reasonable;legitimate;lawful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1633
    },
    {
        "Front": "成年",
        "Back": "majority;adult age",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1634
    },
    {
        "Front": "制服",
        "Back": "uniform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1635
    },
    {
        "Front": "征服",
        "Back": "conquest;subjugation;overcoming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1636
    },
    {
        "Front": "製法",
        "Back": "manufacturing method;recipe;formula",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1637
    },
    {
        "Front": "精密",
        "Back": "precise;exact;detailed;minute;close",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1638
    },
    {
        "Front": "声明",
        "Back": "declaration;statement;proclamation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1639
    },
    {
        "Front": "姓名",
        "Back": "full name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1640
    },
    {
        "Front": "制約",
        "Back": "limitation;restriction;condition;constraints",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1641
    },
    {
        "Front": "生理",
        "Back": "physiology;menses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1642
    },
    {
        "Front": "勢力",
        "Back": "influence;power;might;strength;potency;force;energy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1643
    },
    {
        "Front": "整列",
        "Back": "stand in a row;form a line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1644
    },
    {
        "Front": "急かす",
        "Back": "to hurry;to urge on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1645
    },
    {
        "Front": "伜",
        "Back": "son;my son",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1646
    },
    {
        "Front": "責務",
        "Back": "duty;obligation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1647
    },
    {
        "Front": "世辞",
        "Back": "flattery;compliment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1648
    },
    {
        "Front": "世帯",
        "Back": "household",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1649
    },
    {
        "Front": "世代",
        "Back": "generation;the world;the age",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1650
    },
    {
        "Front": "切開",
        "Back": "clearing (land);opening up;cutting through",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1651
    },
    {
        "Front": "接触",
        "Back": "touch;contact",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1652
    },
    {
        "Front": "設置",
        "Back": "establishment;institution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1653
    },
    {
        "Front": "折衷",
        "Back": "compromise;cross;blending;eclecticism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1654
    },
    {
        "Front": "設定",
        "Back": "establishment;creation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1655
    },
    {
        "Front": "説得",
        "Back": "persuasion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1656
    },
    {
        "Front": "節",
        "Back": "node;section;occasion;time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1657
    },
    {
        "Front": "切実",
        "Back": "compelling;serious;severe;acute;earnest;pressing;urgent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1658
    },
    {
        "Front": "接続詞",
        "Back": "conjunction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1659
    },
    {
        "Front": "切ない",
        "Back": "painful;trying;oppressive;suffocating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1660
    },
    {
        "Front": "設立",
        "Back": "establishment;foundation;institution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1661
    },
    {
        "Front": "攻め",
        "Back": "attack;offence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1662
    },
    {
        "Front": "世論",
        "Back": "public opinion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1663
    },
    {
        "Front": "仙",
        "Back": "hermit;wizard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1664
    },
    {
        "Front": "前",
        "Back": "before",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1665
    },
    {
        "Front": "繊維",
        "Back": "fibre;fiber;textile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1666
    },
    {
        "Front": "選挙",
        "Back": "election",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1667
    },
    {
        "Front": "宣教",
        "Back": "religious mission",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1668
    },
    {
        "Front": "宣言",
        "Back": "declaration;proclamation;announcement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1669
    },
    {
        "Front": "先行",
        "Back": "preceding;going first",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1670
    },
    {
        "Front": "選考",
        "Back": "selection;screening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1671
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦災",
        "Back": "war damage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1672
    },
    {
        "Front": "専修",
        "Back": "specialization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1673
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦術",
        "Back": "tactics",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1674
    },
    {
        "Front": "潜水",
        "Back": "diving",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1675
    },
    {
        "Front": "先先月",
        "Back": "month before last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1676
    },
    {
        "Front": "先先週",
        "Back": "week before last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1677
    },
    {
        "Front": "先代",
        "Back": "family predecessor;previous age;previous generation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1678
    },
    {
        "Front": "先だって",
        "Back": "recently;the other day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1679
    },
    {
        "Front": "先着",
        "Back": "first arrival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1680
    },
    {
        "Front": "先天的",
        "Back": "a priori;inborn;innate;inherent;congenital;hereditary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1681
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦闘",
        "Back": "battle;fight;combat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1682
    },
    {
        "Front": "潜入",
        "Back": "infiltration;sneaking in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1683
    },
    {
        "Front": "船舶",
        "Back": "ship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1684
    },
    {
        "Front": "専用",
        "Back": "exclusive use;personal use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1685
    },
    {
        "Front": "占領",
        "Back": "occupation;capture;possession;have a room to oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1686
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦力",
        "Back": "war potential",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1687
    },
    {
        "Front": "税務署",
        "Back": "tax office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1688
    },
    {
        "Front": "是正",
        "Back": "correction;revision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1689
    },
    {
        "Front": "絶版",
        "Back": "out of print",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1690
    },
    {
        "Front": "絶望",
        "Back": "despair;hopelessness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1691
    },
    {
        "Front": "是非とも",
        "Back": "by all means (with sense of not taking no for an answer)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1692
    },
    {
        "Front": "膳",
        "Back": "(small) table;tray;meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1693
    },
    {
        "Front": "禅",
        "Back": "Zen (Buddhism)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1694
    },
    {
        "Front": "全快",
        "Back": "complete recovery of health",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1695
    },
    {
        "Front": "全盛",
        "Back": "height of prosperity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1696
    },
    {
        "Front": "前提",
        "Back": "preamble;premise;reason;prerequisite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1697
    },
    {
        "Front": "前途",
        "Back": "future prospects;outlook;the journey ahead",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1698
    },
    {
        "Front": "全滅",
        "Back": "annihilation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1699
    },
    {
        "Front": "善良",
        "Back": "goodness;excellence;virtue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1700
    },
    {
        "Front": "前例",
        "Back": "precedent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1701
    },
    {
        "Front": "僧",
        "Back": "monk;priest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1702
    },
    {
        "Front": "沿う",
        "Back": "to run along;to follow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1703
    },
    {
        "Front": "添う",
        "Back": "to accompany;to become married;to comply with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1704
    },
    {
        "Front": "総",
        "Back": "whole;all;general;gross",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1705
    },
    {
        "Front": "相応",
        "Back": "suitability;fitness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1706
    },
    {
        "Front": "総会",
        "Back": "general meeting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1707
    },
    {
        "Front": "創刊",
        "Back": "launching (e.g. newspaper);first issue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1708
    },
    {
        "Front": "送金",
        "Back": "remittance;sending money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1709
    },
    {
        "Front": "走行",
        "Back": "running a wheeled vehicle (e.g. car);traveling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1710
    },
    {
        "Front": "総合",
        "Back": "synthesis;coordination;putting together;integration;composite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1711
    },
    {
        "Front": "捜査",
        "Back": "search (esp. in criminal investigations);investigation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1712
    },
    {
        "Front": "捜索",
        "Back": "search (esp. for someone or something missing);investigation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1713
    },
    {
        "Front": "然うして",
        "Back": "and;like that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1714
    },
    {
        "Front": "装飾",
        "Back": "ornament",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1715
    },
    {
        "Front": "操縦",
        "Back": "management;handling;control;manipulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1716
    },
    {
        "Front": "創造",
        "Back": "creation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1717
    },
    {
        "Front": "壮大",
        "Back": "magnificent;grand;majestic;splendid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1718
    },
    {
        "Front": "騒動",
        "Back": "strife;riot;rebellion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1719
    },
    {
        "Front": "遭難",
        "Back": "disaster;shipwreck;accident",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1720
    },
    {
        "Front": "相場",
        "Back": "market price;speculation;estimation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1721
    },
    {
        "Front": "装備",
        "Back": "equipment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1722
    },
    {
        "Front": "創立",
        "Back": "establishment;founding;organization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1723
    },
    {
        "Front": "添える",
        "Back": "to add to;to attach;to append;to accompany;to garnish;to imitate;to annex",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1724
    },
    {
        "Front": "即座に",
        "Back": "immediately;right away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1725
    },
    {
        "Front": "促進",
        "Back": "promotion;acceleration;encouragement;facilitation;spurring on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1726
    },
    {
        "Front": "即する",
        "Back": "to conform to;to agree with;to be adapted to;to be based on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1727
    },
    {
        "Front": "束縛",
        "Back": "restraint;shackles;restriction;confinement;binding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1728
    },
    {
        "Front": "側面",
        "Back": "side;flank;sidelight;lateral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1729
    },
    {
        "Front": "其処",
        "Back": "that place;there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1730
    },
    {
        "Front": "其処で",
        "Back": "so (conj);accordingly;now;then;thereupon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1731
    },
    {
        "Front": "損なう",
        "Back": "to harm;to hurt;to injure;to damage;to fail in doing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1732
    },
    {
        "Front": "其処ら",
        "Back": "everywhere;somewhere;approximately;that area;around there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1733
    },
    {
        "Front": "素材",
        "Back": "raw materials;subject matter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1734
    },
    {
        "Front": "阻止",
        "Back": "obstruction;check;hindrance;prevention;interdiction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1735
    },
    {
        "Front": "然して",
        "Back": "and",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1736
    },
    {
        "Front": "訴訟",
        "Back": "litigation;lawsuit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1737
    },
    {
        "Front": "育ち",
        "Back": "breeding;growth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1738
    },
    {
        "Front": "措置",
        "Back": "measure;step",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1739
    },
    {
        "Front": "其方",
        "Back": "over there;the other",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1740
    },
    {
        "Front": "素っ気ない",
        "Back": "cold;short;curt;blunt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1741
    },
    {
        "Front": "率直",
        "Back": "frankness;candour;openheartedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1742
    },
    {
        "Front": "外方",
        "Back": "look (or turn) the other way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1743
    },
    {
        "Front": "備え付ける",
        "Back": "to provide;to furnish;to equip;to install",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1744
    },
    {
        "Front": "備わる",
        "Back": "to be furnished with;to be endowed with;to possess;to be among;to be one of;to be possessed of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1745
    },
    {
        "Front": "その上",
        "Back": "in addition;furthermore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1746
    },
    {
        "Front": "その内",
        "Back": "eventually;sooner or later;of the previously mentioned",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1747
    },
    {
        "Front": "その為",
        "Back": "hence;for that reason",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1748
    },
    {
        "Front": "その外",
        "Back": "besides;in addition;the rest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1749
    },
    {
        "Front": "其の儘",
        "Back": "without change;as it is (i.e. now)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1750
    },
    {
        "Front": "聳える",
        "Back": "to rise;to tower;to soar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1751
    },
    {
        "Front": "素朴",
        "Back": "simplicity;artlessness;naivete",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1752
    },
    {
        "Front": "染まる",
        "Back": "to dye",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1753
    },
    {
        "Front": "背く",
        "Back": "to run counter to;to go against;to disobey;to infringe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1754
    },
    {
        "Front": "染める",
        "Back": "to dye;to colour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1755
    },
    {
        "Front": "逸らす",
        "Back": "to turn away;to avert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1756
    },
    {
        "Front": "反り",
        "Back": "warp;curvature;curve;arch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1757
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れ",
        "Back": "it;that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1758
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れから",
        "Back": "and then;after that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1759
    },
    {
        "Front": "各々",
        "Back": "each;every;either;respectively;severally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1760
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れで",
        "Back": "and (conj);thereupon;because of that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1761
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れでは",
        "Back": "in that situation;well then ...",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1762
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れでも",
        "Back": "but (still);and yet;nevertheless;even so;notwithstanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1763
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れ共",
        "Back": "or;or else",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1764
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れに",
        "Back": "besides;moreover",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1765
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れ程",
        "Back": "to that degree;extent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1766
    },
    {
        "Front": "其れ故",
        "Back": "therefore;for that reason;so",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1767
    },
    {
        "Front": "揃い",
        "Back": "set;suit;uniform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1768
    },
    {
        "Front": "徐々",
        "Back": "gradually;steadily;quietly;slowly;soon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1769
    },
    {
        "Front": "損失",
        "Back": "loss",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1770
    },
    {
        "Front": "存続",
        "Back": "duration;continuance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1771
    },
    {
        "Front": "沿い",
        "Back": "along",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1772
    },
    {
        "Front": "像",
        "Back": "statue;image;figure;picture;portrait",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1773
    },
    {
        "Front": "増強",
        "Back": "augment;reinforce;increase",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1774
    },
    {
        "Front": "蔵相",
        "Back": "Minister of Finance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1775
    },
    {
        "Front": "増進",
        "Back": "promoting;increase;advance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1776
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぞんざい",
        "Back": "rude;careless;slovenly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "他意",
        "Back": "ill will;malice;another intention;secret purpose;ulterior motive;fickleness;double-mindedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1777
    },
    {
        "Front": "退化",
        "Back": "degeneration;retrogression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1779
    },
    {
        "Front": "対応",
        "Back": "interaction;correspondence;coping with;dealing with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1778
    },
    {
        "Front": "体格",
        "Back": "physique;constitution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1780
    },
    {
        "Front": "大概",
        "Back": "in general;mainly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1781
    },
    {
        "Front": "退学",
        "Back": "dropping out of school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1782
    },
    {
        "Front": "大金",
        "Back": "great cost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1783
    },
    {
        "Front": "待遇",
        "Back": "treatment;reception",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1784
    },
    {
        "Front": "対決",
        "Back": "confrontation;showdown",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1785
    },
    {
        "Front": "体験",
        "Back": "personal experience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1786
    },
    {
        "Front": "対抗",
        "Back": "opposition;antagonism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1787
    },
    {
        "Front": "対して",
        "Back": "for;in regard to;per",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1788
    },
    {
        "Front": "大衆",
        "Back": "general public",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1789
    },
    {
        "Front": "退職",
        "Back": "retirement (from office)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1791
    },
    {
        "Front": "対処",
        "Back": "deal with;cope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1790
    },
    {
        "Front": "退治",
        "Back": "extermination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1792
    },
    {
        "Front": "態勢",
        "Back": "attitude;conditions;preparations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1793
    },
    {
        "Front": "対談",
        "Back": "talk;dialogue;conversation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1794
    },
    {
        "Front": "対等",
        "Back": "equivalent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1795
    },
    {
        "Front": "滞納",
        "Back": "non-payment;default",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1796
    },
    {
        "Front": "対比",
        "Back": "contrast;comparison",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1797
    },
    {
        "Front": "大部",
        "Back": "most (e.g. most part);greater;fairly;a good deal;much",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1798
    },
    {
        "Front": "対辺",
        "Back": "(geometrical) opposite side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1799
    },
    {
        "Front": "待望",
        "Back": "expectant waiting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1800
    },
    {
        "Front": "怠慢",
        "Back": "negligence;procrastination;carelessness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1801
    },
    {
        "Front": "対面",
        "Back": "interview;meeting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1802
    },
    {
        "Front": "対立",
        "Back": "confrontation;opposition;antagonism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1803
    },
    {
        "Front": "体力",
        "Back": "physical strength",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1804
    },
    {
        "Front": "対話",
        "Back": "interactive;interaction;conversation;dialogue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1805
    },
    {
        "Front": "耐える",
        "Back": "to bear;to endure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1806
    },
    {
        "Front": "絶える",
        "Back": "to die out;to peter out;to become extinct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1807
    },
    {
        "Front": "高",
        "Back": "quantity;amount;volume;number;amount of money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1808
    },
    {
        "Front": "高まる",
        "Back": "to rise;to swell;to be promoted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1809
    },
    {
        "Front": "焚火",
        "Back": "(open) fire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1810
    },
    {
        "Front": "沢山",
        "Back": "many;a lot;much",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1811
    },
    {
        "Front": "逞しい",
        "Back": "burly;strong;sturdy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1812
    },
    {
        "Front": "巧み",
        "Back": "skill;cleverness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1813
    },
    {
        "Front": "類",
        "Back": "a kind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1814
    },
    {
        "Front": "丈",
        "Back": "height;stature;length;measure;all (one has)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1815
    },
    {
        "Front": "足し算",
        "Back": "addition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1816
    },
    {
        "Front": "多数決",
        "Back": "majority rule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1817
    },
    {
        "Front": "助け",
        "Back": "assistance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1818
    },
    {
        "Front": "携わる",
        "Back": "to participate;to take part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1819
    },
    {
        "Front": "漂う",
        "Back": "to drift about;to float;to hang in air",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1820
    },
    {
        "Front": "立方",
        "Back": "dancing (geisha)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1821
    },
    {
        "Front": "忽ち",
        "Back": "at once;in a moment;suddenly;all at once",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1822
    },
    {
        "Front": "立ち寄る",
        "Back": "to stop by;to drop in for a short visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1823
    },
    {
        "Front": "達者",
        "Back": "skillful;in good health",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1824
    },
    {
        "Front": "達成",
        "Back": "achievement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1825
    },
    {
        "Front": "たった",
        "Back": "only;merely;but;no more than",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "尊い",
        "Back": "precious;valuable;priceless;noble;exalted;sacred",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1826
    },
    {
        "Front": "貴い",
        "Back": "precious;valuable;priceless;noble;exalted;sacred",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1827
    },
    {
        "Front": "尊ぶ",
        "Back": "to value;to prize;to esteem",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1828
    },
    {
        "Front": "絶つ",
        "Back": "to sever;to cut off;to suppress;to abstain (from)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1829
    },
    {
        "Front": "盾",
        "Back": "shield;buckler;escutcheon;pretext",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1830
    },
    {
        "Front": "建前",
        "Back": "face;official stance;public position or attitude (as opposed to private thoughts)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1831
    },
    {
        "Front": "奉る",
        "Back": "to offer;to present;to revere;to do respectfully",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1832
    },
    {
        "Front": "例え",
        "Back": "example;even if;if;though;although",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1834
    },
    {
        "Front": "仮令",
        "Back": "example;even if;if;though;although",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1833
    },
    {
        "Front": "他動詞",
        "Back": "transitive verb (direct obj)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1835
    },
    {
        "Front": "辿り着く",
        "Back": "to grope along to;to struggle on to;to arrive somewhere after a struggle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1836
    },
    {
        "Front": "辿る",
        "Back": "to follow (road);to pursue (course);to follow up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1837
    },
    {
        "Front": "掌",
        "Back": "the palm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1838
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽しむ",
        "Back": "to enjoy oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1839
    },
    {
        "Front": "頼み",
        "Back": "request;favor;reliance;dependence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1840
    },
    {
        "Front": "煙草",
        "Back": "(pt:) (n) (uk) tobacco (pt: tabaco);cigarettes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1841
    },
    {
        "Front": "度々",
        "Back": "often;repeatedly;frequently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1842
    },
    {
        "Front": "他方",
        "Back": "another side;different direction;(on) the other hand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1843
    },
    {
        "Front": "多忙",
        "Back": "busy;pressure of work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1844
    },
    {
        "Front": "給う",
        "Back": "to receive;to grant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1845
    },
    {
        "Front": "偶に",
        "Back": "occasionally;once in a while",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1846
    },
    {
        "Front": "堪らない",
        "Back": "intolerable;unbearable;unendurable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1847
    },
    {
        "Front": "溜まり",
        "Back": "collected things;gathering place;arrears",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1848
    },
    {
        "Front": "賜る",
        "Back": "to grant;to bestow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1849
    },
    {
        "Front": "例",
        "Back": "instance;example;case;precedent;experience;custom;usage;parallel;illustration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1850
    },
    {
        "Front": "躊躇う",
        "Back": "to hesitate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1851
    },
    {
        "Front": "保つ",
        "Back": "to keep;to preserve;to hold;to retain;to maintain;to support;to sustain;to last;to endure;to keep we",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1852
    },
    {
        "Front": "容易い",
        "Back": "easy;simple;light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1853
    },
    {
        "Front": "多様",
        "Back": "diversity;variety",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1854
    },
    {
        "Front": "弛み",
        "Back": "slack;slackening;dullness;letdown",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1855
    },
    {
        "Front": "弛む",
        "Back": "to slacken;to loosen;to relax",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1856
    },
    {
        "Front": "誰",
        "Back": "adjectival suffix for a person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1857
    },
    {
        "Front": "垂れる",
        "Back": "to hang;to droop;to drop;to lower;to pull down;to dangle;to sag;to drip;to ooze;to trickle;to leave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1858
    },
    {
        "Front": "歎",
        "Back": "grief;sigh;lamentation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1859
    },
    {
        "Front": "反",
        "Back": "roll of cloth (c. 10 yds.);.245 acres;300 tsubo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1860
    },
    {
        "Front": "単一",
        "Back": "single;simple;sole;individual;unitory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1861
    },
    {
        "Front": "短歌",
        "Back": "tanka;31-syllable Japanese poem",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1862
    },
    {
        "Front": "担架",
        "Back": "stretcher;litter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1863
    },
    {
        "Front": "短気",
        "Back": "quick temper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1864
    },
    {
        "Front": "探検",
        "Back": "exploration;expedition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1865
    },
    {
        "Front": "短縮",
        "Back": "shortening;abbreviation;reduction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1866
    },
    {
        "Front": "箪笥",
        "Back": "chest of drawers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1867
    },
    {
        "Front": "炭素",
        "Back": "carbon (C)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1868
    },
    {
        "Front": "短大",
        "Back": "junior college",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1869
    },
    {
        "Front": "単調",
        "Back": "monotony;monotone;dullness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1870
    },
    {
        "Front": "単独",
        "Back": "sole;independence;single;solo (flight)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1871
    },
    {
        "Front": "短波",
        "Back": "short wave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1872
    },
    {
        "Front": "蛋白質",
        "Back": "protein",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1873
    },
    {
        "Front": "第",
        "Back": "ordinal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1874
    },
    {
        "Front": "第一",
        "Back": "first;foremost;# 1",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1875
    },
    {
        "Front": "大胆",
        "Back": "bold;daring;audacious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1876
    },
    {
        "Front": "台無し",
        "Back": "mess;spoiled;(come to) nothing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1877
    },
    {
        "Front": "大便",
        "Back": "feces;excrement;shit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1878
    },
    {
        "Front": "代弁",
        "Back": "pay by proxy;act for another;speak for another",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1879
    },
    {
        "Front": "台本",
        "Back": "libretto;scenario",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1880
    },
    {
        "Front": "代用",
        "Back": "substitution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1881
    },
    {
        "Front": "打開",
        "Back": "break in the deadlock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1882
    },
    {
        "Front": "妥協",
        "Back": "compromise;giving in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1883
    },
    {
        "Front": "妥結",
        "Back": "agreement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1884
    },
    {
        "Front": "打撃",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;blow;shock;strike;damage; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;batting (baseball)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1885
    },
    {
        "Front": "駄作",
        "Back": "poor work;rubbish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1886
    },
    {
        "Front": "脱出",
        "Back": "escape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1887
    },
    {
        "Front": "脱する",
        "Back": "to escape from;to get out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1888
    },
    {
        "Front": "脱退",
        "Back": "secession",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1889
    },
    {
        "Front": "だぶだぶ",
        "Back": "loose;baggy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "騙す",
        "Back": "to trick;to cheat;to deceive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1890
    },
    {
        "Front": "だらけ",
        "Back": "implying (negatively) that something is full of&nbsp;&nbsp;e.g. mistakes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "怠い",
        "Back": "sluggish;feel heavy;languid;dull",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1891
    },
    {
        "Front": "壇",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;platform;podium;rostrum; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;(arch) mandala",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1892
    },
    {
        "Front": "団結",
        "Back": "unity;union;combination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1893
    },
    {
        "Front": "断言",
        "Back": "declaration;affirmation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1894
    },
    {
        "Front": "断然",
        "Back": "firmly;absolutely;definitely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1895
    },
    {
        "Front": "段々",
        "Back": "gradually;by degrees",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1896
    },
    {
        "Front": "旦那",
        "Back": "master (of house);husband (informal)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1897
    },
    {
        "Front": "断面",
        "Back": "cross section",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1898
    },
    {
        "Front": "弾力",
        "Back": "elasticity;flexibility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1899
    },
    {
        "Front": "治安",
        "Back": "public order",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1900
    },
    {
        "Front": "近付く",
        "Back": "to approach;to get near;to get acquainted with;to get closer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1901
    },
    {
        "Front": "違える",
        "Back": "to change",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1902
    },
    {
        "Front": "契る",
        "Back": "to pledge;to promise;to swear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1903
    },
    {
        "Front": "畜産",
        "Back": "animal husbandry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1904
    },
    {
        "Front": "畜生",
        "Back": "beast;brute;damn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1905
    },
    {
        "Front": "蓄積",
        "Back": "accumulation;accumulate;store",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1906
    },
    {
        "Front": "知性",
        "Back": "intelligence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1907
    },
    {
        "Front": "乳",
        "Back": "milk;breast;loop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1908
    },
    {
        "Front": "父母",
        "Back": "father and mother;parents",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1909
    },
    {
        "Front": "縮まる",
        "Back": "to be shortened;to be contracted;to shrink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1910
    },
    {
        "Front": "窒息",
        "Back": "suffocation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1911
    },
    {
        "Front": "些とも",
        "Back": "not at all (neg. verb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1912
    },
    {
        "Front": "秩序",
        "Back": "order;regularity;system;method",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1913
    },
    {
        "Front": "知的",
        "Back": "intellectual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1914
    },
    {
        "Front": "著",
        "Back": "counter for suits of clothing;arriving at ..",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1915
    },
    {
        "Front": "着",
        "Back": "counter for suits of clothing;arriving at ..",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1916
    },
    {
        "Front": "着手",
        "Back": "embarkation;launch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1917
    },
    {
        "Front": "着色",
        "Back": "colouring;coloring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1918
    },
    {
        "Front": "着席",
        "Back": "sit down;seat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1919
    },
    {
        "Front": "着目",
        "Back": "attention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1920
    },
    {
        "Front": "着陸",
        "Back": "landing;alighting;touch down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1921
    },
    {
        "Front": "着工",
        "Back": "start of (construction) work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1922
    },
    {
        "Front": "茶の間",
        "Back": "living room (Japanese style)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1923
    },
    {
        "Front": "茶の湯",
        "Back": "tea ceremony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1924
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちやほや",
        "Back": "pamper;make a fuss of;spoil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼間",
        "Back": "daytime;during the day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1925
    },
    {
        "Front": "宙返り",
        "Back": "somersault;looping-the-loop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1926
    },
    {
        "Front": "中継",
        "Back": "relay;hook-up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1927
    },
    {
        "Front": "忠告",
        "Back": "advice;warning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1928
    },
    {
        "Front": "中指",
        "Back": "middle finger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1929
    },
    {
        "Front": "中傷",
        "Back": "slander;libel;defamation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1930
    },
    {
        "Front": "忠実",
        "Back": "fidelity;faithfulness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1931
    },
    {
        "Front": "中枢",
        "Back": "centre;pivot;mainstay;nucleus;backbone;central figure;pillar;key man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1932
    },
    {
        "Front": "抽選",
        "Back": "lottery;raffle;drawing (of lots)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1933
    },
    {
        "Front": "中断",
        "Back": "interruption;suspension;break",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1934
    },
    {
        "Front": "中腹",
        "Back": "irritated;offended",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1935
    },
    {
        "Front": "中毒",
        "Back": "poisoning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1936
    },
    {
        "Front": "仲人",
        "Back": "go-between;matchmaker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1937
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼飯",
        "Back": "lunch;midday meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1938
    },
    {
        "Front": "中立",
        "Back": "neutrality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1939
    },
    {
        "Front": "中和",
        "Back": "neutralize;counteract",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1940
    },
    {
        "Front": "腸",
        "Back": "guts;bowels;intestines",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1941
    },
    {
        "Front": "蝶",
        "Back": "butterfly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1942
    },
    {
        "Front": "超",
        "Back": "super-;ultra-;hyper-",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1943
    },
    {
        "Front": "庁",
        "Back": "government office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1944
    },
    {
        "Front": "調印",
        "Back": "signature;sign;sealing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1945
    },
    {
        "Front": "聴覚",
        "Back": "the sense of hearing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1946
    },
    {
        "Front": "長官",
        "Back": "chief;(government) secretary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1947
    },
    {
        "Front": "聴講",
        "Back": "lecture attendance;auditing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1948
    },
    {
        "Front": "徴収",
        "Back": "collection;levy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1949
    },
    {
        "Front": "聴診器",
        "Back": "stethoscope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1950
    },
    {
        "Front": "挑戦",
        "Back": "challenge;defiance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1951
    },
    {
        "Front": "長大",
        "Back": "very long;great length",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1952
    },
    {
        "Front": "調停",
        "Back": "arbitration;conciliation;mediation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1953
    },
    {
        "Front": "恰度",
        "Back": "just;right;exactly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1954
    },
    {
        "Front": "長編",
        "Back": "long (e.g. novel&nbsp;&nbsp;film)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1955
    },
    {
        "Front": "丁目",
        "Back": "district of a town;city block (of irregular size)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1956
    },
    {
        "Front": "調理",
        "Back": "cooking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1957
    },
    {
        "Front": "調和",
        "Back": "harmony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1958
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちょくちょく",
        "Back": "often;frequently;now and then;occasionally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "直面",
        "Back": "confrontation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1959
    },
    {
        "Front": "著書",
        "Back": "literary work;book",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1960
    },
    {
        "Front": "貯蓄",
        "Back": "savings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1961
    },
    {
        "Front": "直感",
        "Back": "intuition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1962
    },
    {
        "Front": "一寸",
        "Back": "(ateji) (adv int) (uk) just a minute;a short time;a while;just a little;somewhat;easily;readily;rath",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1963
    },
    {
        "Front": "著名",
        "Back": "well-known;noted;celebrated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1964
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちらっと",
        "Back": "at a glance;by accident",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "塵取り",
        "Back": "dustpan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1965
    },
    {
        "Front": "治療",
        "Back": "medical treatment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1966
    },
    {
        "Front": "賃金",
        "Back": "wages",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1967
    },
    {
        "Front": "沈殿",
        "Back": "precipitation;settlement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1968
    },
    {
        "Front": "沈没",
        "Back": "sinking;foundering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1969
    },
    {
        "Front": "沈黙",
        "Back": "silence;reticence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1970
    },
    {
        "Front": "陳列",
        "Back": "exhibition;display;show",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1971
    },
    {
        "Front": "追及",
        "Back": "gaining on;carrying out;solving (crime)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1972
    },
    {
        "Front": "追跡",
        "Back": "pursuit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1973
    },
    {
        "Front": "次いで",
        "Back": "next;secondly;subsequently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1974
    },
    {
        "Front": "追放",
        "Back": "exile;banishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1975
    },
    {
        "Front": "費やす",
        "Back": "to spend;to devote;to waste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1976
    },
    {
        "Front": "墜落",
        "Back": "falling;crashing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1977
    },
    {
        "Front": "通",
        "Back": "connoisseur;counter for letters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1978
    },
    {
        "Front": "痛感",
        "Back": "feeling keenly;fully realizing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1979
    },
    {
        "Front": "通常",
        "Back": "common;general;usually",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1980
    },
    {
        "Front": "痛切",
        "Back": "keen;acute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1981
    },
    {
        "Front": "杖",
        "Back": "cane",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1982
    },
    {
        "Front": "遣い",
        "Back": "mission;simple task;doing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1983
    },
    {
        "Front": "使い道",
        "Back": "use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1984
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕える",
        "Back": "to serve;to work for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1985
    },
    {
        "Front": "司る",
        "Back": "to rule;to govern;to administer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1986
    },
    {
        "Front": "束の間",
        "Back": "moment;brief time;brief;transient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1987
    },
    {
        "Front": "付き",
        "Back": "attached to;impression;sociality;appearance;furnished with;under;to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1988
    },
    {
        "Front": "付き合う",
        "Back": "to associate with;to keep company with;to get on with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1989
    },
    {
        "Front": "月並み",
        "Back": "every month;common",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1990
    },
    {
        "Front": "尽きる",
        "Back": "to be used up;to be run out;to be exhausted;to be consumed;to come to an end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1991
    },
    {
        "Front": "継ぎ目",
        "Back": "a joint;joining point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1992
    },
    {
        "Front": "吐く",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;to breathe; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;to tell (lies); 3.&nbsp;&nbsp;to vomit;to disgorge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1993
    },
    {
        "Front": "尽くす",
        "Back": "to exhaust;to run out;to serve (a person);to befriend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1994
    },
    {
        "Front": "作り",
        "Back": "make-up;sliced raw fish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1995
    },
    {
        "Front": "造り",
        "Back": "make up;structure;physique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1996
    },
    {
        "Front": "造る",
        "Back": "to make;to create;to manufacture;to draw up;to write;to compose;to build;to coin;to cultivate;to org",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1997
    },
    {
        "Front": "繕う",
        "Back": "to mend;to repair;to fix;to patch up;to darn;to tidy up;to adjust;to trim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1998
    },
    {
        "Front": "接ぐ",
        "Back": "to join;to piece together;to set (bones);to graft (trees)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1999
    },
    {
        "Front": "継ぐ",
        "Back": "to succeed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2000
    },
    {
        "Front": "付け加える",
        "Back": "to add one thing to another",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2001
    },
    {
        "Front": "告げる",
        "Back": "to inform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2002
    },
    {
        "Front": "辻褄",
        "Back": "coherence;consistency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2003
    },
    {
        "Front": "途中",
        "Back": "on the way;en route",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2004
    },
    {
        "Front": "突っ張る",
        "Back": "to support;to become stiff;to become taut;to thrust (ones opponent);to stick to (ones opinion);to in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2005
    },
    {
        "Front": "筒",
        "Back": "pipe;tube",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2006
    },
    {
        "Front": "銃",
        "Back": "gun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2007
    },
    {
        "Front": "突く",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;to thrust;to strike;to attack; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;to poke;to nudge;to pick at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2008
    },
    {
        "Front": "慎む",
        "Back": "to be careful;to be chaste or discreet;to abstain or refrain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2009
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝言",
        "Back": "verbal message;rumor;word",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2010
    },
    {
        "Front": "勤まる",
        "Back": "to be fit for;to be equal to;to function properly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2011
    },
    {
        "Front": "勤め先",
        "Back": "place of work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2012
    },
    {
        "Front": "努めて",
        "Back": "make an effort!;work hard!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2013
    },
    {
        "Front": "津波",
        "Back": "tsunami;tidal wave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2014
    },
    {
        "Front": "抓る",
        "Back": "to pinch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2015
    },
    {
        "Front": "募る",
        "Back": "to invite;to solicit help&nbsp;&nbsp;participation&nbsp;&nbsp;etc",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2016
    },
    {
        "Front": "唾",
        "Back": "saliva;sputum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2017
    },
    {
        "Front": "呟く",
        "Back": "to mutter;to murmur",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2018
    },
    {
        "Front": "瞑る",
        "Back": "to close the eyes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2019
    },
    {
        "Front": "壷",
        "Back": "tsubo jar;pot;vase",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2020
    },
    {
        "Front": "蕾",
        "Back": "bud;flower bud",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2021
    },
    {
        "Front": "躓く",
        "Back": "to stumble;to trip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2022
    },
    {
        "Front": "摘む",
        "Back": "to pinch;to hold;to pick up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2023
    },
    {
        "Front": "詰らない",
        "Back": "insignificant;boring;trifling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2024
    },
    {
        "Front": "詰まり",
        "Back": "in short;in brief;in other words;that is to say;in the long run;after all;blockade;stuffing;ultimate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2025
    },
    {
        "Front": "積もり",
        "Back": "intention;plan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2026
    },
    {
        "Front": "露",
        "Back": "dew",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2027
    },
    {
        "Front": "強まる",
        "Back": "to get strong;to gain strength",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2028
    },
    {
        "Front": "強める",
        "Back": "to strengthen;to emphasize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2029
    },
    {
        "Front": "連なる",
        "Back": "to extend;to stretch out;to stand in a row",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2030
    },
    {
        "Front": "貫く",
        "Back": "to go through",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2031
    },
    {
        "Front": "連ねる",
        "Back": "to link;to join;to put together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2032
    },
    {
        "Front": "釣り",
        "Back": "fishing;angling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2033
    },
    {
        "Front": "吊り革",
        "Back": "strap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2034
    },
    {
        "Front": "釣鐘",
        "Back": "hanging bell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2035
    },
    {
        "Front": "吊るす",
        "Back": "to hang",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2036
    },
    {
        "Front": "手当て",
        "Back": "allowance;compensation;treatment;medical care",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2037
    },
    {
        "Front": "体",
        "Back": "appearance;air;condition;state;form",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2038
    },
    {
        "Front": "提供",
        "Back": "offer;tender;program sponsoring;furnishing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2039
    },
    {
        "Front": "定義",
        "Back": "definition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2040
    },
    {
        "Front": "提携",
        "Back": "cooperation;tie-up;joint business;link-up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2041
    },
    {
        "Front": "体裁",
        "Back": "decency;style;form;appearance;show;get-up;format",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2042
    },
    {
        "Front": "梯子",
        "Back": "ladder;stairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2043
    },
    {
        "Front": "定食",
        "Back": "set meal;special (of the day)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2044
    },
    {
        "Front": "提示",
        "Back": "presentation;exhibit;suggest;citation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2045
    },
    {
        "Front": "訂正",
        "Back": "correction;revision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2046
    },
    {
        "Front": "停滞",
        "Back": "stagnation;tie-up;congestion;retention;accumulation;falling into arrears",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2047
    },
    {
        "Front": "邸宅",
        "Back": "mansion;residence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2048
    },
    {
        "Front": "定年",
        "Back": "retirement age",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2049
    },
    {
        "Front": "堤防",
        "Back": "bank;weir",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2050
    },
    {
        "Front": "手遅れ",
        "Back": "too late;belated treatment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2051
    },
    {
        "Front": "手数",
        "Back": "number of moves;trouble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2052
    },
    {
        "Front": "手掛かり",
        "Back": "contact;trail;scent;on hand;hand hold;clue;key",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2053
    },
    {
        "Front": "手掛ける",
        "Back": "to handle;to manage;to work with;to rear;to look after;to have experience with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2054
    },
    {
        "Front": "手軽",
        "Back": "easy;simple;informal;offhand;cheap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2055
    },
    {
        "Front": "的",
        "Back": "-like;typical",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2056
    },
    {
        "Front": "適応",
        "Back": "adaptation;accommodation;conformity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2057
    },
    {
        "Front": "適宜",
        "Back": "suitability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2058
    },
    {
        "Front": "適性",
        "Back": "aptitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2059
    },
    {
        "Front": "手際",
        "Back": "performance;skill;tact",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2060
    },
    {
        "Front": "手順",
        "Back": "process;procedure;protocol",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2061
    },
    {
        "Front": "手錠",
        "Back": "handcuffs;manacles",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2062
    },
    {
        "Front": "手近",
        "Back": "near;handy;familiar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2063
    },
    {
        "Front": "てっきり",
        "Back": "surely;certainly;beyond doubt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉄鋼",
        "Back": "iron and steel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2064
    },
    {
        "Front": "徹する",
        "Back": "to sink in;to penetrate;to devote oneself;to believe in;to go through;to do intently and exclusively",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2065
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉄片",
        "Back": "iron scraps",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2066
    },
    {
        "Front": "手配",
        "Back": "arrangement;search (by police)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2067
    },
    {
        "Front": "手筈",
        "Back": "arrangement;plan;programme",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2068
    },
    {
        "Front": "手引き",
        "Back": "guidance;guide;introduction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2069
    },
    {
        "Front": "手本",
        "Back": "model;pattern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2070
    },
    {
        "Front": "手回し",
        "Back": "preparations;arrangements",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2071
    },
    {
        "Front": "手元",
        "Back": "on hand;at hand;at home",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2072
    },
    {
        "Front": "照り返す",
        "Back": "to reflect;to throw back light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2073
    },
    {
        "Front": "手分け",
        "Back": "division of labour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2074
    },
    {
        "Front": "店",
        "Back": "store;shop;establishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2075
    },
    {
        "Front": "点火",
        "Back": "ignition;lighting;set fire to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2076
    },
    {
        "Front": "転回",
        "Back": "revolution;rotation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2077
    },
    {
        "Front": "転換",
        "Back": "convert;divert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2078
    },
    {
        "Front": "転居",
        "Back": "moving;changing residence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2079
    },
    {
        "Front": "転勤",
        "Back": "transfer;transmission",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2080
    },
    {
        "Front": "点検",
        "Back": "inspection;examination;checking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2081
    },
    {
        "Front": "転校",
        "Back": "change schools",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2082
    },
    {
        "Front": "天国",
        "Back": "paradise;heaven;Kingdom of Heaven",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2083
    },
    {
        "Front": "天才",
        "Back": "genius;prodigy;natural gift",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2084
    },
    {
        "Front": "天災",
        "Back": "natural calamity;disaster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2085
    },
    {
        "Front": "展示",
        "Back": "exhibition;display",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2086
    },
    {
        "Front": "天井",
        "Back": "ceiling;ceiling price",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2087
    },
    {
        "Front": "転じる",
        "Back": "to turn;to shift;to alter;to distract",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2088
    },
    {
        "Front": "点線",
        "Back": "dotted line;perforated line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2089
    },
    {
        "Front": "天体",
        "Back": "heavenly body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2090
    },
    {
        "Front": "転転",
        "Back": "rolling about;moving from place to place;being passed around repeatedly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2091
    },
    {
        "Front": "てんで",
        "Back": "(not) at all;altogether;entirely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "転任",
        "Back": "change of post",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2092
    },
    {
        "Front": "展望",
        "Back": "view;outlook;prospect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2093
    },
    {
        "Front": "転落",
        "Back": "fall;degradation;slump",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2094
    },
    {
        "Front": "出合う",
        "Back": "to meet by chance;to come across;to happen to encounter;to hold a rendezvous;to have a date",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2095
    },
    {
        "Front": "出入り口",
        "Back": "exit and entrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2096
    },
    {
        "Front": "でかい",
        "Back": "huge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出来物",
        "Back": "able man;tumour;growth;boil;ulcer;abcess;rash;pimple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2097
    },
    {
        "Front": "出切る",
        "Back": "to be out of;to have no more at hand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2098
    },
    {
        "Front": "出くわす",
        "Back": "to happen to meet;to come across",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2099
    },
    {
        "Front": "出鱈目",
        "Back": "irresponsible utterance;nonsense;nonsensical;random;haphazard;unsystematic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2100
    },
    {
        "Front": "出直し",
        "Back": "adjustment;touch up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2101
    },
    {
        "Front": "田園",
        "Back": "country;rural districts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2102
    },
    {
        "Front": "電源",
        "Back": "source of electricity;power (button on TV&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2103
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝説",
        "Back": "tradition;legend;folklore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2104
    },
    {
        "Front": "電線",
        "Back": "electric line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2105
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝達",
        "Back": "transmission (e.g. news);communication;delivery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2106
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝来",
        "Back": "ancestral;hereditary;imported;transmitted;handed down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2107
    },
    {
        "Front": "と",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;if (conjunction); 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;promoted pawn (shogi) (abbr)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "問い合わせる",
        "Back": "to enquire;to seek information",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2108
    },
    {
        "Front": "問屋",
        "Back": "wholesale store",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2109
    },
    {
        "Front": "問う",
        "Back": "to ask;to question;to charge (i.e. with a crime);to accuse;without regard to (neg)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2110
    },
    {
        "Front": "棟",
        "Back": "place;section;building",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2111
    },
    {
        "Front": "等",
        "Back": "et cetera;etc.;and the like",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2112
    },
    {
        "Front": "陶器",
        "Back": "pottery;ceramics",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2113
    },
    {
        "Front": "等級",
        "Back": "grade;class",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2114
    },
    {
        "Front": "討議",
        "Back": "debate;discussion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2115
    },
    {
        "Front": "登校",
        "Back": "attendance (at school)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2116
    },
    {
        "Front": "統合",
        "Back": "integration;unification;synthesis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2117
    },
    {
        "Front": "倒産",
        "Back": "(corporate) bankruptcy;insolvency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2118
    },
    {
        "Front": "投資",
        "Back": "investment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2119
    },
    {
        "Front": "統治",
        "Back": "rule;reign;government;governing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2120
    },
    {
        "Front": "統制",
        "Back": "regulation;control",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2121
    },
    {
        "Front": "当選",
        "Back": "being elected;winning the prize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2122
    },
    {
        "Front": "逃走",
        "Back": "flight;desertion;escape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2123
    },
    {
        "Front": "統率",
        "Back": "command;lead;generalship;leadership",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2124
    },
    {
        "Front": "到達",
        "Back": "reaching;attaining;arrival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2125
    },
    {
        "Front": "到底",
        "Back": "(cannot) possibly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2126
    },
    {
        "Front": "丁々",
        "Back": "clashing of swords;felling of trees;ringing of an ax",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2127
    },
    {
        "Front": "投入",
        "Back": "throw;investment;making (an electrical circuit)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2128
    },
    {
        "Front": "当人",
        "Back": "the one concerned;the said person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2129
    },
    {
        "Front": "逃亡",
        "Back": "escape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2130
    },
    {
        "Front": "冬眠",
        "Back": "hibernation;winter sleep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2131
    },
    {
        "Front": "登録",
        "Back": "registration;register;entry;record",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2132
    },
    {
        "Front": "討論",
        "Back": "debate;discussion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2133
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠ざかる",
        "Back": "to go far off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2134
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠回り",
        "Back": "detour;roundabout way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2135
    },
    {
        "Front": "通りかかる",
        "Back": "to happen to pass by",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2136
    },
    {
        "Front": "兎角",
        "Back": "anyhow;anyway;somehow or other;generally speaking;in any case;this and that;many;be apt to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2137
    },
    {
        "Front": "咎める",
        "Back": "to blame;to find fault;to take someone to task;to aggravate (an injury)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2138
    },
    {
        "Front": "時折",
        "Back": "sometimes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2139
    },
    {
        "Front": "跡切れる",
        "Back": "to pause;to be interrupted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2140
    },
    {
        "Front": "説く",
        "Back": "to explain;to advocate;to preach;to persuade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2141
    },
    {
        "Front": "特技",
        "Back": "special skill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2142
    },
    {
        "Front": "特産",
        "Back": "specialty;special product",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2143
    },
    {
        "Front": "特集",
        "Back": "feature (e.g. newspaper);special edition;report",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2144
    },
    {
        "Front": "得点",
        "Back": "score;points made;marks obtained;runs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2145
    },
    {
        "Front": "特派",
        "Back": "send specially;special envoy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2146
    },
    {
        "Front": "特有",
        "Back": "characteristic (of);peculiar (to)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2147
    },
    {
        "Front": "研ぐ",
        "Back": "to sharpen;to grind;to scour;to hone;to polish;to wash (rice)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2148
    },
    {
        "Front": "刺",
        "Back": "thorn;splinter;spine;biting words",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2149
    },
    {
        "Front": "遂げる",
        "Back": "to accomplish;to achieve;to carry out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2150
    },
    {
        "Front": "床",
        "Back": "bed;sickbed;alcove;padding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2151
    },
    {
        "Front": "所が",
        "Back": "however;while;even if",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2152
    },
    {
        "Front": "所で",
        "Back": "by the way;even if;no matter what",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2153
    },
    {
        "Front": "年頃",
        "Back": "age;marriageable age;age of puberty;adolescence;for some years",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2154
    },
    {
        "Front": "年寄り",
        "Back": "old people;the aged",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2155
    },
    {
        "Front": "戸締り",
        "Back": "closing up;fastening the doors",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2156
    },
    {
        "Front": "途上",
        "Back": "en route;half way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2157
    },
    {
        "Front": "綴じる",
        "Back": "to bind;to file",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2158
    },
    {
        "Front": "途絶える",
        "Back": "to stop;to cease;to come to an end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2159
    },
    {
        "Front": "特許",
        "Back": "special permission;patent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2160
    },
    {
        "Front": "疾っくに",
        "Back": "long ago;already;a long time ago",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2161
    },
    {
        "Front": "特権",
        "Back": "privilege;special right",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2162
    },
    {
        "Front": "咄嗟",
        "Back": "moment;instant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2163
    },
    {
        "Front": "取っ手",
        "Back": "handle;grip;knob",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2164
    },
    {
        "Front": "突破",
        "Back": "breaking through;breakthrough;penetration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2165
    },
    {
        "Front": "突如",
        "Back": "suddenly;all of a sudden",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2166
    },
    {
        "Front": "迚も",
        "Back": "very;awfully;exceedingly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2167
    },
    {
        "Front": "整える",
        "Back": "to put in order;to get ready;to arrange;to adjust",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2168
    },
    {
        "Front": "届け",
        "Back": "report;notification;registration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2169
    },
    {
        "Front": "滞る",
        "Back": "to stagnate;to be delayed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2170
    },
    {
        "Front": "止まる",
        "Back": "to be limited to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2171
    },
    {
        "Front": "留める",
        "Back": "to stop;to cease;to put an end to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2172
    },
    {
        "Front": "止める",
        "Back": "to stop;to cease;to put an end to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2173
    },
    {
        "Front": "唱える",
        "Back": "to recite;to chant;to call upon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2174
    },
    {
        "Front": "兎に角",
        "Back": "anyhow;at any rate;anyway;somehow or other;generally speaking;in any case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2175
    },
    {
        "Front": "殿様",
        "Back": "feudal lord",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2176
    },
    {
        "Front": "幕",
        "Back": "curtain;bunting;act (in play)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2177
    },
    {
        "Front": "帳",
        "Back": "curtain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2178
    },
    {
        "Front": "扉",
        "Back": "door;opening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2179
    },
    {
        "Front": "徒歩",
        "Back": "walking;going on foot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2180
    },
    {
        "Front": "乏しい",
        "Back": "meagre;scarce;limited;destitute;hard up;scanty;poor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2181
    },
    {
        "Front": "富",
        "Back": "wealth;fortune",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2182
    },
    {
        "Front": "富む",
        "Back": "to be rich;to become rich",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2183
    },
    {
        "Front": "兎も角",
        "Back": "anyhow;anyway;somehow or other;generally speaking;in any case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2184
    },
    {
        "Front": "共稼ぎ",
        "Back": "working together;(husband and wife) earning a living together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2185
    },
    {
        "Front": "灯",
        "Back": "light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2186
    },
    {
        "Front": "伴う",
        "Back": "to accompany;to bring with;to be accompanied by;to be involved in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2187
    },
    {
        "Front": "共働き",
        "Back": "dual income",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2188
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕らえる",
        "Back": "to seize;to grasp;to capture;to arrest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2189
    },
    {
        "Front": "取りあえず",
        "Back": "at once;first of all;for the time being",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2190
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り扱い",
        "Back": "treatment;service;handling;management",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2191
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り扱う",
        "Back": "to treat;to handle;to deal in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2192
    },
    {
        "Front": "鳥居",
        "Back": "torii (Shinto shrine archway)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2193
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り替え",
        "Back": "swap;exchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2194
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り組む",
        "Back": "to tackle;to wrestle with;to engage in a bout;to come to grips with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2195
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り締まり",
        "Back": "control;management;supervision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2196
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り締まる",
        "Back": "to manage;to control;to supervise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2197
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り調べる",
        "Back": "to investigate;to examine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2198
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り立てる",
        "Back": "to collect;to extort;to appoint;to promote",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2199
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り次ぐ",
        "Back": "to act as an agent for;to announce (someone);to convey (a message)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2200
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り除く",
        "Back": "to remove;to take away;to set apart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2201
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り引き",
        "Back": "transactions;dealings;business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2202
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り巻く",
        "Back": "to surround;to circle;to enclose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2203
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り混ぜる",
        "Back": "to mix;to put together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2204
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り戻す",
        "Back": "to take back;to regain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2205
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り寄せる",
        "Back": "to order;to send away for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2206
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り分",
        "Back": "especially;above all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2207
    },
    {
        "Front": "副",
        "Back": "especially;above all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2208
    },
    {
        "Front": "蕩ける",
        "Back": "to be enchanted with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2209
    },
    {
        "Front": "とんだ",
        "Back": "terrible;awful;serious;preposterous;absolutely not",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "胴",
        "Back": "trunk;body;frame",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2210
    },
    {
        "Front": "働",
        "Back": "work;labor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2211
    },
    {
        "Front": "同",
        "Back": "the same;the said;ibid.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2212
    },
    {
        "Front": "同意",
        "Back": "agreement;consent;same meaning;same opinion;approval",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2213
    },
    {
        "Front": "動員",
        "Back": "mobilization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2214
    },
    {
        "Front": "同感",
        "Back": "agreement;same opinion;same feeling;sympathy;concurrence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2215
    },
    {
        "Front": "動機",
        "Back": "motive;incentive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2216
    },
    {
        "Front": "同級",
        "Back": "the same grade;same class",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2217
    },
    {
        "Front": "同居",
        "Back": "living together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2218
    },
    {
        "Front": "動向",
        "Back": "trend;tendency;movement;attitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2219
    },
    {
        "Front": "同士",
        "Back": "fellow;companion;comrade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2220
    },
    {
        "Front": "同志",
        "Back": "same mind;comrade;kindred soul",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2221
    },
    {
        "Front": "如何して",
        "Back": "why?;for what reason;how;in what way;for what purpose;what for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2222
    },
    {
        "Front": "如何しても",
        "Back": "by all means;at any cost;no matter what;after all;in the long run;cravingly;at any rate;surely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2223
    },
    {
        "Front": "同情",
        "Back": "sympathy;compassion;sympathize;pity;feel for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2224
    },
    {
        "Front": "道場",
        "Back": "dojo;hall used for martial arts training;mandala",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2225
    },
    {
        "Front": "何卒",
        "Back": "please;kindly;by all means",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2226
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうぞ宜しく",
        "Back": "pleased to meet you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2227
    },
    {
        "Front": "同調",
        "Back": "sympathy;agree with;alignment;tuning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2228
    },
    {
        "Front": "動的",
        "Back": "dynamic;kinetic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2229
    },
    {
        "Front": "同等",
        "Back": "equality;equal;same rights;same rank",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2230
    },
    {
        "Front": "堂々",
        "Back": "magnificent;grand;impressive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2231
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうにか",
        "Back": "in some way or other;one way or another",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "導入",
        "Back": "introduction;bringing in;leading in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2232
    },
    {
        "Front": "同封",
        "Back": "enclosure (e.g. in a letter)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2233
    },
    {
        "Front": "同盟",
        "Back": "alliance;union;league",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2234
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうやら",
        "Back": "it seems like;somehow or other",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "動揺",
        "Back": "disturbance;unrest;shaking;trembling;pitching;rolling;oscillation;agitation;excitement;commotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2235
    },
    {
        "Front": "動力",
        "Back": "power;motive power;dynamic force",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2236
    },
    {
        "Front": "独裁",
        "Back": "dictatorship;despotism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2237
    },
    {
        "Front": "読者",
        "Back": "reader",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2238
    },
    {
        "Front": "独自",
        "Back": "original;peculiar;characteristic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2239
    },
    {
        "Front": "独占",
        "Back": "monopoly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2240
    },
    {
        "Front": "独創",
        "Back": "originality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2241
    },
    {
        "Front": "何処",
        "Back": "where;what place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2242
    },
    {
        "Front": "何処か",
        "Back": "somewhere;anywhere;in some respects",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2243
    },
    {
        "Front": "土産",
        "Back": "product of the land",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2244
    },
    {
        "Front": "土台",
        "Back": "foundation;base;basis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2245
    },
    {
        "Front": "何方",
        "Back": "which;who",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2246
    },
    {
        "Front": "土手",
        "Back": "embankment;bank",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2247
    },
    {
        "Front": "怒鳴る",
        "Back": "to shout;to yell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2248
    },
    {
        "Front": "何の",
        "Back": "which;what",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2249
    },
    {
        "Front": "土俵",
        "Back": "arena",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2250
    },
    {
        "Front": "土木",
        "Back": "public works",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2251
    },
    {
        "Front": "何々",
        "Back": "which (emphatic)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2252
    },
    {
        "Front": "度忘れ",
        "Back": "lapse of memory;forget for a moment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2253
    },
    {
        "Front": "鈍感",
        "Back": "thickheadedness;stolidity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2254
    },
    {
        "Front": "内閣",
        "Back": "cabinet;(government) ministry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2255
    },
    {
        "Front": "乃至",
        "Back": "from...to;between...and;or",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2256
    },
    {
        "Front": "内臓",
        "Back": "internal organs;intestines;viscera",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2257
    },
    {
        "Front": "内部",
        "Back": "interior;inside;internal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2258
    },
    {
        "Front": "内乱",
        "Back": "civil war;insurrection;rebellion;domestic conflict",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2259
    },
    {
        "Front": "内陸",
        "Back": "inland",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2260
    },
    {
        "Front": "苗",
        "Back": "rice seedling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2261
    },
    {
        "Front": "尚",
        "Back": "furthermore;still;yet;more;still more;greater;further;less",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2262
    },
    {
        "Front": "尚更",
        "Back": "all the more;still less",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2263
    },
    {
        "Front": "中程",
        "Back": "middle;midway",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2264
    },
    {
        "Front": "流し",
        "Back": "sink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2265
    },
    {
        "Front": "長々",
        "Back": "long;drawn-out;very long",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2266
    },
    {
        "Front": "殴る",
        "Back": "to strike;to hit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2267
    },
    {
        "Front": "嘆く",
        "Back": "to sigh;to lament;to grieve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2268
    },
    {
        "Front": "投げ出す",
        "Back": "to throw down;to abandon;to sacrifice;to throw out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2269
    },
    {
        "Front": "和やか",
        "Back": "mild;calm;gentle;quiet;harmonious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2270
    },
    {
        "Front": "名残",
        "Back": "remains;traces;memory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2271
    },
    {
        "Front": "情け",
        "Back": "sympathy;compassion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2272
    },
    {
        "Front": "情け深い",
        "Back": "tender-hearted;compassionate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2273
    },
    {
        "Front": "為さる",
        "Back": "to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2274
    },
    {
        "Front": "詰る",
        "Back": "to rebuke;to scold;to tell off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2275
    },
    {
        "Front": "何故",
        "Back": "why;how",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2276
    },
    {
        "Front": "何故なら",
        "Back": "because",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2277
    },
    {
        "Front": "名高い",
        "Back": "famous;celebrated;well-known",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2278
    },
    {
        "Front": "雪崩",
        "Back": "avalanche",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2279
    },
    {
        "Front": "懐く",
        "Back": "to become emotionally attached",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2280
    },
    {
        "Front": "名付ける",
        "Back": "to name (someone)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2281
    },
    {
        "Front": "何気ない",
        "Back": "casual;unconcerned",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2282
    },
    {
        "Front": "何しろ",
        "Back": "at any rate;anyhow;anyway;in any case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2283
    },
    {
        "Front": "何も",
        "Back": "nothing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2284
    },
    {
        "Front": "何より",
        "Back": "most;best",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2285
    },
    {
        "Front": "七日",
        "Back": "seven days;the seventh day (of the month)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2286
    },
    {
        "Front": "名札",
        "Back": "name plate;name tag",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2287
    },
    {
        "Front": "生臭い",
        "Back": "smelling of fish or blood;fish or meat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2288
    },
    {
        "Front": "生温い",
        "Back": "lukewarm;halfhearted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2289
    },
    {
        "Front": "生身",
        "Back": "living flesh;flesh and blood;the quick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2290
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉛",
        "Back": "lead (the metal)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2291
    },
    {
        "Front": "鈍る",
        "Back": "to become less capable;to grow dull;to become blunt;to weaken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2292
    },
    {
        "Front": "並み",
        "Back": "average;medium;common;ordinary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2293
    },
    {
        "Front": "滑らか",
        "Back": "smoothness;glassiness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2294
    },
    {
        "Front": "嘗める",
        "Back": "to lick;to taste;to experience;to make fun of;to make light of;to put down;to treat with contempt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2295
    },
    {
        "Front": "悩ましい",
        "Back": "seductive;melancholy;languid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2296
    },
    {
        "Front": "悩ます",
        "Back": "to afflict;to torment;to harass;to molest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2297
    },
    {
        "Front": "悩み",
        "Back": "trouble(s);worry;distress;anguish;agony;problem",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2298
    },
    {
        "Front": "平均",
        "Back": "equilibrium;balance;average;mean",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2299
    },
    {
        "Front": "慣らす",
        "Back": "to accustom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2300
    },
    {
        "Front": "馴らす",
        "Back": "to domesticate;to tame",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2301
    },
    {
        "Front": "並びに",
        "Back": "and",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2302
    },
    {
        "Front": "成り立つ",
        "Back": "to conclude;to consist of;to be practical (logical&nbsp;&nbsp;feasible&nbsp;&nbsp;viable);to hold true",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2303
    },
    {
        "Front": "成る丈",
        "Back": "as much as possible;if possible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2304
    },
    {
        "Front": "成るべく",
        "Back": "as much as possible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2305
    },
    {
        "Front": "慣れ",
        "Back": "practice;experience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2306
    },
    {
        "Front": "馴れ馴れしい",
        "Back": "over-familiar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2307
    },
    {
        "Front": "難",
        "Back": "difficulty;hardships;defect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2308
    },
    {
        "Front": "南",
        "Back": "south",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2309
    },
    {
        "Front": "なんか",
        "Back": "things like ...;or something like that .. (often derogatory)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "何だか",
        "Back": "a little;somewhat;somehow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2310
    },
    {
        "Front": "なんだかんだ",
        "Back": "something or other",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "何て",
        "Back": "how...!;what...!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2311
    },
    {
        "Front": "何と",
        "Back": "what;how;whatever",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2312
    },
    {
        "Front": "何となく",
        "Back": "somehow or other;for some reason or another",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2313
    },
    {
        "Front": "何とも",
        "Back": "nothing (with neg. verb);quite;not a bit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2314
    },
    {
        "Front": "何なり",
        "Back": "any;anything;whatever",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2315
    },
    {
        "Front": "荷",
        "Back": "load;baggage;cargo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2316
    },
    {
        "Front": "似通う",
        "Back": "to resemble closely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2317
    },
    {
        "Front": "面皰",
        "Back": "pimple;acne",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2318
    },
    {
        "Front": "賑わう",
        "Back": "to prosper;to flourish;to do thriving business;to be crowded with people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2319
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪い",
        "Back": "hateful;abominable;poor-looking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2320
    },
    {
        "Front": "憎しみ",
        "Back": "hatred",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2321
    },
    {
        "Front": "肉親",
        "Back": "blood relationship;blood relative",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2322
    },
    {
        "Front": "肉体",
        "Back": "the body;the flesh",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2323
    },
    {
        "Front": "逃げ出す",
        "Back": "to run away;to escape from",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2324
    },
    {
        "Front": "西日",
        "Back": "westering sun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2325
    },
    {
        "Front": "滲む",
        "Back": "to run;to blur;to spread;to blot;to ooze",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2326
    },
    {
        "Front": "日夜",
        "Back": "day and night;always",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2327
    },
    {
        "Front": "日当",
        "Back": "daily allowance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2328
    },
    {
        "Front": "荷造り",
        "Back": "packing;baling;crating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2329
    },
    {
        "Front": "担う",
        "Back": "to carry on shoulder;to bear (burden);to shoulder (gun)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2330
    },
    {
        "Front": "二人",
        "Back": "two persons;two people;pair;couple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2331
    },
    {
        "Front": "にも拘らず",
        "Back": "in spite of;nevertheless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2332
    },
    {
        "Front": "入手",
        "Back": "obtaining;coming to hand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2333
    },
    {
        "Front": "入賞",
        "Back": "winning a prize or place (in a contest)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2334
    },
    {
        "Front": "入浴",
        "Back": "bathe;bathing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2335
    },
    {
        "Front": "尿",
        "Back": "urine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2336
    },
    {
        "Front": "俄か",
        "Back": "sudden;abrupt;unexpected;improvised;offhand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2337
    },
    {
        "Front": "認識",
        "Back": "recognition;cognizance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2338
    },
    {
        "Front": "妊娠",
        "Back": "conception;pregnancy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2339
    },
    {
        "Front": "人情",
        "Back": "humanity;empathy;kindness;sympathy;human nature;common sense;customs and manners",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2340
    },
    {
        "Front": "任務",
        "Back": "duty;function;office;mission;task",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2341
    },
    {
        "Front": "任命",
        "Back": "appointment;nomination;ordination;commission;designation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2342
    },
    {
        "Front": "抜かす",
        "Back": "to omit;to leave out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2343
    },
    {
        "Front": "抜け出す",
        "Back": "to slip out;to sneak away;to excel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2344
    },
    {
        "Front": "盗み",
        "Back": "stealing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2345
    },
    {
        "Front": "沼",
        "Back": "swamp;bog;pond;lake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2346
    },
    {
        "Front": "音",
        "Back": "sound;note",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2347
    },
    {
        "Front": "値打ち",
        "Back": "value;worth;price;dignity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2348
    },
    {
        "Front": "寝かせる",
        "Back": "to put to bed;to lay down;to ferment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2349
    },
    {
        "Front": "捻子",
        "Back": "screw;helix;spiral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2350
    },
    {
        "Front": "ねじ回し",
        "Back": "screwdriver",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2351
    },
    {
        "Front": "捻じれる",
        "Back": "to twist;to wrench;to screw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2352
    },
    {
        "Front": "鼠",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;mouse;rat; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;dark gray;slate color",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2353
    },
    {
        "Front": "妬む",
        "Back": "to be jealous;to be envious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2354
    },
    {
        "Front": "強請る",
        "Back": "to tease;to coax;to solicit;to demand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2355
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱湯",
        "Back": "boiling water",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2356
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱意",
        "Back": "zeal;enthusiasm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2357
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱量",
        "Back": "temperature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2358
    },
    {
        "Front": "粘り",
        "Back": "stickyness;viscosity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2359
    },
    {
        "Front": "粘る",
        "Back": "to be sticky;to be adhesive;to persevere;to persist;to stick to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2360
    },
    {
        "Front": "値引き",
        "Back": "price reduction;discount",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2361
    },
    {
        "Front": "根回し",
        "Back": "making necessary arrangements",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2362
    },
    {
        "Front": "眠たい",
        "Back": "sleepy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2363
    },
    {
        "Front": "練る",
        "Back": "to knead;to work over;to polish up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2364
    },
    {
        "Front": "念",
        "Back": "sense;idea;thought;feeling;desire;concern;attention;care",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2365
    },
    {
        "Front": "年鑑",
        "Back": "yearbook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2366
    },
    {
        "Front": "年号",
        "Back": "name of an era;year number",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2367
    },
    {
        "Front": "燃焼",
        "Back": "burning;combustion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2368
    },
    {
        "Front": "年生",
        "Back": "pupil in .... year;student in .... year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2369
    },
    {
        "Front": "年長",
        "Back": "seniority",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2370
    },
    {
        "Front": "燃料",
        "Back": "fuel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2371
    },
    {
        "Front": "年輪",
        "Back": "annual tree ring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2372
    },
    {
        "Front": "脳",
        "Back": "brain;memory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2373
    },
    {
        "Front": "農耕",
        "Back": "farming;agriculture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2374
    },
    {
        "Front": "農場",
        "Back": "farm (agriculture)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2375
    },
    {
        "Front": "農地",
        "Back": "agricultural land",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2376
    },
    {
        "Front": "納入",
        "Back": "payment;supply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2377
    },
    {
        "Front": "逃す",
        "Back": "to let loose;to set free;to let escape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2378
    },
    {
        "Front": "逃れる",
        "Back": "to escape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2379
    },
    {
        "Front": "軒並み",
        "Back": "row of houses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2380
    },
    {
        "Front": "鋸",
        "Back": "saw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2381
    },
    {
        "Front": "望ましい",
        "Back": "desirable;hoped for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2382
    },
    {
        "Front": "臨む",
        "Back": "to look out on;to face;to deal with;to attend (function)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2383
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗っ取る",
        "Back": "to capture;to occupy;to usurp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2384
    },
    {
        "Front": "長閑",
        "Back": "tranquil;calm;quiet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2385
    },
    {
        "Front": "罵る",
        "Back": "to speak ill of;to abuse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2386
    },
    {
        "Front": "延べ",
        "Back": "futures;credit (buying);stretching;total",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2387
    },
    {
        "Front": "飲み込む",
        "Back": "to gulp down;to swallow deeply;to understand;to take in;to catch on to;to learn;to digest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2388
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗り換え",
        "Back": "transfer (trains&nbsp;&nbsp;buses&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2389
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗り込む",
        "Back": "to board;to embark on;to get into (a car);to ship (passengers);to man (a ship);to help (someone) int",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2390
    },
    {
        "Front": "刃",
        "Back": "edge (of a sword)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2391
    },
    {
        "Front": "派",
        "Back": "clique;faction;school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2392
    },
    {
        "Front": "把握",
        "Back": "grasp;catch;understanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2393
    },
    {
        "Front": "肺",
        "Back": "lung",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2394
    },
    {
        "Front": "廃棄",
        "Back": "annullment;disposal;abandon;scrap;discarding;repeal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2395
    },
    {
        "Front": "配給",
        "Back": "distribution (eg. films&nbsp;&nbsp;rice)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2396
    },
    {
        "Front": "配偶者",
        "Back": "spouse;wife;husband",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2397
    },
    {
        "Front": "拝啓",
        "Back": "Dear (so and so)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2398
    },
    {
        "Front": "背景",
        "Back": "background;scenery;setting;circumstance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2399
    },
    {
        "Front": "背後",
        "Back": "back;rear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2400
    },
    {
        "Front": "灰皿",
        "Back": "ashtray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2401
    },
    {
        "Front": "廃止",
        "Back": "abolition;repeal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2402
    },
    {
        "Front": "拝借",
        "Back": "borrowing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2403
    },
    {
        "Front": "排除",
        "Back": "exclusion;removal;rejection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2404
    },
    {
        "Front": "排水",
        "Back": "drainage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2405
    },
    {
        "Front": "敗戦",
        "Back": "defeat;losing a war",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2406
    },
    {
        "Front": "配置",
        "Back": "arrangement (of resources);disposition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2407
    },
    {
        "Front": "配布",
        "Back": "distribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2408
    },
    {
        "Front": "配分",
        "Back": "distribution;allotment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2409
    },
    {
        "Front": "配慮",
        "Back": "consideration;concern;forethought",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2410
    },
    {
        "Front": "配列",
        "Back": "arrangement;array (programming)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2411
    },
    {
        "Front": "映える",
        "Back": "to shine;to look attractive;to look pretty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2412
    },
    {
        "Front": "破壊",
        "Back": "destruction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2413
    },
    {
        "Front": "墓地",
        "Back": "cemetery;graveyard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2414
    },
    {
        "Front": "捗る",
        "Back": "to make progress;to move right ahead (with the work);to advance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2415
    },
    {
        "Front": "果ない",
        "Back": "fleeting;transient;short-lived;momentary;vain;fickle;miserable;empty;ephemeral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2416
    },
    {
        "Front": "諮る",
        "Back": "to consult with;to confer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2417
    },
    {
        "Front": "図る",
        "Back": "to plot;to attempt;to plan;to take in;to deceive;to devise;to design;to refer A to B",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2418
    },
    {
        "Front": "剥がす",
        "Back": "to tear off;to peel off;to rip off;to strip off;to skin;to flay;to disrobe;to deprive of;to detach;t",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2419
    },
    {
        "Front": "破棄",
        "Back": "revocation;annulment;breaking (e.g. treaty)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2420
    },
    {
        "Front": "泊",
        "Back": "counter for nights of a stay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2421
    },
    {
        "Front": "迫害",
        "Back": "persecution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2422
    },
    {
        "Front": "薄弱",
        "Back": "feebleness;weakness;weak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2423
    },
    {
        "Front": "白状",
        "Back": "confession",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2424
    },
    {
        "Front": "剥ぐ",
        "Back": "to tear off;to peel off;to rip off;to strip off;to skin;to flay;to disrobe;to deprive of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2425
    },
    {
        "Front": "派遣",
        "Back": "dispatch;send",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2426
    },
    {
        "Front": "励ます",
        "Back": "to encourage;to cheer;to raise (the voice)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2427
    },
    {
        "Front": "励む",
        "Back": "to be zealous;to brace oneself;to endeavour;to strive;to make an effort",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2428
    },
    {
        "Front": "剥げる",
        "Back": "to come off;to be worn off;to fade;to discolor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2429
    },
    {
        "Front": "鋏",
        "Back": "scissors",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2430
    },
    {
        "Front": "柱",
        "Back": "pillar;post",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2431
    },
    {
        "Front": "橋渡し",
        "Back": "bridge building;mediation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2432
    },
    {
        "Front": "恥",
        "Back": "shame;embarrassment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2433
    },
    {
        "Front": "弾く",
        "Back": "to flip;to snap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2434
    },
    {
        "Front": "始め",
        "Back": "beginning;start;origin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2435
    },
    {
        "Front": "始めまして",
        "Back": "How do you do?;I am glad to meet you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2436
    },
    {
        "Front": "恥じらう",
        "Back": "to feel shy;to be bashful;to blush",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2437
    },
    {
        "Front": "恥じる",
        "Back": "to feel ashamed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2438
    },
    {
        "Front": "蓮",
        "Back": "lotus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2439
    },
    {
        "Front": "筈",
        "Back": "it should be so",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2440
    },
    {
        "Front": "弾む",
        "Back": "to spring;to bound;to bounce;to be stimulated;to be encouraged;to get lively;to treat oneself to;to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2441
    },
    {
        "Front": "破損",
        "Back": "damage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2442
    },
    {
        "Front": "機",
        "Back": "loom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2443
    },
    {
        "Front": "果たして",
        "Back": "as was expected;really",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2444
    },
    {
        "Front": "果たす",
        "Back": "to accomplish;to fulfill;to carry out;to achieve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2445
    },
    {
        "Front": "裸足",
        "Back": "barefoot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2446
    },
    {
        "Front": "蜂蜜",
        "Back": "honey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2447
    },
    {
        "Front": "発掘",
        "Back": "excavation;exhumation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2448
    },
    {
        "Front": "発生",
        "Back": "outbreak;spring forth;occurrence;incidence;origin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2449
    },
    {
        "Front": "発足",
        "Back": "starting;inauguration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2450
    },
    {
        "Front": "初",
        "Back": "first;new",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2451
    },
    {
        "Front": "発",
        "Back": "departure;beginning;counter for gunshots",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2452
    },
    {
        "Front": "発育",
        "Back": "(physical) growth;development",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2453
    },
    {
        "Front": "発芽",
        "Back": "burgeoning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2454
    },
    {
        "Front": "発言",
        "Back": "utterance;speech;proposal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2455
    },
    {
        "Front": "発病",
        "Back": "attack (disease)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2456
    },
    {
        "Front": "初耳",
        "Back": "something heard for the first time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2457
    },
    {
        "Front": "果て",
        "Back": "the end;the extremity;the limit(s);the result",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2458
    },
    {
        "Front": "果てる",
        "Back": "to end;to be finished;to be exhausted;to die;to perish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2459
    },
    {
        "Front": "話し合い",
        "Back": "discussion;conference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2460
    },
    {
        "Front": "甚だ",
        "Back": "very;greatly;exceedingly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2461
    },
    {
        "Front": "華々しい",
        "Back": "brilliant;magnificent;spectacular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2462
    },
    {
        "Front": "花びら",
        "Back": "(flower) petal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2463
    },
    {
        "Front": "華やか",
        "Back": "gay;showy;brilliant;gorgeous;florid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2464
    },
    {
        "Front": "阻む",
        "Back": "to keep someone from doing;to stop;to prevent;to check;to hinder;to obstruct;to oppose;to thwart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2465
    },
    {
        "Front": "浜",
        "Back": "beach;seashore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2466
    },
    {
        "Front": "浜辺",
        "Back": "beach;foreshore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2467
    },
    {
        "Front": "填まる",
        "Back": "to get into;to go into;to fit;to be fit for;to suit;to fall into;to plunge into;to be deceived;to be",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2468
    },
    {
        "Front": "歯磨",
        "Back": "dentifrice;toothpaste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2469
    },
    {
        "Front": "填める",
        "Back": "to get in;to insert;to put on;to make love",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2470
    },
    {
        "Front": "生やす",
        "Back": "to grow;to cultivate;to wear beard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2471
    },
    {
        "Front": "早める",
        "Back": "to hasten;to quicken;to expedite;to precipitate;to accelerate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2472
    },
    {
        "Front": "流行",
        "Back": "fashionable;fad;in vogue;prevailing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2473
    },
    {
        "Front": "腹立ち",
        "Back": "anger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2474
    },
    {
        "Front": "原っぱ",
        "Back": "open field;empty lot;plain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2475
    },
    {
        "Front": "張り紙",
        "Back": "paper patch;paper backing;poster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2476
    },
    {
        "Front": "遥か",
        "Back": "far;far-away;distant;remote;far off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2477
    },
    {
        "Front": "破裂",
        "Back": "explosion;rupture;break off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2478
    },
    {
        "Front": "腫れる",
        "Back": "to swell (from inflammation);to become swollen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2479
    },
    {
        "Front": "班",
        "Back": "group;party;section (mil)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2480
    },
    {
        "Front": "判",
        "Back": "seal;stamp;monogram signature;judgment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2481
    },
    {
        "Front": "版",
        "Back": "edition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2482
    },
    {
        "Front": "繁栄",
        "Back": "prospering;prosperity;thriving;flourishing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2483
    },
    {
        "Front": "反感",
        "Back": "antipathy;revolt;animosity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2484
    },
    {
        "Front": "版画",
        "Back": "art print",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2485
    },
    {
        "Front": "反響",
        "Back": "echo;reverberation;repercussion;reaction;influence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2486
    },
    {
        "Front": "判決",
        "Back": "judicial decision;judgement;sentence;decree",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2487
    },
    {
        "Front": "反撃",
        "Back": "counterattack;counteroffensive;counterblow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2488
    },
    {
        "Front": "反射",
        "Back": "reflection;reverberation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2489
    },
    {
        "Front": "繁殖",
        "Back": "breed;multiply;increase;propagation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2490
    },
    {
        "Front": "繁盛",
        "Back": "prosperity;flourishing;thriving",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2491
    },
    {
        "Front": "反する",
        "Back": "to be inconsistent with;to oppose;to contradict;to transgress;to rebel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2492
    },
    {
        "Front": "判定",
        "Back": "judgement;decision;award;verdict",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2493
    },
    {
        "Front": "反応",
        "Back": "reaction;response",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2494
    },
    {
        "Front": "半端",
        "Back": "remnant;fragment;incomplete set;fraction;odd sum;incompleteness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2495
    },
    {
        "Front": "反発",
        "Back": "repelling;rebound;recover;oppose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2496
    },
    {
        "Front": "反乱",
        "Back": "insurrection;mutiny;rebellion;revolt;uprising",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2497
    },
    {
        "Front": "氾濫",
        "Back": "overflowing;flood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2498
    },
    {
        "Front": "黴菌",
        "Back": "bacteria;germ(s)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2499
    },
    {
        "Front": "賠償",
        "Back": "reparations;indemnity;compensation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2500
    },
    {
        "Front": "倍率",
        "Back": "diameter;magnification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2501
    },
    {
        "Front": "馬鹿馬鹿しい",
        "Back": "stupid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2502
    },
    {
        "Front": "馬鹿らしい",
        "Back": "absurd",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2503
    },
    {
        "Front": "漠然",
        "Back": "obscure;vague;equivocal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2504
    },
    {
        "Front": "爆弾",
        "Back": "bomb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2505
    },
    {
        "Front": "爆破",
        "Back": "blast;explosion;blow up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2506
    },
    {
        "Front": "暴露",
        "Back": "disclosure;exposure;revelation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2507
    },
    {
        "Front": "化ける",
        "Back": "to appear in disguise;to take the form of;to change for the worse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2508
    },
    {
        "Front": "罰",
        "Back": "(divine) punishment;curse;retribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2509
    },
    {
        "Front": "伐",
        "Back": "strike;attack;punish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2510
    },
    {
        "Front": "ばてる",
        "Back": "to be exhausted;to be worn out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "発条",
        "Back": "spring (e.g. coil&nbsp;&nbsp;leaf)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2511
    },
    {
        "Front": "散蒔く",
        "Back": "to disseminate;to scatter;to give money freely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2512
    },
    {
        "Front": "万",
        "Back": "many;all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2513
    },
    {
        "Front": "万人",
        "Back": "all people;everybody;10000 people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2514
    },
    {
        "Front": "万能",
        "Back": "all-purpose;almighty;omnipotent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2515
    },
    {
        "Front": "番目",
        "Back": "cardinal number suffix",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2516
    },
    {
        "Front": "非",
        "Back": "faulty-;non-",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2517
    },
    {
        "Front": "費",
        "Back": "cost;expense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2518
    },
    {
        "Front": "延いては",
        "Back": "not only...but also;in addition to;consequently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2519
    },
    {
        "Front": "控室",
        "Back": "waiting room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2520
    },
    {
        "Front": "控える",
        "Back": "to draw in;to hold back;to make notes;to be temperate in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2521
    },
    {
        "Front": "悲観",
        "Back": "pessimism;disappointment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2522
    },
    {
        "Front": "匹",
        "Back": "head;small animal counter;roll of cloth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2523
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き上げる",
        "Back": "to withdraw;to leave;to pull out;to retire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2524
    },
    {
        "Front": "率いる",
        "Back": "to lead;to spearhead (a group);to command (troops)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2525
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き受ける",
        "Back": "to undertake;to take up;to take over;to be responsible for;to guarantee;to contract (disease)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2526
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き起こす",
        "Back": "to cause",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2527
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き下げる",
        "Back": "to pull down;to lower;to reduce;to withdraw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2528
    },
    {
        "Front": "引きずる",
        "Back": "to seduce;to drag along;to pull;to prolong;to support",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2529
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き取る",
        "Back": "to take charge of;to take over;to retire to a private place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2530
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き分け",
        "Back": "a draw (in competition);tie game",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2531
    },
    {
        "Front": "否決",
        "Back": "rejection;negation;voting down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2532
    },
    {
        "Front": "非行",
        "Back": "delinquency;misconduct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2533
    },
    {
        "Front": "日頃",
        "Back": "normally;habitually",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2534
    },
    {
        "Front": "久しい",
        "Back": "long;long-continued;old (story)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2535
    },
    {
        "Front": "久し振り",
        "Back": "after a long time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2536
    },
    {
        "Front": "悲惨",
        "Back": "misery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2537
    },
    {
        "Front": "秘書",
        "Back": "(private) secretary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2538
    },
    {
        "Front": "比重",
        "Back": "specific gravity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2539
    },
    {
        "Front": "密か",
        "Back": "secret;private;surreptitious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2540
    },
    {
        "Front": "浸す",
        "Back": "to soak;to dip;to drench",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2541
    },
    {
        "Front": "一向",
        "Back": "earnestly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2542
    },
    {
        "Front": "左利き",
        "Back": "left-handedness;sake drinker;left-hander",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2543
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ掻く",
        "Back": "to scratch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2544
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ掛ける",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;to hang (something) on (something);to throw on (clothes); 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;to hook;to catch;to trap;to ensnar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2545
    },
    {
        "Front": "必修",
        "Back": "required (subject)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2546
    },
    {
        "Front": "匹敵",
        "Back": "comparing with;match;rival;equal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2547
    },
    {
        "Front": "未",
        "Back": "eighth sign of Chinese zodiac (The Ram&nbsp;&nbsp;1pm-3pm&nbsp;&nbsp;south-southwest&nbsp;&nbsp;June)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2548
    },
    {
        "Front": "必然",
        "Back": "inevitable;necessary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2549
    },
    {
        "Front": "一息",
        "Back": "puffy;a breath;a pause;an effort",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2550
    },
    {
        "Front": "単",
        "Back": "one layer;single",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2551
    },
    {
        "Front": "人柄",
        "Back": "personality;character;personal appearance;gentility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2552
    },
    {
        "Front": "一頃",
        "Back": "once;some time ago",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2553
    },
    {
        "Front": "人質",
        "Back": "hostage;prisoner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2554
    },
    {
        "Front": "一筋",
        "Back": "a line;earnestly;blindly;straightforwardly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2555
    },
    {
        "Front": "一まず",
        "Back": "for the present;once;in outline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2556
    },
    {
        "Front": "一人でに",
        "Back": "by itself;automatically;naturally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2557
    },
    {
        "Front": "酷い",
        "Back": "cruel;awful;severe;very bad;serious;terrible;heavy;violent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2558
    },
    {
        "Front": "日取り",
        "Back": "fixed date;appointed day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2559
    },
    {
        "Front": "雛",
        "Back": "young bird;chick;doll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2560
    },
    {
        "Front": "日向",
        "Back": "sunny place;in the sun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2561
    },
    {
        "Front": "非難",
        "Back": "blame;attack;criticism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2563
    },
    {
        "Front": "避難",
        "Back": "taking refuge;finding shelter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2562
    },
    {
        "Front": "日の丸",
        "Back": "the Japanese flag",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2564
    },
    {
        "Front": "火花",
        "Back": "spark",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2565
    },
    {
        "Front": "日々",
        "Back": "every day;daily;day after day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2566
    },
    {
        "Front": "悲鳴",
        "Back": "shriek;scream",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2567
    },
    {
        "Front": "百科事典",
        "Back": "encyclopedia",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2568
    },
    {
        "Front": "百科辞典",
        "Back": "encyclopedia",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2569
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷やかす",
        "Back": "to banter;to make fun of;to jeer at;to cool;to refrigerate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2570
    },
    {
        "Front": "日焼け",
        "Back": "sunburn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2571
    },
    {
        "Front": "票",
        "Back": "label;ballot;ticket;sign",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2572
    },
    {
        "Front": "標語",
        "Back": "motto;slogan;catchword",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2573
    },
    {
        "Front": "ひょっと",
        "Back": "possibly;accidentally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "平たい",
        "Back": "flat;even;level;simple;plain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2574
    },
    {
        "Front": "比率",
        "Back": "ratio;proportion;percentage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2575
    },
    {
        "Front": "肥料",
        "Back": "manure;fertilizer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2576
    },
    {
        "Front": "比例",
        "Back": "proportion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2577
    },
    {
        "Front": "疲労",
        "Back": "fatigue;weariness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2578
    },
    {
        "Front": "広まる",
        "Back": "to spread;to be propagated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2579
    },
    {
        "Front": "貧困",
        "Back": "poverty;lack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2580
    },
    {
        "Front": "品質",
        "Back": "quality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2581
    },
    {
        "Front": "品種",
        "Back": "brand;kind;description",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2582
    },
    {
        "Front": "貧弱",
        "Back": "poor;meagre;insubstantial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2583
    },
    {
        "Front": "頻繁",
        "Back": "frequency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2584
    },
    {
        "Front": "美",
        "Back": "beauty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2585
    },
    {
        "Front": "微笑",
        "Back": "smile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2586
    },
    {
        "Front": "美術",
        "Back": "art;fine arts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2587
    },
    {
        "Front": "吃驚",
        "Back": "be surprised;be amazed;be frightened;astonishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2588
    },
    {
        "Front": "びっしょり",
        "Back": "wet through;drenched",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "描写",
        "Back": "depiction;description;portrayal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2589
    },
    {
        "Front": "びり",
        "Back": "last on the list;at the bottom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "微量",
        "Back": "minuscule amount;extremely small quantity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2590
    },
    {
        "Front": "敏感",
        "Back": "sensibility;susceptibility;sensitive (to);well attuned to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2591
    },
    {
        "Front": "貧乏",
        "Back": "poverty;destitute;poor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2592
    },
    {
        "Front": "歩",
        "Back": "pawn (in chess or shogi)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2593
    },
    {
        "Front": "不意",
        "Back": "sudden;abrupt;unexpected;unforeseen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2594
    },
    {
        "Front": "封",
        "Back": "seal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2595
    },
    {
        "Front": "封鎖",
        "Back": "blockade;freezing (funds)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2596
    },
    {
        "Front": "風習",
        "Back": "custom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2597
    },
    {
        "Front": "風俗",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;manners;customs; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;sex service;sex industry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2598
    },
    {
        "Front": "風土",
        "Back": "natural features;topography;climate;spiritual features",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2599
    },
    {
        "Front": "不可欠",
        "Back": "indispensable;essential",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2600
    },
    {
        "Front": "深める",
        "Back": "to deepen;to heighten;to intensify",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2601
    },
    {
        "Front": "不吉",
        "Back": "ominous;sinister;bad luck;ill omen;inauspiciousness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2602
    },
    {
        "Front": "不況",
        "Back": "recession;depression;slump",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2603
    },
    {
        "Front": "布巾",
        "Back": "tea-towel;dish cloth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2604
    },
    {
        "Front": "福",
        "Back": "good fortune",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2605
    },
    {
        "Front": "復旧",
        "Back": "restoration;restitution;rehabilitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2606
    },
    {
        "Front": "複合",
        "Back": "composite;complex",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2607
    },
    {
        "Front": "福祉",
        "Back": "welfare;well-being",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2608
    },
    {
        "Front": "覆面",
        "Back": "mask;veil;disguise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2609
    },
    {
        "Front": "膨れる",
        "Back": "to get cross;to get sulky;to swell (out);to expand;to be inflated;to distend;to bulge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2610
    },
    {
        "Front": "不景気",
        "Back": "business recession;hard times;depression;gloom;sullenness;cheerlessness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2611
    },
    {
        "Front": "老ける",
        "Back": "to age",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2612
    },
    {
        "Front": "布告",
        "Back": "edict;ordinance;proclamation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2613
    },
    {
        "Front": "富豪",
        "Back": "wealthy person;millionaire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2614
    },
    {
        "Front": "負債",
        "Back": "debt;liabilities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2615
    },
    {
        "Front": "相応しい",
        "Back": "appropriate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2616
    },
    {
        "Front": "不在",
        "Back": "absence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2617
    },
    {
        "Front": "不山戯る",
        "Back": "to romp;to gambol;to frolic;to joke;to make fun of;to flirt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2618
    },
    {
        "Front": "負傷",
        "Back": "injury;wound",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2619
    },
    {
        "Front": "不審",
        "Back": "incomplete understanding;doubt;question;distrust;suspicion;strangeness;infidelity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2620
    },
    {
        "Front": "不振",
        "Back": "dullness;depression;slump;stagnation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2621
    },
    {
        "Front": "不順",
        "Back": "irregularity;unseasonableness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2622
    },
    {
        "Front": "付属",
        "Back": "attached;belonging;affiliated;annexed;associated;subordinate;incidental;dependent;auxiliary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2623
    },
    {
        "Front": "負担",
        "Back": "burden;charge;responsibility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2624
    },
    {
        "Front": "不調",
        "Back": "bad condition;not to work out (ie a deal);disagreement;break-off;disorder;slump;out of form",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2625
    },
    {
        "Front": "復活",
        "Back": "revival (e.g. musical);restoration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2626
    },
    {
        "Front": "復興",
        "Back": "revival;renaissance;reconstruction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2627
    },
    {
        "Front": "沸騰",
        "Back": "boiling;seething",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2628
    },
    {
        "Front": "仏",
        "Back": "French",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2629
    },
    {
        "Front": "不図",
        "Back": "suddenly;casually;accidentally;incidentally;unexpectedly;unintentionally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2630
    },
    {
        "Front": "不当",
        "Back": "injustice;impropriety;unreasonableness;undeservedness;unfair;invalid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2631
    },
    {
        "Front": "不動産",
        "Back": "real estate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2632
    },
    {
        "Front": "赴任",
        "Back": "(proceeding to) new appointment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2633
    },
    {
        "Front": "腐敗",
        "Back": "decay;depravity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2634
    },
    {
        "Front": "不評",
        "Back": "bad reputation;disgrace;unpopularity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2635
    },
    {
        "Front": "不便",
        "Back": "pity;compassion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2636
    },
    {
        "Front": "不服",
        "Back": "dissatisfaction;discontent;disapproval;objection;complaint;protest;disagreement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2637
    },
    {
        "Front": "普遍",
        "Back": "universality;ubiquity;omnipresence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2638
    },
    {
        "Front": "踏まえる",
        "Back": "to be based on;to have origin in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2639
    },
    {
        "Front": "文",
        "Back": "letter;writings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2640
    },
    {
        "Front": "不明",
        "Back": "unknown;obscure;indistinct;uncertain;ambiguous;ignorant;lack of wisdom;anonymous;unidentified",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2641
    },
    {
        "Front": "扶養",
        "Back": "support;maintenance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2642
    },
    {
        "Front": "振り",
        "Back": "pretence;show;appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2643
    },
    {
        "Front": "振り出し",
        "Back": "outset;starting point;drawing or issuing (draft)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2644
    },
    {
        "Front": "不良",
        "Back": "badness;delinquent;inferiority;failure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2645
    },
    {
        "Front": "浮力",
        "Back": "buoyancy;floating power",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2646
    },
    {
        "Front": "震わせる",
        "Back": "to be shaking;to be trembling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2647
    },
    {
        "Front": "付録",
        "Back": "appendix;supplement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2648
    },
    {
        "Front": "分",
        "Back": "minute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2649
    },
    {
        "Front": "憤慨",
        "Back": "indignation;resentment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2650
    },
    {
        "Front": "紛失",
        "Back": "losing something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2651
    },
    {
        "Front": "噴出",
        "Back": "spewing;gushing;spouting;eruption;effusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2652
    },
    {
        "Front": "紛争",
        "Back": "dispute;trouble;strife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2653
    },
    {
        "Front": "ふんだん",
        "Back": "plentiful;abundant;lavish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "奮闘",
        "Back": "hard struggle;strenuous effort",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2654
    },
    {
        "Front": "粉末",
        "Back": "fine powder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2655
    },
    {
        "Front": "部",
        "Back": "department;part;category;counter for copies of a newspaper or magazine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2656
    },
    {
        "Front": "部下",
        "Back": "subordinate person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2657
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶかぶか",
        "Back": "too big;baggy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "侮辱",
        "Back": "insult;contempt;slight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2658
    },
    {
        "Front": "武装",
        "Back": "arms;armament;armed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2659
    },
    {
        "Front": "斑",
        "Back": "spots;speckles;mottles",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2660
    },
    {
        "Front": "物資",
        "Back": "goods;materials",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2661
    },
    {
        "Front": "物体",
        "Back": "body;object",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2662
    },
    {
        "Front": "物議",
        "Back": "public discussion (criticism)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2663
    },
    {
        "Front": "打付ける",
        "Back": "to knock;to run into;to nail on;to strike hard;to hit and attack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2664
    },
    {
        "Front": "仏像",
        "Back": "Buddhist image (statue)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2665
    },
    {
        "Front": "無難",
        "Back": "safety;security",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2666
    },
    {
        "Front": "部門",
        "Back": "class;group;category;department;field;branch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2667
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶら下げる",
        "Back": "to hang;to suspend;to dangle;to swing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2668
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶらぶら",
        "Back": "dangle heavily;swing;sway to and fro;aimlessly;idly;lazily;loiter;loaf;be idle;stroll idly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "武力",
        "Back": "armed might;military power;the sword;force",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2669
    },
    {
        "Front": "無礼",
        "Back": "impolite;rude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2670
    },
    {
        "Front": "文化財",
        "Back": "cultural assets;cultural property",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2671
    },
    {
        "Front": "分業",
        "Back": "division of labor;specialization;assembly-line production",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2672
    },
    {
        "Front": "文語",
        "Back": "written language;literary language",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2673
    },
    {
        "Front": "分散",
        "Back": "dispersion;decentralization;variance (statistics)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2674
    },
    {
        "Front": "分子",
        "Back": "numerator;molecule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2675
    },
    {
        "Front": "文書",
        "Back": "document;writing;letter;note;records;archives",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2676
    },
    {
        "Front": "分担",
        "Back": "apportionment;sharing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2677
    },
    {
        "Front": "分配",
        "Back": "division;sharing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2678
    },
    {
        "Front": "分母",
        "Back": "denominator",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2679
    },
    {
        "Front": "分離",
        "Back": "separation;detachment;segregation;isolation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2680
    },
    {
        "Front": "分裂",
        "Back": "split;division;break up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2681
    },
    {
        "Front": "兵器",
        "Back": "arms;weapons;ordinance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2682
    },
    {
        "Front": "閉口",
        "Back": "shut mouth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2683
    },
    {
        "Front": "平行",
        "Back": "(going) side by side;concurrent;abreast;at the same time;occurring together;parallel;parallelism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2684
    },
    {
        "Front": "閉鎖",
        "Back": "closing;closure;shutdown;lockout;unsociable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2685
    },
    {
        "Front": "兵士",
        "Back": "soldier",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2686
    },
    {
        "Front": "平常",
        "Back": "normal;usual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2687
    },
    {
        "Front": "平方",
        "Back": "square (e.g. metre);square",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2688
    },
    {
        "Front": "並列",
        "Back": "arrangement;parallel;abreast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2689
    },
    {
        "Front": "辟易",
        "Back": "wince;shrink back;succumbing to;being frightened;disconcerted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2690
    },
    {
        "Front": "臍",
        "Back": "navel;belly-button",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2691
    },
    {
        "Front": "隔たる",
        "Back": "to be distant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2692
    },
    {
        "Front": "謙る",
        "Back": "to deprecate oneself and praise the listener",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2693
    },
    {
        "Front": "経る",
        "Back": "to pass;to elapse;to experience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2694
    },
    {
        "Front": "編",
        "Back": "compilation;editing;completed poem;book;part of book",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2695
    },
    {
        "Front": "偏",
        "Back": "side;left radical of a character;inclining;inclining toward;biased",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2696
    },
    {
        "Front": "変革",
        "Back": "change;reform;revolution;upheaval;(the) Reformation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2697
    },
    {
        "Front": "返還",
        "Back": "return;restoration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2698
    },
    {
        "Front": "偏見",
        "Back": "prejudice;narrow view",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2699
    },
    {
        "Front": "返済",
        "Back": "repayment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2700
    },
    {
        "Front": "変遷",
        "Back": "change;transition;vicissitudes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2701
    },
    {
        "Front": "返答",
        "Back": "reply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2702
    },
    {
        "Front": "変動",
        "Back": "change;fluctuation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2703
    },
    {
        "Front": "弁解",
        "Back": "explanation;justification;defence;excuse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2704
    },
    {
        "Front": "便宜",
        "Back": "convenience;accommodation;advantage;expedience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2705
    },
    {
        "Front": "弁護",
        "Back": "defense;pleading;advocacy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2706
    },
    {
        "Front": "弁償",
        "Back": "next word;compensation;reparation;indemnity;reimbursement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2707
    },
    {
        "Front": "弁論",
        "Back": "discussion;debate;argument",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2708
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぺこぺこ",
        "Back": "fawn;be very hungry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "穂",
        "Back": "ear (of plant);head (of plant)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2709
    },
    {
        "Front": "保育",
        "Back": "nursing;nurturing;rearing;lactation;suckling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2710
    },
    {
        "Front": "倣",
        "Back": "imitate;follow;emulate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2711
    },
    {
        "Front": "法案",
        "Back": "bill (law)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2712
    },
    {
        "Front": "崩壊",
        "Back": "collapse;decay (physics);crumbling;breaking down;caving in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2713
    },
    {
        "Front": "法学",
        "Back": "law;jurisprudence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2714
    },
    {
        "Front": "放棄",
        "Back": "abandonment;renunciation;abdication (responsibility&nbsp;&nbsp;right)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2715
    },
    {
        "Front": "宝器",
        "Back": "treasured article or vessel;outstanding individual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2716
    },
    {
        "Front": "封建",
        "Back": "feudalistic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2717
    },
    {
        "Front": "豊作",
        "Back": "abundant harvest;bumper crop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2718
    },
    {
        "Front": "方策",
        "Back": "plan;policy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2719
    },
    {
        "Front": "奉仕",
        "Back": "attendance;service",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2720
    },
    {
        "Front": "方式",
        "Back": "form;method;system",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2721
    },
    {
        "Front": "放射",
        "Back": "radiation;emission",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2722
    },
    {
        "Front": "放射能",
        "Back": "radioactivity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2723
    },
    {
        "Front": "報酬",
        "Back": "remuneration;recompense;reward;toll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2724
    },
    {
        "Front": "放出",
        "Back": "release;emit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2725
    },
    {
        "Front": "報じる",
        "Back": "to inform;to report",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2726
    },
    {
        "Front": "報ずる",
        "Back": "to inform;to report",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2727
    },
    {
        "Front": "放置",
        "Back": "leave as is;leave to chance;leave alone;neglect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2728
    },
    {
        "Front": "法廷",
        "Back": "courtroom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2729
    },
    {
        "Front": "報道",
        "Back": "information;report",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2730
    },
    {
        "Front": "褒美",
        "Back": "reward;prize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2731
    },
    {
        "Front": "葬る",
        "Back": "to bury;to inter;to entomb;to consign to oblivion;to shelve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2732
    },
    {
        "Front": "放り込む",
        "Back": "to throw into",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2733
    },
    {
        "Front": "放り出す",
        "Back": "to throw out;to fire;to expel;to give up;to abandon;to neglect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2734
    },
    {
        "Front": "飽和",
        "Back": "saturation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2735
    },
    {
        "Front": "保温",
        "Back": "retaining warmth;keeping heat in;heat insulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2736
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕獲",
        "Back": "capture;seizure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2737
    },
    {
        "Front": "保管",
        "Back": "charge;custody;safekeeping;deposit;storage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2738
    },
    {
        "Front": "補給",
        "Back": "supply;supplying;replenishment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2739
    },
    {
        "Front": "補強",
        "Back": "compensation;reinforcement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2740
    },
    {
        "Front": "保険",
        "Back": "insurance;guarantee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2741
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕鯨",
        "Back": "whaling;whale fishing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2742
    },
    {
        "Front": "誇る",
        "Back": "to boast of;to be proud of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2743
    },
    {
        "Front": "綻びる",
        "Back": "to come apart at the seams;to begin to open;to smile broadly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2744
    },
    {
        "Front": "保護",
        "Back": "care;protection;shelter;guardianship;favor;patronage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2745
    },
    {
        "Front": "干し物",
        "Back": "dried washing (clothes)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2746
    },
    {
        "Front": "保守",
        "Back": "conservative;maintaining",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2747
    },
    {
        "Front": "保障",
        "Back": "guarantee;security;assurance;pledge;warranty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2748
    },
    {
        "Front": "補償",
        "Back": "compensation;reparation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2749
    },
    {
        "Front": "補充",
        "Back": "supplementation;supplement;replenishment;replenishing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2750
    },
    {
        "Front": "補助",
        "Back": "assistance;support;aid;auxiliary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2751
    },
    {
        "Front": "舗装",
        "Back": "pavement;road surface",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2752
    },
    {
        "Front": "補足",
        "Back": "supplement;complement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2753
    },
    {
        "Front": "発作",
        "Back": "fit;spasm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2754
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほっと",
        "Back": "feel relieved",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "頬っぺた",
        "Back": "cheek",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2755
    },
    {
        "Front": "辺り",
        "Back": "(in the) neighbourhood;vicinity;nearby",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2756
    },
    {
        "Front": "殆ど",
        "Back": "mostly;almost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2757
    },
    {
        "Front": "解く",
        "Back": "to unfasten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2758
    },
    {
        "Front": "施す",
        "Back": "to donate;to give;to conduct;to apply;to perform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2759
    },
    {
        "Front": "保母",
        "Back": "day care worker in a kindergarten&nbsp;&nbsp;nursery school&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2760
    },
    {
        "Front": "保養",
        "Back": "health preservation;recuperation;recreation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2761
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕吏",
        "Back": "constable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2762
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕虜",
        "Back": "prisoner (of war)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2763
    },
    {
        "Front": "滅びる",
        "Back": "to be ruined;to go under;to perish;to be destroyed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2764
    },
    {
        "Front": "滅ぼす",
        "Back": "to destroy;to overthrow;to wreck;to ruin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2765
    },
    {
        "Front": "本格",
        "Back": "propriety;fundamental rules",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2766
    },
    {
        "Front": "本館",
        "Back": "main building",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2767
    },
    {
        "Front": "本気",
        "Back": "seriousness;truth;sanctity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2768
    },
    {
        "Front": "本質",
        "Back": "essence;true nature;reality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2769
    },
    {
        "Front": "本体",
        "Back": "substance;real form;object of worship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2770
    },
    {
        "Front": "本音",
        "Back": "real intention;motive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2771
    },
    {
        "Front": "本の",
        "Back": "mere;only;just",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2772
    },
    {
        "Front": "本能",
        "Back": "instinct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2773
    },
    {
        "Front": "本場",
        "Back": "home;habitat;center;best place;genuine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2774
    },
    {
        "Front": "本文",
        "Back": "text (of document);body (of letter)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2775
    },
    {
        "Front": "本名",
        "Back": "real name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2776
    },
    {
        "Front": "卯",
        "Back": "fourth sign of Chinese zodiac (The Hare&nbsp;&nbsp;5am-7am&nbsp;&nbsp;east&nbsp;&nbsp;February)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2777
    },
    {
        "Front": "防衛",
        "Back": "defense;protection;self-defense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2778
    },
    {
        "Front": "防火",
        "Back": "fire prevention;fire fighting;fire proof",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2779
    },
    {
        "Front": "妨害",
        "Back": "disturbance;obstruction;hindrance;jamming;interference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2780
    },
    {
        "Front": "紡績",
        "Back": "spinning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2781
    },
    {
        "Front": "呆然",
        "Back": "dumbfounded;overcome with surprise;in blank amazement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2782
    },
    {
        "Front": "膨脹",
        "Back": "expansion;swelling;increase;growth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2783
    },
    {
        "Front": "冒頭",
        "Back": "beginning;start;outset",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2784
    },
    {
        "Front": "暴動",
        "Back": "insurrection;rebellion;revolt;riot;uprising",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2785
    },
    {
        "Front": "暴風",
        "Back": "storm;windstorm;gale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2786
    },
    {
        "Front": "暴力",
        "Back": "violence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2787
    },
    {
        "Front": "募金",
        "Back": "fund-raising;collection of funds",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2788
    },
    {
        "Front": "牧師",
        "Back": "pastor;minister;clergyman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2789
    },
    {
        "Front": "母校",
        "Back": "alma mater",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2790
    },
    {
        "Front": "没収",
        "Back": "forfeited",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2791
    },
    {
        "Front": "坊ちゃん",
        "Back": "son (of others)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2792
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぼつぼつ",
        "Back": "gradually;here and there;spots;pimples",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "没落",
        "Back": "ruin;fall;collapse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2793
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぼやく",
        "Back": "to grumble;to complain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぼやける",
        "Back": "to become dim;to become blurred",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "藍褸",
        "Back": "rag;scrap;tattered clothes;fault (esp. in a pretense);defect;run-down or junky",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2794
    },
    {
        "Front": "枚",
        "Back": "counter for flat objects (e.g. sheets of paper)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2795
    },
    {
        "Front": "埋蔵",
        "Back": "buried property;treasure trove",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2796
    },
    {
        "Front": "舞う",
        "Back": "to dance;to flutter about;to revolve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2797
    },
    {
        "Front": "真上",
        "Back": "just above;right overhead",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2798
    },
    {
        "Front": "前売り",
        "Back": "advance sale;booking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2799
    },
    {
        "Front": "前置き",
        "Back": "preface;introduction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2800
    },
    {
        "Front": "前もって",
        "Back": "in advance;beforehand;previously",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2801
    },
    {
        "Front": "任す",
        "Back": "to entrust;to leave to a person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2802
    },
    {
        "Front": "負かす",
        "Back": "to defeat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2803
    },
    {
        "Front": "賄う",
        "Back": "to give board to;to provide meals;to pay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2804
    },
    {
        "Front": "曲がる",
        "Back": "to turn;to bend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2805
    },
    {
        "Front": "巻",
        "Back": "volume",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2806
    },
    {
        "Front": "紛らわしい",
        "Back": "confusing;misleading;equivocal;ambiguous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2807
    },
    {
        "Front": "紛れる",
        "Back": "to be diverted;to slip into",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2808
    },
    {
        "Front": "膜",
        "Back": "membrane;film",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2809
    },
    {
        "Front": "捲る",
        "Back": "verb suffix to indicate reckless abandon to the activity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2810
    },
    {
        "Front": "真心",
        "Back": "sincerity;devotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2811
    },
    {
        "Front": "誠",
        "Back": "truth;faith;fidelity;sincerity;trust;confidence;reliance;devotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2812
    },
    {
        "Front": "真に",
        "Back": "truly;actually;really",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2813
    },
    {
        "Front": "まごつく",
        "Back": "to be confused;to be flustered",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "正しく",
        "Back": "surely;no doubt;evidently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2814
    },
    {
        "Front": "正に",
        "Back": "correctly;surely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2815
    },
    {
        "Front": "勝る",
        "Back": "to excel;to surpass;to outrival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2816
    },
    {
        "Front": "増し",
        "Back": "extra;additional;less objectionable;better;preferable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2817
    },
    {
        "Front": "真下",
        "Back": "right under;directly below",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2818
    },
    {
        "Front": "況して",
        "Back": "still more;still less (with neg. verb);to say nothing of;not to mention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2819
    },
    {
        "Front": "交える",
        "Back": "to mix;to converse with;to cross (swords)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2820
    },
    {
        "Front": "交わる",
        "Back": "to cross;to intersect;to associate with;to mingle with;to interest;to join",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2821
    },
    {
        "Front": "麻酔",
        "Back": "anaesthesia",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2822
    },
    {
        "Front": "益々",
        "Back": "increasingly;more and more",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2823
    },
    {
        "Front": "不味い",
        "Back": "unappetising;unpleasant (taste&nbsp;&nbsp;appearance&nbsp;&nbsp;situation);ugly;unskilful;awkward;bungling;unwise;untime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2824
    },
    {
        "Front": "股",
        "Back": "groin;crotch;thigh",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2825
    },
    {
        "Front": "跨がる",
        "Back": "to extend over or into;to straddle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2826
    },
    {
        "Front": "跨ぐ",
        "Back": "to straddle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2827
    },
    {
        "Front": "瞬き",
        "Back": "wink;twinkling (of stars);flicker (of light)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2828
    },
    {
        "Front": "待ち合わせ",
        "Back": "appointment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2829
    },
    {
        "Front": "間違う",
        "Back": "to make a mistake;to be incorrect;to be mistaken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2830
    },
    {
        "Front": "待ち遠しい",
        "Back": "looking forward to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2831
    },
    {
        "Front": "待ち望む",
        "Back": "to look anxiously for;to wait eagerly for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2832
    },
    {
        "Front": "区々",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;several;various;divergent;conflicting;different;diverse; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;trivial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2833
    },
    {
        "Front": "末期",
        "Back": "closing years (period&nbsp;&nbsp;days);last stage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2834
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ二つ",
        "Back": "in two equal parts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2835
    },
    {
        "Front": "纏まり",
        "Back": "conclusion;settlement;consistency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2836
    },
    {
        "Front": "纏め",
        "Back": "settlement;conclusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2837
    },
    {
        "Front": "免れる",
        "Back": "to escape from;to be rescued from;to avoid;to evade;to avert;to elude;to be exempted;to be relieved",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2838
    },
    {
        "Front": "招き",
        "Back": "invitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2839
    },
    {
        "Front": "麻痺",
        "Back": "paralysis;palsy;numbness;stupor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2840
    },
    {
        "Front": "眩しい",
        "Back": "dazzling;radiant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2841
    },
    {
        "Front": "目蓋",
        "Back": "eyelid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2842
    },
    {
        "Front": "間々",
        "Back": "occasionally;frequently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2843
    },
    {
        "Front": "間もなく",
        "Back": "soon;before long;in a short time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2844
    },
    {
        "Front": "眉",
        "Back": "eyebrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2845
    },
    {
        "Front": "鞠",
        "Back": "ball",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2846
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸ごと",
        "Back": "in its entirety;whole;wholly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2847
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸っきり",
        "Back": "completely;perfectly;just as if",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2848
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸で",
        "Back": "quite;entirely;completely;at all;as if;as though;so to speak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2849
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸々",
        "Back": "completely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2850
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸める",
        "Back": "to make round;to round off;to roll up;to curl up;to seduce;to cajole;to explain away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2851
    },
    {
        "Front": "満月",
        "Back": "full moon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2852
    },
    {
        "Front": "満場",
        "Back": "unanimous;whole audience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2853
    },
    {
        "Front": "真ん中",
        "Back": "middle;centre;mid-way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2854
    },
    {
        "Front": "真ん前",
        "Back": "right in front;under the nose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2855
    },
    {
        "Front": "真ん丸い",
        "Back": "perfectly circular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2856
    },
    {
        "Front": "三",
        "Back": "(num) three",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2857
    },
    {
        "Front": "見合い",
        "Back": "formal marriage interview",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2858
    },
    {
        "Front": "見合わせる",
        "Back": "to exchange glances;to postpone;to suspend operations;to refrain from performing an action",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2859
    },
    {
        "Front": "見落とす",
        "Back": "to overlook;to fail to notice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2860
    },
    {
        "Front": "未開",
        "Back": "savage land;backward region;uncivilized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2861
    },
    {
        "Front": "味覚",
        "Back": "taste;palate;sense of taste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2862
    },
    {
        "Front": "見掛ける",
        "Back": "to (happen to) see;to notice;to catch sight of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2863
    },
    {
        "Front": "三日月",
        "Back": "new moon;crescent moon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2864
    },
    {
        "Front": "見方",
        "Back": "viewpoint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2865
    },
    {
        "Front": "見苦しい",
        "Back": "unsightly;ugly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2866
    },
    {
        "Front": "見込み",
        "Back": "hope;prospects;expectation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2867
    },
    {
        "Front": "未婚",
        "Back": "unmarried",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2868
    },
    {
        "Front": "惨め",
        "Back": "miserable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2869
    },
    {
        "Front": "未熟",
        "Back": "inexperience;unripeness;raw;unskilled;immature;inexperienced",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2870
    },
    {
        "Front": "微塵",
        "Back": "particle;atom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2871
    },
    {
        "Front": "見すぼらしい",
        "Back": "shabby;seedy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2872
    },
    {
        "Front": "見せびらかす",
        "Back": "to show off;to flaunt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2873
    },
    {
        "Front": "見せ物",
        "Back": "show;exhibition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2874
    },
    {
        "Front": "満たす",
        "Back": "to satisfy;to ingratiate;to fill;to fulfill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2875
    },
    {
        "Front": "乱す",
        "Back": "to throw out of order;to disarrange;to disturb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2876
    },
    {
        "Front": "乱れる",
        "Back": "to get confused;to be disordered;to be disturbed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2877
    },
    {
        "Front": "未知",
        "Back": "not yet known",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2878
    },
    {
        "Front": "導く",
        "Back": "to be guided;to be shown",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2879
    },
    {
        "Front": "身近",
        "Back": "near oneself;close to one;familiar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2880
    },
    {
        "Front": "密集",
        "Back": "crowd;close formation;dense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2881
    },
    {
        "Front": "密接",
        "Back": "related;connected;close;intimate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2882
    },
    {
        "Front": "見っともない",
        "Back": "shameful;indecent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2883
    },
    {
        "Front": "蜜",
        "Back": "nectar;honey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2884
    },
    {
        "Front": "密度",
        "Back": "density",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2885
    },
    {
        "Front": "見積り",
        "Back": "estimation;quotation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2886
    },
    {
        "Front": "未定",
        "Back": "not yet fixed;undecided;pending",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2887
    },
    {
        "Front": "見通し",
        "Back": "perspective;unobstructed view;outlook;forecast;prospect;insight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2888
    },
    {
        "Front": "源",
        "Back": "source;origin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2889
    },
    {
        "Front": "身なり",
        "Back": "personal appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2890
    },
    {
        "Front": "峰",
        "Back": "peak;ridge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2891
    },
    {
        "Front": "見逃す",
        "Back": "to miss;to overlook;to leave at large",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2892
    },
    {
        "Front": "見晴らし",
        "Back": "view",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2893
    },
    {
        "Front": "身振り",
        "Back": "gesture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2894
    },
    {
        "Front": "見舞",
        "Back": "enquiry;expression of sympathy;expression of concern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2895
    },
    {
        "Front": "脈",
        "Back": "pulse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2896
    },
    {
        "Front": "未練",
        "Back": "lingering affection;attachment;regret(s);reluctance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2897
    },
    {
        "Front": "見渡す",
        "Back": "to look out over;to survey (scene);to take an extensive view of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2898
    },
    {
        "Front": "民主",
        "Back": "democratic;the head of the nation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2899
    },
    {
        "Front": "民宿",
        "Back": "private home providing lodging for travelers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2900
    },
    {
        "Front": "民族",
        "Back": "people;race;nation;racial customs;folk customs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2901
    },
    {
        "Front": "民俗",
        "Back": "people;race;nation;racial customs;folk customs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2902
    },
    {
        "Front": "六",
        "Back": "(num) six",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2903
    },
    {
        "Front": "無意味",
        "Back": "nonsense;no meaning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2904
    },
    {
        "Front": "向き",
        "Back": "direction;situation;exposure;aspect;suitability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2905
    },
    {
        "Front": "無口",
        "Back": "reticence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2906
    },
    {
        "Front": "向け",
        "Back": "for ~;oriented towards ~",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2907
    },
    {
        "Front": "婿",
        "Back": "son-in-law",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2908
    },
    {
        "Front": "無効",
        "Back": "invalid;no effect;unavailable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2909
    },
    {
        "Front": "無言",
        "Back": "silence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2910
    },
    {
        "Front": "毟る",
        "Back": "to pluck;to pick;to tear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2911
    },
    {
        "Front": "無邪気",
        "Back": "innocence;simple-mindedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2912
    },
    {
        "Front": "結び",
        "Back": "ending;conclusion;union",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2913
    },
    {
        "Front": "結び付き",
        "Back": "connection;relation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2914
    },
    {
        "Front": "結び付く",
        "Back": "to be connected or related;to join together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2915
    },
    {
        "Front": "結び付ける",
        "Back": "to combine;to join;to tie on;to attach with a knot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2916
    },
    {
        "Front": "無線",
        "Back": "wireless;radio",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2917
    },
    {
        "Front": "無駄遣い",
        "Back": "waste money on;squander money on;flog a dead horse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2918
    },
    {
        "Front": "無断",
        "Back": "without permission;without notice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2919
    },
    {
        "Front": "無知",
        "Back": "ignorance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2920
    },
    {
        "Front": "無茶",
        "Back": "absurd;unreasonable;excessive;rash;absurdity;nonsense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2921
    },
    {
        "Front": "無茶苦茶",
        "Back": "confused;jumbled;mixed up;unreasonable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2922
    },
    {
        "Front": "空しい",
        "Back": "vacant;futile;vain;void;empty;ineffective;lifeless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2923
    },
    {
        "Front": "無念",
        "Back": "chagrin;regret",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2924
    },
    {
        "Front": "無能",
        "Back": "inefficiency;incompetence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2925
    },
    {
        "Front": "無闇に",
        "Back": "unreasonably;absurdly;recklessly;indiscreetly;at random",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2926
    },
    {
        "Front": "無用",
        "Back": "useless;futility;needlessness;unnecessariness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2927
    },
    {
        "Front": "群がる",
        "Back": "to swarm;to gather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2928
    },
    {
        "Front": "無論",
        "Back": "of course;naturally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2929
    },
    {
        "Front": "名産",
        "Back": "noted product",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2930
    },
    {
        "Front": "名称",
        "Back": "name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2931
    },
    {
        "Front": "命中",
        "Back": "a hit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2932
    },
    {
        "Front": "名簿",
        "Back": "register of names",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2933
    },
    {
        "Front": "名誉",
        "Back": "honor;credit;prestige",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2934
    },
    {
        "Front": "明瞭",
        "Back": "clarity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2935
    },
    {
        "Front": "明朗",
        "Back": "bright;clear;cheerful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2936
    },
    {
        "Front": "目方",
        "Back": "weight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2937
    },
    {
        "Front": "恵み",
        "Back": "blessing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2938
    },
    {
        "Front": "恵む",
        "Back": "to bless;to show mercy to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2939
    },
    {
        "Front": "目覚しい",
        "Back": "brilliant;splendid;striking;remarkable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2940
    },
    {
        "Front": "目覚める",
        "Back": "to wake up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2941
    },
    {
        "Front": "召す",
        "Back": "to call;to send for;to put on;to wear;to take (a bath);to ride in;to buy;to eat;to drink;to catch (a",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2942
    },
    {
        "Front": "雌",
        "Back": "female (animal)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2943
    },
    {
        "Front": "滅茶苦茶",
        "Back": "absurd;unreasonable;excessive;messed up;spoiled;wreaked",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2944
    },
    {
        "Front": "目付き",
        "Back": "look;expression of the eyes;eyes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2945
    },
    {
        "Front": "滅亡",
        "Back": "downfall;ruin;collapse;destruction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2946
    },
    {
        "Front": "愛でたい",
        "Back": "auspicious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2947
    },
    {
        "Front": "目眩",
        "Back": "dizziness;giddiness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2948
    },
    {
        "Front": "目盛",
        "Back": "scale;gradations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2949
    },
    {
        "Front": "面会",
        "Back": "interview",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2950
    },
    {
        "Front": "免除",
        "Back": "exemption;exoneration;discharge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2951
    },
    {
        "Front": "面する",
        "Back": "to face on;to look out on to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2952
    },
    {
        "Front": "面目",
        "Back": "face;honour;reputation;prestige;dignity;credit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2953
    },
    {
        "Front": "設ける",
        "Back": "to create;to establish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2954
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し入れる",
        "Back": "to propose;to suggest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2955
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し込み",
        "Back": "application;entry;request;subscription;offer;proposal;overture;challenge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2956
    },
    {
        "Front": "申出",
        "Back": "proposal;request;claim;report;notice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2957
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し出る",
        "Back": "to report to;to tell;to suggest;to submit;to request;to make an offer;to come forward with informati",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2958
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し分",
        "Back": "objection;shortcomings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2959
    },
    {
        "Front": "盲点",
        "Back": "blind spot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2960
    },
    {
        "Front": "猛烈",
        "Back": "violent;vehement;rage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2961
    },
    {
        "Front": "藻掻く",
        "Back": "to struggle;to wriggle;to be impatient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2962
    },
    {
        "Front": "目録",
        "Back": "catalogue;catalog;list",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2963
    },
    {
        "Front": "目論見",
        "Back": "a plan;a scheme;a project;a program;intention;goal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2964
    },
    {
        "Front": "模型",
        "Back": "model;dummy;maquette",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2965
    },
    {
        "Front": "模索",
        "Back": "groping (for)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2966
    },
    {
        "Front": "若し",
        "Back": "if;in case;supposing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2967
    },
    {
        "Front": "若しかしたら",
        "Back": "perhaps;maybe;by some chance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2968
    },
    {
        "Front": "若しかして",
        "Back": "perhaps;possibly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2969
    },
    {
        "Front": "若しかすると",
        "Back": "perhaps;maybe;by some chance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2970
    },
    {
        "Front": "若しくは",
        "Back": "or;otherwise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2971
    },
    {
        "Front": "若しも",
        "Back": "if",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2972
    },
    {
        "Front": "齎らす",
        "Back": "to bring;to take;to bring about",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2973
    },
    {
        "Front": "凭れる",
        "Back": "to lean against;to lean on;to recline on;to lie heavy (on the stomach)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2974
    },
    {
        "Front": "持ち",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;hold;charge;keep possession;in charge; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;wear;durability;life;draw; 3.&nbsp;&nbsp;usage (suff)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2975
    },
    {
        "Front": "持ち切り",
        "Back": "hot topic;talk of the town",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2976
    },
    {
        "Front": "物体ない",
        "Back": "too good;more than one deserves;wasteful;sacrilegious;unworthy of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2977
    },
    {
        "Front": "以て",
        "Back": "with;by;by means of;because;in view of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2978
    },
    {
        "Front": "専ら",
        "Back": "wholly;solely;entirely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2979
    },
    {
        "Front": "持て成す",
        "Back": "to entertain;to make welcome",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2980
    },
    {
        "Front": "持てる",
        "Back": "to be well liked;to be popular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2981
    },
    {
        "Front": "基",
        "Back": "basis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2982
    },
    {
        "Front": "物置き",
        "Back": "storeroom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2983
    },
    {
        "Front": "物好き",
        "Back": "curiosity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2984
    },
    {
        "Front": "物足りない",
        "Back": "unsatisfied;unsatisfactory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2985
    },
    {
        "Front": "最早",
        "Back": "already;now",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2986
    },
    {
        "Front": "模範",
        "Back": "exemplar;exemplification;exemplum;model;example",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2987
    },
    {
        "Front": "模倣",
        "Back": "imitation;copying",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2988
    },
    {
        "Front": "揉める",
        "Back": "to disagree;to dispute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2989
    },
    {
        "Front": "腿",
        "Back": "thigh;femur",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2990
    },
    {
        "Front": "催す",
        "Back": "to hold (a meeting);to give (a dinner);to feel;to show signs of;to develop symptoms of;to feel (sick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2991
    },
    {
        "Front": "漏らす",
        "Back": "to let leak;to reveal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2992
    },
    {
        "Front": "盛り上がる",
        "Back": "to rouse;to swell;to rise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2993
    },
    {
        "Front": "漏る",
        "Back": "to leak;to run out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2994
    },
    {
        "Front": "漏れる",
        "Back": "to leak out;to escape;to come through;to shine through;to filter out;to be omitted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2995
    },
    {
        "Front": "脆い",
        "Back": "brittle;fragile;tender-hearted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2996
    },
    {
        "Front": "もろに",
        "Back": "completely;all the way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "問",
        "Back": "problem;question",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2997
    },
    {
        "Front": "矢",
        "Back": "arrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2998
    },
    {
        "Front": "哉",
        "Back": "question mark",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2999
    },
    {
        "Front": "喧しい",
        "Back": "noisy;strict;fussy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3000
    },
    {
        "Front": "野外",
        "Back": "fields;outskirts;open air;suburbs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3001
    },
    {
        "Front": "軈て",
        "Back": "before long;soon;at length",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3002
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜行",
        "Back": "walking around at night;night train;night travel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3003
    },
    {
        "Front": "役職",
        "Back": "post;managerial position;official position",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3004
    },
    {
        "Front": "役立つ",
        "Back": "to be useful;to be helpful;to serve the purpose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3005
    },
    {
        "Front": "役場",
        "Back": "town hall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3006
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜具",
        "Back": "bedding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3007
    },
    {
        "Front": "優",
        "Back": "gentle;affectionate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3008
    },
    {
        "Front": "屋敷",
        "Back": "mansion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3009
    },
    {
        "Front": "養う",
        "Back": "to rear;to maintain;to cultivate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3010
    },
    {
        "Front": "社",
        "Back": "Shinto shrine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3011
    },
    {
        "Front": "野心",
        "Back": "ambition;aspiration;designs;treachery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3012
    },
    {
        "Front": "易い",
        "Back": "easy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3013
    },
    {
        "Front": "安っぽい",
        "Back": "cheap-looking;tawdry;insignificant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3014
    },
    {
        "Front": "休める",
        "Back": "to rest;to suspend;to give relief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3015
    },
    {
        "Front": "野生",
        "Back": "wild",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3016
    },
    {
        "Front": "矢鱈に",
        "Back": "randomly;recklessly;blindly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3017
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜中",
        "Back": "all night;the whole night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3018
    },
    {
        "Front": "奴",
        "Back": "servant;fellow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3019
    },
    {
        "Front": "やっ付ける",
        "Back": "to beat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3020
    },
    {
        "Front": "矢っ張り",
        "Back": "also;as I thought;still;in spite of;absolutely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3021
    },
    {
        "Front": "野党",
        "Back": "opposition party",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3022
    },
    {
        "Front": "病",
        "Back": "illness;disease",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3023
    },
    {
        "Front": "闇",
        "Back": "darkness;the dark;black-marketeering;dark;shady;illegal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3024
    },
    {
        "Front": "病む",
        "Back": "to fall ill;to be ill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3025
    },
    {
        "Front": "止むを得ない",
        "Back": "cannot be helped;unavoidable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3026
    },
    {
        "Front": "稍",
        "Back": "a little;partially;somewhat;a short time;a while",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3027
    },
    {
        "Front": "ややこしい",
        "Back": "puzzling;tangled;complicated;complex",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "遣り通す",
        "Back": "to carry through;to achieve;to complete",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3028
    },
    {
        "Front": "やり遂げる",
        "Back": "to accomplish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3029
    },
    {
        "Front": "遣る",
        "Back": "to do;to have sexual intercourse;to kill;to give (to inferiors&nbsp;&nbsp;animals&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.);to dispatch (a letter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3030
    },
    {
        "Front": "和らげる",
        "Back": "to soften;to moderate;to relieve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3031
    },
    {
        "Front": "優位",
        "Back": "predominance;ascendancy;superiority",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3032
    },
    {
        "Front": "憂鬱",
        "Back": "depression;melancholy;dejection;gloom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3033
    },
    {
        "Front": "有益",
        "Back": "beneficial;profitable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3034
    },
    {
        "Front": "優越",
        "Back": "supremacy;predominance;being superior to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3035
    },
    {
        "Front": "勇敢",
        "Back": "bravery;heroism;gallantry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3036
    },
    {
        "Front": "有機",
        "Back": "organic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3037
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕暮れ",
        "Back": "evening;(evening) twilight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3038
    },
    {
        "Front": "融資",
        "Back": "financing;loan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3039
    },
    {
        "Front": "有する",
        "Back": "to own;to be endowed with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3040
    },
    {
        "Front": "融通",
        "Back": "lending (money);accommodation;adaptability;versatility;finance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3041
    },
    {
        "Front": "優勢",
        "Back": "superiority;superior power;predominance;preponderance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3042
    },
    {
        "Front": "優先",
        "Back": "preference;priority",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3043
    },
    {
        "Front": "誘導",
        "Back": "guidance;leading;induction;introduction;incitement;inducement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3044
    },
    {
        "Front": "優美",
        "Back": "grace;refinement;elegance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3045
    },
    {
        "Front": "有望",
        "Back": "good prospects;full of hope;promising",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3046
    },
    {
        "Front": "遊牧",
        "Back": "nomadism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3047
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕焼け",
        "Back": "sunset",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3048
    },
    {
        "Front": "有力",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;influence;prominence; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;potent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3049
    },
    {
        "Front": "幽霊",
        "Back": "ghost;specter;apparition;phantom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3050
    },
    {
        "Front": "誘惑",
        "Back": "temptation;allurement;lure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3051
    },
    {
        "Front": "揺さぶる",
        "Back": "to shake;to jolt;to rock;to swing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3052
    },
    {
        "Front": "茹でる",
        "Back": "to boil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3053
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゆとり",
        "Back": "reserve;affluence;room;time (to spare)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "指差す",
        "Back": "to point at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3054
    },
    {
        "Front": "弓",
        "Back": "bow (and arrow)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3055
    },
    {
        "Front": "揺らぐ",
        "Back": "to swing;to sway;to shake;to tremble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3056
    },
    {
        "Front": "緩む",
        "Back": "to become loose;to slacken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3057
    },
    {
        "Front": "緩める",
        "Back": "to loosen;to slow down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3058
    },
    {
        "Front": "緩やか",
        "Back": "lenient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3059
    },
    {
        "Front": "世",
        "Back": "world;society;age;generation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3060
    },
    {
        "Front": "好い",
        "Back": "good",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3061
    },
    {
        "Front": "要因",
        "Back": "primary factor;main cause",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3062
    },
    {
        "Front": "溶液",
        "Back": "solution (liquid)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3063
    },
    {
        "Front": "用件",
        "Back": "business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3064
    },
    {
        "Front": "養護",
        "Back": "protection;nursing;protective care",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3065
    },
    {
        "Front": "用紙",
        "Back": "blank form",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3066
    },
    {
        "Front": "様式",
        "Back": "style;form;pattern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3067
    },
    {
        "Front": "要する",
        "Back": "to demand;to require;to take",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3068
    },
    {
        "Front": "要請",
        "Back": "claim;demand;request;application",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3069
    },
    {
        "Front": "養成",
        "Back": "training;development",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3070
    },
    {
        "Front": "様相",
        "Back": "aspect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3071
    },
    {
        "Front": "用品",
        "Back": "articles;supplies;parts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3072
    },
    {
        "Front": "洋風",
        "Back": "western style",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3073
    },
    {
        "Front": "用法",
        "Back": "directions;rules of use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3074
    },
    {
        "Front": "要望",
        "Back": "demand for;request",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3075
    },
    {
        "Front": "余暇",
        "Back": "leisure;leisure time;spare time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3076
    },
    {
        "Front": "予感",
        "Back": "presentiment;premonition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3077
    },
    {
        "Front": "余興",
        "Back": "side show;entertainment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3078
    },
    {
        "Front": "預金",
        "Back": "deposit;bank account",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3079
    },
    {
        "Front": "抑圧",
        "Back": "check;restraint;oppression;suppression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3080
    },
    {
        "Front": "浴室",
        "Back": "bathroom;bath",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3081
    },
    {
        "Front": "抑制",
        "Back": "suppression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3082
    },
    {
        "Front": "欲深い",
        "Back": "greedy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3083
    },
    {
        "Front": "欲望",
        "Back": "desire;appetite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3084
    },
    {
        "Front": "寄こす",
        "Back": "to send;to forward",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3085
    },
    {
        "Front": "横綱",
        "Back": "sumo grand champion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3086
    },
    {
        "Front": "葦",
        "Back": "reed;bulrush",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3087
    },
    {
        "Front": "善し悪し",
        "Back": "good or bad;merits or demerits;quality;suitability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3088
    },
    {
        "Front": "予想",
        "Back": "expectation;anticipation;prediction;forecast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3089
    },
    {
        "Front": "余所見",
        "Back": "looking away;looking aside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3090
    },
    {
        "Front": "余地",
        "Back": "place;room;margin;scope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3091
    },
    {
        "Front": "依って",
        "Back": "therefore;consequently;accordingly;because of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3092
    },
    {
        "Front": "余程",
        "Back": "very;greatly;much;to a large extent;quite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3093
    },
    {
        "Front": "与党",
        "Back": "government party;(ruling) party in power;government",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3094
    },
    {
        "Front": "呼び止める",
        "Back": "to challenge;to call somebody to halt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3095
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜更かし",
        "Back": "staying up late;keeping late hours;sitting up late at night;nighthawk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3096
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜更け",
        "Back": "late at night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3097
    },
    {
        "Front": "読み上げる",
        "Back": "to read out loud (and clearly);to call a roll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3098
    },
    {
        "Front": "寄り掛かる",
        "Back": "to lean against;to recline on;to lean on;to rely on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3099
    },
    {
        "Front": "宜しく",
        "Back": "well;properly;suitably;best regards;please remember me",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3100
    },
    {
        "Front": "弱まる",
        "Back": "to abate;to weaken;to be emaciated;to be dejected;to be perplexed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3101
    },
    {
        "Front": "弱める",
        "Back": "to weaken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3102
    },
    {
        "Front": "弱る",
        "Back": "to weaken;to be troubled;to be downcast;to be emaciated;to be dejected;to be perplexed;to impair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3103
    },
    {
        "Front": "来場",
        "Back": "attendance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3104
    },
    {
        "Front": "酪農",
        "Back": "dairy (farm)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3105
    },
    {
        "Front": "落下",
        "Back": "fall;drop;come down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3106
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽観",
        "Back": "optimism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3107
    },
    {
        "Front": "濫用",
        "Back": "abuse;misuse;misappropriation;using to excess",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3108
    },
    {
        "Front": "理屈",
        "Back": "theory;reason",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3109
    },
    {
        "Front": "利根",
        "Back": "intelligence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3110
    },
    {
        "Front": "利子",
        "Back": "interest (bank)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3111
    },
    {
        "Front": "利潤",
        "Back": "profit;returns",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3112
    },
    {
        "Front": "理性",
        "Back": "reason;sense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3113
    },
    {
        "Front": "利息",
        "Back": "interest (bank)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3114
    },
    {
        "Front": "立体",
        "Back": "solid body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3115
    },
    {
        "Front": "立法",
        "Back": "legislation;lawmaking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3116
    },
    {
        "Front": "利点",
        "Back": "advantage;point in favor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3117
    },
    {
        "Front": "略語",
        "Back": "abbreviation;acronym",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3118
    },
    {
        "Front": "略奪",
        "Back": "pillage;plunder;looting;robbery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3119
    },
    {
        "Front": "流",
        "Back": "styleof;method of;manner of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3120
    },
    {
        "Front": "流通",
        "Back": "circulation of money or goods;flow of water or air;distribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3121
    },
    {
        "Front": "了",
        "Back": "finish;completion;understanding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3122
    },
    {
        "Front": "料",
        "Back": "material;charge;rate;fee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3123
    },
    {
        "Front": "領域",
        "Back": "area;domain;territory;field;region;regime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3124
    },
    {
        "Front": "了解",
        "Back": "comprehension;consent;understanding;roger (on the radio)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3125
    },
    {
        "Front": "領海",
        "Back": "territorial waters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3126
    },
    {
        "Front": "両極",
        "Back": "both extremities;north and south poles;positive and negative poles",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3127
    },
    {
        "Front": "良好",
        "Back": "favorable;satisfactory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3128
    },
    {
        "Front": "良識",
        "Back": "good sense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3129
    },
    {
        "Front": "良質",
        "Back": "good quality;superior quality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3130
    },
    {
        "Front": "了承",
        "Back": "acknowledgement;understanding (e.g. please be understanding of the mess during our renovation)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3131
    },
    {
        "Front": "良心",
        "Back": "conscience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3132
    },
    {
        "Front": "領地",
        "Back": "territory;dominion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3133
    },
    {
        "Front": "領土",
        "Back": "dominion;territory;possession",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3134
    },
    {
        "Front": "両立",
        "Back": "compatibility;coexistence;standing together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3135
    },
    {
        "Front": "旅客",
        "Back": "passenger (transport)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3136
    },
    {
        "Front": "旅券",
        "Back": "passport",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3137
    },
    {
        "Front": "履歴",
        "Back": "personal history;background;career;log",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3138
    },
    {
        "Front": "理論",
        "Back": "theory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3139
    },
    {
        "Front": "輪",
        "Back": "counter for wheels and flowers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3140
    },
    {
        "Front": "林業",
        "Back": "forestry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3141
    },
    {
        "Front": "類似",
        "Back": "analogous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3142
    },
    {
        "Front": "類推",
        "Back": "analogy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3143
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷酷",
        "Back": "cruelty;coldheartedness;relentless;ruthless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3144
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷蔵",
        "Back": "cold storage;refrigeration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3145
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷淡",
        "Back": "coolness;indifference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3146
    },
    {
        "Front": "恋愛",
        "Back": "love;love-making;passion;emotion;affections",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3147
    },
    {
        "Front": "連休",
        "Back": "consecutive holidays",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3148
    },
    {
        "Front": "連日",
        "Back": "every day;prolonged",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3149
    },
    {
        "Front": "連中",
        "Back": "colleagues;company;a lot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3150
    },
    {
        "Front": "連帯",
        "Back": "solidarity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3151
    },
    {
        "Front": "連邦",
        "Back": "commonwealth;federation of states",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3152
    },
    {
        "Front": "連盟",
        "Back": "league;union;alliance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3153
    },
    {
        "Front": "老衰",
        "Back": "senility;senile decay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3154
    },
    {
        "Front": "朗読",
        "Back": "reading aloud;recitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3155
    },
    {
        "Front": "浪費",
        "Back": "waste;extravagance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3156
    },
    {
        "Front": "労力",
        "Back": "labour;effort;toil;trouble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3157
    },
    {
        "Front": "碌な",
        "Back": "satisfactory;decent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3158
    },
    {
        "Front": "碌に",
        "Back": "well;enough;sufficient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3159
    },
    {
        "Front": "露骨",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;frank;blunt;plain;outspoken; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;conspicuous;open; 3.&nbsp;&nbsp;broad;suggestive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3160
    },
    {
        "Front": "論議",
        "Back": "discussion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3161
    },
    {
        "Front": "論理",
        "Back": "logic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3162
    },
    {
        "Front": "和",
        "Back": "sum;harmony;peace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3163
    },
    {
        "Front": "我がまま",
        "Back": "selfishness;egoism;wilfulness;disobedience;whim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3164
    },
    {
        "Front": "枠",
        "Back": "frame;slide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3165
    },
    {
        "Front": "惑星",
        "Back": "planet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3166
    },
    {
        "Front": "技",
        "Back": "art;technique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3167
    },
    {
        "Front": "態と",
        "Back": "on purpose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3168
    },
    {
        "Front": "態々",
        "Back": "expressly;specially;doing something especially rather than incidentally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3169
    },
    {
        "Front": "煩わしい",
        "Back": "troublesome;annoying;complicated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3170
    },
    {
        "Front": "渡り鳥",
        "Back": "migratory bird;bird of passage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3171
    },
    {
        "Front": "詫び",
        "Back": "apology",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3172
    },
    {
        "Front": "和風",
        "Back": "Japanese style",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3173
    },
    {
        "Front": "和文",
        "Back": "Japanese text;sentence in Japanese",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3174
    },
    {
        "Front": "藁",
        "Back": "straw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3175
    },
    {
        "Front": "割合に",
        "Back": "comparatively",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3176
    },
    {
        "Front": "割り当て",
        "Back": "allotment;assignment;allocation;quota;rationing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3177
    },
    {
        "Front": "割り込む",
        "Back": "to cut in;to thrust oneself into;to wedge oneself in;to muscle in on;to interrupt;to disturb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3178
    },
    {
        "Front": "割り算",
        "Back": "division (math)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3179
    },
    {
        "Front": "割引き",
        "Back": "discount;reduction;rebate;tenths discounted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3180
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪者",
        "Back": "bad fellow;rascal;ruffian;scoundrel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3181
    },
    {
        "Front": "アイデア",
        "Back": "idea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アクセル",
        "Back": "accelerator",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アップ",
        "Back": "up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アプローチ",
        "Back": "approach (in golf)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アマチュア",
        "Back": "amateur",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アラブ",
        "Back": "Arab",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アルカリ",
        "Back": "alkali",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アルミ",
        "Back": "aluminum (Al);aluminium",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アワー",
        "Back": "hour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アンケート",
        "Back": "(fr:) (n) questionnaire (fr: enquete);survey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アンコール",
        "Back": "encore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "イエス",
        "Back": "Jesus;yes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インターチェンジ",
        "Back": "interchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インターナショナル",
        "Back": "international",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インターフォン",
        "Back": "intercom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インテリ",
        "Back": "egghead;intelligentsia",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インフォメーション",
        "Back": "information",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インフレ",
        "Back": "inflation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ウェートレス",
        "Back": "waitress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "エアメール",
        "Back": "air mail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "エレガント",
        "Back": "elegant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "エンジニア",
        "Back": "engineer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "オーケー",
        "Back": "OK",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "オートマチック",
        "Back": "automatic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "オープン",
        "Back": "open",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "オリエンテーション",
        "Back": "orientation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "オレンジ",
        "Back": "an orange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "オンライン",
        "Back": "on-line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カーペット",
        "Back": "carpet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カクテル",
        "Back": "cocktail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カット",
        "Back": "cut;cutting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カテゴリー",
        "Back": "category",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カムバック",
        "Back": "comeback",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カメラマン",
        "Back": "cameraman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カルテ",
        "Back": "(de:) (n) clinical records (de: Karte)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガイド",
        "Back": "tour guide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カンニング",
        "Back": "cunning;cheat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガイドブック",
        "Back": "guidebook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガレージ",
        "Back": "garage (at house)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "キャッチ",
        "Back": "catch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "キャリア",
        "Back": "career;career government employee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "クイズ",
        "Back": "quiz",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "クラブ",
        "Back": "club;crab",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "クレーン",
        "Back": "crane",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "グラフ",
        "Back": "graph",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "グレー",
        "Back": "grey;gray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コーナー",
        "Back": "corner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゲスト",
        "Back": "guest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コマーシャル",
        "Back": "a commercial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コミュニケーション",
        "Back": "communication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンタクト",
        "Back": "contact;contact lens",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コメント",
        "Back": "comment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンテスト",
        "Back": "contest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コントラスト",
        "Back": "contrast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コントロール",
        "Back": "control",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンパス",
        "Back": "compass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "サイクル",
        "Back": "cycle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "サイズ",
        "Back": "size",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "サボる",
        "Back": "to be truant;to be idle;to sabotage by slowness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "サンキュー",
        "Back": "thank you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "サンタクロース",
        "Back": "Santa Claus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "シート",
        "Back": "seat;sheet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "システム",
        "Back": "system",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "シック",
        "Back": "chic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "シナリオ",
        "Back": "scenario",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ショー",
        "Back": "show",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ショック",
        "Back": "shock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジーパン",
        "Back": "jeans (lit: jeans pants);dungarees",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジャズ",
        "Back": "jazz",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジャンパー",
        "Back": "jacket;jumper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジャンプ",
        "Back": "jump",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジャンボ",
        "Back": "jumbo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジャンル",
        "Back": "genre",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スタジオ",
        "Back": "studio",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スチーム",
        "Back": "steam",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ストライキ",
        "Back": "strike",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ストレス",
        "Back": "stress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ストロー",
        "Back": "straw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ストロボ",
        "Back": "stroboscope (lit: strobo);strobe lamp;stroboscopic lamp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スピード",
        "Back": "speed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スプリング",
        "Back": "spring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スペース",
        "Back": "space",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スポーツカー",
        "Back": "sports car",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スラックス",
        "Back": "slacks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "セール",
        "Back": "sale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "セクション",
        "Back": "section",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "セックス",
        "Back": "sexual intercourse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "セレモニー",
        "Back": "ceremony",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "センス",
        "Back": "good sense (for music&nbsp;&nbsp;style&nbsp;&nbsp;tact&nbsp;&nbsp;etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゼリー",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;jelly; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ソース",
        "Back": "source",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ソックス",
        "Back": "socks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ソロ",
        "Back": "solo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイトル",
        "Back": "title",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイピスト",
        "Back": "typist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイマー",
        "Back": "timer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイミング",
        "Back": "timing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイム",
        "Back": "time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイムリー",
        "Back": "timely;run-batted-in (baseball);RBI",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイヤ",
        "Back": "tire;tyre",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイル",
        "Back": "tile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タレント",
        "Back": "talent;star;personality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タワー",
        "Back": "tower",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダース",
        "Back": "dozen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダウン",
        "Back": "down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダブる",
        "Back": "to coincide (fall on the same day);to have two of something;to repeat a school year after failing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダンプ",
        "Back": "dump",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "チームワーク",
        "Back": "teamwork",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "チェンジ",
        "Back": "change",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "チャイム",
        "Back": "chime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "チャンネル",
        "Back": "a channel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ティッシュペーパー",
        "Back": "tissue paper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "テレックス",
        "Back": "telex;teletypewriter exchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "データ",
        "Back": "data",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "デコレーション",
        "Back": "decoration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "デザート",
        "Back": "dessert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "デザイン",
        "Back": "design",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "デッサン",
        "Back": "(fr:) (n) rough sketch (fr: dessin)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "デモンストレーション",
        "Back": "demonstration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "トーン",
        "Back": "tone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "トラブル",
        "Back": "trouble (sometimes used as a verb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "トランジスター",
        "Back": "transistor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドライ",
        "Back": "dry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドライクリーニング",
        "Back": "dry cleaning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドライバー",
        "Back": "driver;screwdriver",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドライブイン",
        "Back": "drive in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドリル",
        "Back": "drill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ナイター",
        "Back": "game under lights (e.g. baseball) (lit: nighter);night game",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ナプキン",
        "Back": "napkin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ナンセンス",
        "Back": "nonsense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ニュー",
        "Back": "new",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ニュアンス",
        "Back": "nuance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ネガ",
        "Back": "(photographic) negative",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ノイローゼ",
        "Back": "(de:) (n) neurosis (de: Neurose)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ハンガー",
        "Back": "hangar;(coat) hanger;hunger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "バー",
        "Back": "bar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "バッジ",
        "Back": "badge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "バット",
        "Back": "bat;vat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "パジャマ",
        "Back": "pajamas;pyjamas",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "パチンコ",
        "Back": "pachinko (Japanese pinball)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "パトカー",
        "Back": "patrol car",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "パンク",
        "Back": "1.&nbsp;&nbsp;(abbr) puncture;bursting; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp;punk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ヒント",
        "Back": "hint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビールス",
        "Back": "virus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビジネス",
        "Back": "business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ファイト",
        "Back": "fight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ファイル",
        "Back": "file",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ファン",
        "Back": "fan;fun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "フィルター",
        "Back": "(camera) filter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "フェリー",
        "Back": "ferry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "フォーム",
        "Back": "foam;form",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "フロント",
        "Back": "front",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブーツ",
        "Back": "boots",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブーム",
        "Back": "boom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブザー",
        "Back": "buzzer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブルー",
        "Back": "blue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベース",
        "Back": "base;bass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベスト",
        "Back": "best;vest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベストセラー",
        "Back": "best-seller",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ペア",
        "Back": "pair;pear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ホース",
        "Back": "hose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ホール",
        "Back": "hall;hole",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボイコット",
        "Back": "boycott",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボルト",
        "Back": "volt;bolt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポーズ",
        "Back": "pause",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポイント",
        "Back": "point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポジション",
        "Back": "position",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポット",
        "Back": "pot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポンプ",
        "Back": "pump",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "マーク",
        "Back": "mark",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "マスコミ",
        "Back": "mass communication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "マッサージ",
        "Back": "massage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミスプリント",
        "Back": "misprint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミセス",
        "Back": "Mrs.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミュージック",
        "Back": "music",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミリ",
        "Back": "milli-;10^-3",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ムード",
        "Back": "mood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "メーカー",
        "Back": "maker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "メッセージ",
        "Back": "message",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "メディア",
        "Back": "media",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "メロディー",
        "Back": "melody",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "モーテル",
        "Back": "motel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "モニター",
        "Back": "(computer) monitor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ヤング",
        "Back": "young",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ユニーク",
        "Back": "unique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ユニフォーム",
        "Back": "uniform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ライス",
        "Back": "rice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ラベル",
        "Back": "label",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ランプ",
        "Back": "lamp;ramp;headlight;light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ルーズ",
        "Back": "loose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ルール",
        "Back": "rule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レース",
        "Back": "race;lace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レギュラー",
        "Back": "regular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レクリエーション",
        "Back": "recreation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レッスン",
        "Back": "lesson",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レディー",
        "Back": "lady",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レバー",
        "Back": "lever;liver",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レンジ",
        "Back": "range;stove",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レンタカー",
        "Back": "hire car (lit: rent-a-car)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レントゲン",
        "Back": "X-ray (lit: Roentgen)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ロープ",
        "Back": "rope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ローマ字",
        "Back": "romanization;Roman letters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3182
    },
    {
        "Front": "ロマンチック",
        "Back": "romantic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ワット",
        "Back": "watt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n1-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    }
]